[Music]
[Música]
The old postman passes me
The Old postman passes me
by Every
by Every
day not a
day not a
post telling me
post telling me
why you're
why You're
[Music]
[Música]
to be One For number
a be One For number
one Maybe two
one Maybe two
for number
for number
two but when he comes round to
two but when he comes round to
me there's Never
me there's Never
a from
a from
The Old Postman passes me
you The Old postman passes me
by not a
by not a
[Music]
[Música]
Word though he smiles he doesn't know
Word though he smiles he doesn't know
Why I haven't heard
Why i haven't heard
[Music]
[Música]
from the B of Dreams on his
from the B of Dreams on his
should i'd be grateful for just a white
should i'd be grateful for just a white
Li say your care again then I won't care
Li say your care Again then I won't care
When The Old Postman passes me by
When The Old postman passes me by
[Laughs]
[Risas]
[Music]
[Música]
either
o
[Laughs]
[Risas]
[Music]
[Música]
The old postman passes me
The Old postman passes me
by not a
by not a
[Music]
[Música]
Word though he smiles he doesn't know
Word though he smiles he doesn't know
Why I haven't
Why I haven't
heard from the B of Dreams on his
heard from the B of Dreams on his
shoulders
shoulders
I'd be grateful for just a white
i'd be grateful for just a white
Li Say You care Again then I won't care
Li Say You care Again then I won't care
When The Old
When The Old
Postman passes me by
postman passes me by
[Music]
[Música]
[Laughs]
[Risas]
I'm so
I'm so
lonesome I could
lonesome I could
Cry Just watching
Cry Just watching
couples
couples
passing
passing
by It's no fun
by It's no fun
Being all
Being all
Alone night
Alone night
wasn't meant to be that way it really
wasn't meant to be that way it really
isn't
isn't
right so I tell my
right so I Tell my
heart Don't
heart Don't
Die there must be
Die there must be
someone as Blue as
someone as Blue as
I just want someone to walk with
I I just want someone to Walk with
someone to
someone to
Talk just to help the time pass
Talk just to help the time pass
by I'm so
by I'm so
Lonesome I Could Cry
lonesome I could Cry
[Music]
[Música]
[Laughs]
[Risas]
so I tell my
so I Tell my
heart Don't
heart Don't
There must be someone to die there
Die there must be someone
as Blue as
as Blue as
I just want someone to walk
I I just want someone to Walk
with
with
someone To talk
someone To talk
with just to help the
with just to help the
time pass
time pass
by I'm so
by I'm so
l I
l I
could cry
could Cry
[Music]
[Música]
Walking by
Walking by
Myself
Myself
places talking to Myself about you
places talking to Myself about you
What a lonesome
What a lonesome
[Music]
[Música]
conversation I keep asking
conversation I keep asking
things and get no
things and get no
an sitting by
an sitting by
Myself with Nothing to
Myself with Nothing to
do talking to myself about
do talking to Myself about
you While I'm listening for
you While I'm listening for
kn on the door and dreaming that you
kn on the door and Dreaming that you
Walk
Walk
through I'll Keep talking to Myself
through I'll Keep talking to Myself
about you
about you
[Music]
[Música]
by
by
Myself places we
Myself places we
talking to
talking to
About myself
Myself about
you What lon some
you What lon some
conversation I keep asking
conversation I keep asking
things and I get no
things and I get no
an sitting by
an sitting by
Myself Nothing to
Myself Nothing to
talking to myself
do talking to Myself
But
But
You While I'm listening for your knock
You While I'm listening for your knock
on the
on the
door then Dreaming that you
door then Dreaming that you
soon
soon
through Now
through Now
Keep to
Keep to
Myself
Myself
about you
about you
[Music]
[Música]
hf
hf
do
do
Who If the Never
Who If the Never
Who cares What my Friends might
se Who cares What my Friends might
[Music]
[Música]
say or If the postman tells me there's
say or If the postman tells me there's
no Word today
no Word today
Who If I'm Left Alone
Who If I'm left Alone
[Music]
[Música]
How are you family? How are you?
qué tal familia Cómo estáis
Well today we have a
Bueno pues hoy tenemos un
a rather unpleasant direct, don't you
un directo bastante desagradable no os
I'm going to deceive you, I would love to tell you
voy a engañar sea me encantaría deciros
another thing but I think the live of
otra cosa pero creo que el directo de
today around the topic that deals with is
hoy en torno al tema que trata es
quite unpleasant no
bastante desagradable no
[Music]
[Música]
I don't even know how Rosaca is going to turn out
sé ni siquiera Cómo va a salir rosaca
beautiful heart hairstyle and thank you for
corazón precioso peinado y gracias por
remove your mustache by blowing a kiss
quitarte el bigote car lanzando un beso
I felt like it, I didn't
me apetecía no me
like G I don't like I don't like to be
gusta G no me gusta no me gusta estar
So the truth is that I like it better
así ait la verdad es que me gusta más
as it was but it had as it had as
como estaba pero tenía como tenía como
the beard is already very thick and I don't
la barba ya muy super poblada y no me
I wanted to start fixing and cutting
apetecía ponerme a arreglar cortar por
here leave the little mustache over there
aquí dejar el bigotillo por allá
So we start from scratch, we don't renew
entonces empezamos de cero no renovamos
face and as it grows we will
cara y conforme vaya creciendo Le vamos
Shaping again as it goes
Dando forma otra vez conforme vaya
We are growing, giving it shape but that
creciendo Le vamos Dando forma pero que
You know that I don't like it like that.
sepáis que no eh que no me gusta así
Hey, I don't like it like that. Now, of course.
eh que no me gusta así Ahora Claro está
a little better because I'm a little more
un poco mejor porque estoy un poco más
I'm not thin, I'm not brown
delgado no estoy Moreno
Well
bueno
Okay family, let's see the camera is a
bueno familia a ver la cámara está un
not bad because it had to be thrown away a bit
poco mal porque había que echarla un
a little further here There we are there
poco más para acá Ahí estamos ahí
we are
estamos
no but well but well besides I have myself
no pero bueno pero bueno además me tengo
that I have to peel, eh, and I also have to peel
que pelar eh además me tengo que pelar
by
por
there the focus very
ahí el foco muy
strong the truth is that the director of
fuerte la verdad es que el directillo de
today uncle
hoy tío
Oh, today's live stream!
Ah el directo de hoy vaya
cloth mother of God Oh
tela madre de Dios Ay
Nara
nara
eh is what I feel about what is
eh es que lo que siento ante lo que está
happening I could tell you that it would be
ocurriendo podría deciros que sería
disappointment but of course not disappointment with
decepción pero claro no decepción con
with people as such because they no longer
con las personas como tal porque ya no
you can be disappointed in people
te puedes decepcionar de las personas
that you don't expect anything good you know but
que no esperas nada bueno sabes pero a
the best a little disappointment for the
lo mejor un poco de decepción por la
society as such
sociedad como tal
humanity I wouldn't know what to call you
humanidad No sabría Cómo llamaros
eh I put the chat today just for
eh he puesto el chat hoy solo para
members because it is the topic is a topic
miembros porque es el tema es un tema
delicate and the truth is I wouldn't like it
delicado y la verdad no me gustaría
trolling spam nonsense at least
troleos spam tonterías por lo menos
while we are touching on the subject
mientras que estamos tocando el tema
Okay
vale
when we finish with the topic and we
cuando terminemos con el tema y nos
Let's go to the bun that Peppa has
vayamos al moño que Peppa le ha
answered ar of Troy there already it is
contestado ar de Troya ahí ya lo lo
I reopen okay since I
vuelvo a abrir vale desde que me
I understand that I have a bad feeling because Pili
enterado tengo un mal cuerpo pues Pili
If you read the sentence you freak out, that is to say it is
Si Tú lees la sentencia flipas o sea es
terrifying terrifying of
terrorífica terrorífica de
I'm really taking this and now we start
verdad me tomo esto y ahora empezamos
Okay, watch out, Tania says she's going to take it
vale ojo que Tania dice que va a tomar
measurements yes the pants will
medidas sí la del pantalón va a
take the pants will
tomar las del pantalón va a
take
tomar
Hey, says TT Javi, do what you have to.
eh dice TT Javi Haz lo que tengas que
do today and end it with this
hacer hoy y punto y final con esta
garbage people please and it will depend
basura de personas por favor e dependerá
it will depend on her
de dependerá de ella
Em Okay, now I'll explain it to you.
em Bueno ahora te explico ahora te
I explain, Tete, I'm going to take this and I
explico tete me voy a tomar esto y me
I'm going to take this and let's start the topic
voy a tomar esto y Y empezamos el tema
Ok, and we start to discuss the topic, let's see.
vale Y empezamos a tratar el tema vemos
reactions and we see what it is about
reacciones y vemos vemos de qué va la
move
movida
but it's brutal
pero es brutal
eh, those who always speak are the ones who
eh siempre hablan los que
Those who have always speak
tienen siempre hablan los que tienen
This is the ones who have to
esta o sea los que tienen que
Those who have always speak to be silent
callarse siempre hablan los que tienen
that
que
shut up but the worst thing is that it's not that, man
callarse pero lo peor No es eso tío lo
It's worse that there are people defending this.
peor es que haya gente defendiendo esto
uncle eh
tío eh
go
voy
Marini I'm going I'm going
marini voy voy
wait
espera
but you won't like it
pero no te va a gustar
Hey, okay.
Eh bueno
Marina is flirting with me on WhatsApp
Marina me está peloteando por WhatsApp
Okay, I'm telling you so you know that
vale os lo digo para que sepáis que que
He's been writing to me all day long
lleva todo el día escribiéndome por
WhatsApp to ask me silly questions How
WhatsApp para preguntarme tontería Cómo
hang a picture where I put an arcata
colgar un cuadro donde pongo un arcata
of a
de un
mirror finally finally finally finally
espejo en fin en fin en fin en fin
in short and in principle By the way it is being
en fin y en principio Por cierto se está
premiering video on the main channel
estrenando vídeo en el canal principal
It coincided with the live broadcast, not the video.
ha coincidido con el directo no el vídeo
of the Channel
del Canal
the main thing is always those who speak the most
principal siempre hablan los que más
They have to keep quiet but it is
tienen que callar pero es
how good to see
que bueno a ver
I don't know if my Lili is out there, I don't know if
no sé si está mi Lili por ahí no sé si
is my
está mi
Lilit, well it doesn't matter. I don't know if it is.
lilit bueno da igual No sé si está
working if Joana is around here or what
currando si está por aquí o qué Joana un
kiss
beso
beautiful Let's see let's go a little in
guapa A ver vamos a vamos a un poco en
context of what has happened in the
contexto de de lo que ha pasado en las
last hours
últimas horas
and I ask you to go I ask you to
y Os pido vamos Os pido el
respect that the subject deserves, okay, I know that
respeto que merece el tema vale sé que
You're probably going to get really pissed off
seguramente os vais a cabrear muchísimo
as we see things, okay, I know
conforme vayamos viendo cosas vale sé
This is going to make your blood boil.
que os va a hervir la sangre este
direct is not suitable for very people
directo no es apto para personas muy
sensitive I already warned you
sensibles Ya lo aviso
And no, I don't know if it will be the last live show, eh?
e no no sé si será el último directo eh
on this topic because I'm not going to talk here
sobre este tema porque aquí no voy a
go into depth on many things
entrar en profundidad en muchas cosas
that there are things that have not yet been said
que hay que todavía no se han dicho
Okay, I'm not going to read the sentence in this one.
vale no voy a leer la sentencia en este
live okay I don't know if I'll do another live
directo vale No sé si haré otro directo
reading The
leyendo La
sentence I think it will be rather A lo
sentencia Creo que será más bien A lo
better a topic to deal with well in the
mejor un tema para tratarlo bien en el
channel
canal
main with your clicks not with the
principal con sus clicks no con los
clips of the importance that has been given to
clips de la importancia que le ha dado a
she during these last two years to the
ella durante estos últimos dos años a la
sentence not the protagonist of this
sentencia no la protagonista de este de
This excerpt I don't think will be a video
este extracto No creo que será un vídeo
for the main channel very
para el canal principal muy
probably but it will depend on what
probablemente pero dependerá de de lo
that she is still her, you know, that is, yes
que sigue siendo ella sabes o sea si
keep being a pain if you continue
sigue tocando las narices si sigue
threatening if he continues to defame will depend
amenazando si sigue difamando dependerá
I really like her, I mean, eh, nothing more
de ella yo de verdad O sea eh sin más
okay this has come out this has chatted is
vale esto ha salido esto ha challado es
one more topic that we are not going to censor
un tema más que no nos vamos a censurar
and it is a topic that we are going to talk about
y es un tema del que vamos a hablar
evidently and now the one I follow
evidentemente y ya el el que yo siga
dealing with this topic or continue it
tratando el tema este o lo siga
extending because man will depend on
extendiendo pues hombre dependerá de
She Of course, obviously if she continues then
ella Claro evidentemente si sigue pues
Here we go
ahí vamos
because there is much more there is much more eh or
porque hay mucho más hay mucho más eh o
sea
sea
This is something that came out okay
esto Esto es una cosa que ha salido vale
because she made her
porque ella la hizo
public
pública
and there's a lot more behind this eh or
y y hay mucho más detrás de esto eh o
were you imagining this kind of person?
sea imaginaron no este tipo de persona
This type of characters, well, imagine
este tipo de personajes Pues imaginaros
everything that has to be behind it is not
todo lo que tiene que haber detrás no
Well this is something, this is one of them.
pues esto es algo esto es una de ellas
This is one of the things behind it
esto es una de las cosas que hay detrás
Okay
vale
eh here basically what happened is very
eh aquí básicamente lo que pasó es muy
simple the day we were doing
sencillo el día que estuvimos haciendo
the Corrillo that if I'm not mistaken was the
el Corrillo que si no me equivoco fue el
Tuesday was here alanne Consuelo
martes estaba aquí alanne Consuelo
Sister on the day of the Corrillo Who
Sor el día del Corrillo Quiénes
we were there was alanne sorco
estábamos estaba alanne sorco
Consuelo Carmen did not come
Consuelo Carmen no vino
He didn't even come there in the end, he didn't come there at all.
ahí ni vino al final aí no vino no al
in the end there is no consolation for the donkey, that is to say consolation
final no consuelo al asne o sea consuelo
To the donkey Sor and I were not four no
al asne Sor y yo no estábamos cuatro no
the other day It's done Yes, of course. Good.
el otro día Ya está Sí claro Bueno
Well, we were direct, we had the
pues el directo estábamos teníamos el
directly prepared I had prepared it
directo preparado yo lo había preparado
at noon before going to the gym and
al mediodía antes de irme al gimnasio y
all those things no and it was a direct from
todas esas cosas no y era un directo de
bun But I swear that I in the afternoon
moño Pero te lo juro que yo por la tarde
When I was preparing the live broadcast
cuando Estaba preparando el directo yo
I was laughing my head off, that is
me estaba descojonando de la risa o sea
the belly is so hard from laughing with the
la barriga durísima de la risa con la
Tania, the nonsense that she said
Tania la barbaridades que decía la
nonsense that he says or rather because it is a
tontería que dice o sea porque es una
very very short person eh or rather she is a
persona muy muy corta eh o sea es una
very very short person or rather it is no longer that
persona muy muy corta o sea ya no es que
say clown Because no no no it's not that it is
diga payasada Porque no no no es que es
a very very slow person very short very
una persona muy muy lerda muy corta muy
short very short very short okay or so
corta muy corta muy corta vale o sea se
I would say things like if you
ponía decir cosas como que si a ti te
They report it and you don't go through the procedure
denuncian y tú no vas el procedimiento
It is archived, he was farting live.
se archiva se tiraba peos en el directo
he exploded with anger with the con
se le explotaba con el cabreo con la con
the bad temper she has is not
la la mala leche esta que ella tiene no
and from which farts escaped, no
y y de la se le escapaba ventosidades no
I mean, I swear it was going to be a
O sea te lo juro que iba a ser un
straight up like super laughing we were
directo como super de risa nos estábamos
laughing and all that stuff is fine. And
descojonando y todo el rollo ese vale Y
It was a few minutes after the start of the
fue a los pocos minutos de empezar el
directly when they start but we are going to
directo cuando me empiezan pero vamos a
the few minutes I don't know if we had
los pocos minutos yo no sé si habíamos
entered into some topic still of the
entrado en algún tema todavía del
heart or in the greeting eh or that is to say it is that
corazón o en el saludo eh o sea es que
It was right after the live show started that I
fue al nada de empezar el directo me
They started sending via WhatsApp because
empezaron a mandar por WhatsApp pues
several tweets were getting tangled up in each other
varios tweets se estaba liando en se
I was messing around on Twitter with a
estaba liando en Twitter con una
information that they had
información que eh habían
found was not information that
encontrado no era una información que
was coming to light, eh, it was a
estuviese saliendo a la luz eh era una
information that was already public but
información que ya era pública pero la
people had found her okay what I
gente había dado con ella okay Yo lo que
I don't understand how this person
no entiendo es cómo esta persona se
can put people to defame
puede poner a difamar a la gente a dar
so much ass to people eh And to go from
tanto por culo a la gente eh Y a ir del
stick that is having something like that but of course
palo que va teniendo algo así pero claro
Now with the passing of the hours, well,
ahora con el paso de las horas Pues lo
I have been understanding that she is that this
he ido entendiendo ella Ella es que esto
He sees it as normal in his life and sees it as normal.
lo ve normal en su vida lo ve normal lo
see something you don't know you won't see it so
ve una cosa que no sabes no lo verá tan
serious defends it justifies it is worth it
grave lo defiende lo justifica vale os
I'm going to teach the information, okay?
voy a enseñar la información vale o sea
I'm going to show you the information we are
os voy a enseñar la información estamos
talking about Tania Palacios Tania Palacio
hablando de Tania Palacios Tania Palacio
from Barcelona that you already know that in
de de Barcelona que ya sabéis que en
YouTube is called Tania pm
YouTube se llama Tania pm
for years he was campaigning
durante años estuvo haciendo campaña
to try to get her husband out of the
para intentar sacar a su marido de la
He was sentenced to 8 years in prison
cárcel Lo condenaron a 8 años de prisión
for abusing a minor and he served
por abusar de una menor y cumplió
condemnation here in this tweet basically
condena aquí en este tweet básicamente
What I do is put the news as
lo que hago yo es poner la noticia como
My entire Twitter feed is worth news of
todo mi Twitter vale noticias de
youtubers that is bad news or
youtubers em que es una noticia mala o
news that leaves more room for Tania
una noticia que dejan más lugar a Tania
I don't owe Tania any kind of
yo no le debo a Tania ningún tipo de
hold anything back or do any favors for him
guardarle nada ni hacerle ningún favor
This was getting messy on Twitter, okay? And
esto se estaba liando en Twitter vale Y
Aside from this, there are a couple of things to clarify here.
aparte aquí hay que aclarar un par de
things look as you see here on the page
cosas mira como veis aquí en la página
from Facebook of the Ana Rosa program as
de Facebook del programa Ana Rosa como
You see here on Facebook, okay, as you can see
veis aquí en su Facebook vale como veis
here created a chain.org a page of
aquí creó un chain.org una página de
Facebook is worth spreading the word.
Facebook para darle difusión vale fuera
feminism looks at this publication
feminis mira en esta publicación llevaba
The husband served 13 months in prison
13 meses el marido en la cárcel cumplió
everything eh, I mean, he turned a lot of years old
todo eh o sea cumplió un montón de años
in jail Well a lot of years
en la cárcel Bueno un montón de años
Let's see, let's see.
em A ver vamos a ver
Let's see why this has
vamos a ver porque esto tiene
fabric point number
tela punto número
one point number
uno punto número
one This is not information that I
uno Esto no es una información que yo
I bring to light but it is not information
saco a la luz pero no es una información
that I bring to light is not even a
que saque yo a la luz ni es una
information that brings to light any
información que saque a la luz ninguna
of the people who were there
de las personas que la estaban
spreading in
difundiendo en
Twitter this is information that she
Twitter esto es una información que ella
for 8 years on their social networks
durante 8 años en en sus redes sociales
on web pages and even creating a
en páginas web e incluso creando un
chain.org
chain.org
was spreading and asking for diffusion
fue difundiendo y pidiendo difusión
even collecting signatures
incluso haciendo una recogida de firmas
because according to her the sentence of this
porque según ella la sentencia de este
The abuser was unfair and had to be removed.
abusador era injusta y había que sacarlo
the sentence is worth the prison sentence
de la cárcel vale la sentencia la
we have the sentence, we have it and
tenemos vale la sentencia la tenemos Y
Of course the sentence is
claro que la Claro que la sentencia es
an injustice the ruling is a
una injusticia el fallo es una
injustice because 8 years is very little
injusticia porque 8 años es muy poco
for what happened or
para lo que pasó o
Surely many of you have
sea seguramente muchos de ustedes habéis
having already read the sentence, the sentence is
leído ya la sentencia la sentencia se
It's out there surfing the internet no By
está por ahí recorriendo internet no Por
What? Well, because she is on these pages
qué Pues porque ella en estas páginas
web And on this chain.org and on the page
web Y en este chain.org y en la página
by Ana Rosa and on her Facebook for no
de Ana Rosa y en su Facebook durante no
I know how many years and spreading it and
sé cuántos años y difundiéndolo y
Spamming asking for a Claro signature
spameando pidiendo una de firma Claro
Well, it puts a series of data
pues pone una serie de datos la
nationality the name the name of the
nacionalidad el nombre el nombre del
judge even went against the
juez incluso iba en contra del
magistrate speaking out against the
magistrado manifestándose en contra del
magistrate with what respect she had for
magistrado con lo que respetaba ella a
the magistrate judges are not worth it then
los magistrados jueces no vale pues
Of course people have quickly found
claro la gente rápidamente ha encontrado
the
la
sentence Why people find
sentencia Por qué la gente encuentra
This is why people find this
esto por qué la gente encuentra esto
This finds it
esto lo encuentra
because Tania in the morning as we already saw
porque Tania por la mañana como ya vimos
Here he began to say in his live broadcast that
aquí se puso a decir en su directo que
She had been in jail for three years
ella había estado TR años en la cárcel
I don't know if it's a troll or a joke, I don't know.
no sé si como un troleo una broma no sé
what's going on in that person's head
qué lo que pasa por la cabeza de esa
person is worth clear people searched Tania
persona vale clar la gente buscó Tania
Palacios Barcelona prison and in the
Palacios Barcelona prisión y en la
first search started to come out
primera búsqueda empezó a salir a la
people All the blogs and all these
gente Todos los blogs y todas estas
things she had published
cosas que ella había publicado
Ok then of course the 8 years in prison
Vale entonces claro los 8 años de cárcel
00000 compensation is worth
00000 de indemnización vale
a crime of sexual abuse of a minor
un delito de abuso sexual a una menor
continued in the
continuado en el
continuous time in time
tiempo continuado en el tiempo
Okay, and one about gender violence is okay.
vale Y uno de violencia de género vale
That's why I think it's like a year of
que por eso creo que es como un año de
of such worth
de tal vale
I repeat and insist, I repeat, I insist here
eh repito e insisto repito insisto aquí
There are two important things to do
hay dos cosas importantes que hay que
make it clear why there are people who are very
dejar claras porque hay gente que es muy
short Okay point number one This is not even
cortita Okay punto número uno Esto ni lo
I make it public nor do they make it public
hago público yo ni lo hacen pública las
people
personas
that they begin to find it and begin
que empiezan a encontrárselo y empiezan
if something gets going on Twitter, he does it
a se empieza a liar en Twitter lo hace
Tania has it in her public
público Tania lo tiene Tania en sus
social networks because Tania had done
redes sociales porque Tania había hecho
a campaign a collection of signatures Okay
una campaña una recogida de firmas Vale
and had been there for 8 years
y había estado 8 años
publishing it This is not a private matter
publicándolo Esto no es un tema privado
There are private topics, eh, that is, topics
temas privados hay eh o sea temas
private, there are private issues, there is a lot of stuff
privados hay temas privados hay que tela
but what sailor cloth is worth if someone
pero que tela marinera vale si alguien
I would have liked to attack her with themes
hubiera querido atacarla con temas
private individuals have to attack them, eh without
privados tiene para atacarlas eh sin
having taken this out
haber sacado Esto
Okay, topic, fabric, where he lives, how he lives, how
vale tema tela dónde vive cóm vive Cómo
it is or rather fabric. Eh, many things, many things.
se o sea tela Eh muchas cosas muchas
things many things many things worth
cosas muchas cosas muchísimas cosas vale
But this is not a private matter, this is not
Pero esto no es un tema privado esto no
belongs to the privacy of
pertenece a la privacidad de
Tania this is one thing This is campaign
Tania esto es una cosa Esto es campaña
that she does on her networks by spamming
que ella hace en sus redes haciendo spam
not only on your Facebook but
en la no solamente en su Facebook sino
signature collections on chain.org
recogidas de firmas en chain.org
spreading it heavily on pages of
difundiéndolo fuertemente en páginas de
TV programs, that is, looking for her
programas de la tele o sea buscando ella
a lot of diffusion she seeks to have diffusion
mucha difusión ella busca tener difusión
on this topic
en este tema
okay and point number two which is also
vale y punto número dos que también es
another nonsense that has
otra tontería que ha
heard and point number two
escuchado y punto número dos
This is not a This is not using a
Esto no es un Esto no es utilizar a un
familiar to attack Tania
familiar para atacar a Tania
Eh, this is not using a family member to
Eh Esto no es usar a un familiar para
attack Tania now I'm going to tell you the
atacar a Tania ahora os voy a contar la
story is that it is mind-blowing it is
historia es que es alucinante es
mind-blowing okay when when this comes out
alucinante vale cuando cuando esto sale
This is amazing This is amazing
Es que esto es flipante Es que esto es
amazing today Tania pm has 2
flipante a día de hoy Tania pm lleva 2
years trying to cancel me because in the
años intentando cancelarme porque en el
In the past I insulted people on YouTube with the
pasado insulté a gente en YouTube con la
that I had
que tuve
conflicts okay this lady has been
conflictos vale esta señora ha estado
two [ __ ]
dos [__]
years two [ __ ]
años dos putísimas
years wanting to cancel me because I
años queriendo cancelarme porque yo
had insulted
había insultado a
people because I had insulted a
gente porque yo había insultado a un
character like Joan
personaje como Joan
flat and because I will look at her and at
planas y porque yo a la a la miare y a
Miare's mother had told her hair
la madre de miare le había dicho pelo
broom and crazy old woman Of course where we are going to
escoba y vieja loca Claro dónde vamos a
compare that to a rape of a woman
comparar eso con una violación a una
minor from 11 to 15 years old
menor desde los 11 años hasta los 15
years Oh, is that the right to honor
años Uy es que el derecho al honor a
Tania Bueno thought it was more serious than a
Tania Bueno le parecía más grave que un
bottle hit
botellazo
it seemed to him
le parecía
very serious live broadcasts almost every day
gravísimo directos casi todos los días
with the damn thing
con la puñetera
sentence reading The damn sentence
sentencia leyendo La puñetera sentencia
without
sin
anonymize and it turns out that the
anonimizar y resulta que la
aunt has been campaigning for
tía ha estado haciendo campaña para
get someone out of jail
sacar de la cárcel a un
uncle with whom she married and trained
tío con el que se ha casado y ha formado
a family and so on
una familia y demás
who abused a minor from the age of 11
que abusó de una menor desde los 11
until the
hasta los
15 and I will not go into all of them
15 y no voy a entrar en todos los
details and in all the proven facts
detalles y en todos los hechos probados
that puts that sentence because it is from
que pone esa sentencia porque es de
horror story Pablo said something
historia de terror Pablo ha dicho algo
On his Twitter Pablo has said something in his
en su Twitter Pablo ha dicho algo en su
Twitter I'm not going to go into detail
Twitter yo no voy a entrar en detalle a
unless she keeps being a pain
no ser que ella siga dando el [__]
obviously because it is clear that
evidentemente porque claro es que
Aquitaine is lying is that
aquitania está mintiendo es que
Aquitaine is lying as always
aquitania está mintiendo como siempre
Of course Tania says here that she was a
claro es que Tania aquí dice que era una
unjust conviction Of course it was unfair
condena injusta Claro que era injusta
Tania is unfair, it is unfair to her.
Tania es injusta es injusta para la
victim who will not be forgotten Of course
víctima que no se va a olvidar Claro que
The sentence is unfair but for the
es injusta la condena pero para la
victim 8 years with that
víctima 8 años con eso se
pay with that you pay with 8 years with
paga con eso se paga con 8 años con
50,000 euros
50.000 eur se
pay that a report that here Tania it
paga que un informe que aquí Tania lo
what was I saying
que estaba diciendo
ok but
vale pero
Good night Javi, telesalseo family no
Buenas noches Javi familia telesalseo no
Never put yourself at the same level as that woman
te pongas nunca la altura de esa mujer
but there will never be height
pero es que no va a haber altura nunca
No one will ever see the height of this
nunca va a ver nadie a altura de esta es
that the sentence for me is worse than the
que la sentencia para mí es peor que la
Daniel's
de Daniel
Sancho is a different crime, he has no
Sancho es otro delito diferente no tiene
nothing to do with it but for me it's worse
nada que ver pero para mí es peor yo
I think there is nothing worse than things
creo que no hay nada peor de las cosas
that we have read
que hemos leído
There is nothing worse than what we have
ahí no hay nada peor de lo que hemos
read there and it is telling you here the
leído ahí y te está diciendo aquí la
The girl is telling you here that
tipa te está diciendo aquí la tipa que
he should be released from prison
haba habría que sacarlo de la cárcel que
They sentenced him without evidence to 8 years.
lo condenaron sin pruebas a 8 años a ti
They condemn you without evidence, of course, to two
te condenan sin pruebas claro a dos
crimes one of gender violence in the
delitos uno de violencia de género en la
family and another to sexual abuse of a
familia y otro a abusos sexuales a una
minor without proof that there was no
menor sin prueba taña que no había
evidence that there was no
pruebas que no había
tests the proven facts of the
pruebas los hechos probados de la
sentence does not say the same thing
sentencia no dice lo mismo
Hey, there was no proof, she tells you.
eh que no había prueba te dice la
colleague, but be careful what you told him
colega pero eh cuidado que le has dicho
broom hair I don't know who we're going to throw at you
pelo escoba no sé quién vamos a echarte
from the internet we are going to we are going to we are going to unite
de internet vamos a vamos a vamos a unir
To all the YouTubers who hate Javi
a todos los youtubers que odien a Javi
oliveira Because he told this hair
oliveira Porque le ha dicho a esta pelo
broom has told the other clown oops
escoba al otro le ha dicho payaso uy
Oh, precisely the lady, eh, who takes and
uy precisamente la señora eh que coge y
when you are habitually arguing in
cuando está discutiendo habitualmente en
your networks here [ __ ] on the [ __ ]
sus redes aquí se caga en en la [__]
mother Ada of a certain Mari 13 okay Uy
madre Ada de una tal Mari 13 vale Uy
Look, oh, look, have you seen the faces of those people?
Mira Uy Mira has visto la cara de esos
rum that has how many do you eat? Oh but
ron que tiene cuántas te comes Uy pero
If this lady was putting me
si esta señora me estaba poniendo a mí
a click in which I say I don't know what
un click en el que yo digo no sé qué de
a tale of a
un cuento de una
Little fox, oh oh oh, how many do you eat?
zorrita Uy uy uy Cuántas te comes vaya
face of
cara de
[ __ ] It's really incredible
zorrón Es que de verdad increíble
incredible
increíble
Look, they want to make a
Mira quieren hacer de un
convicted of unlawful interference in
condenado por intromisión ilegítimo en
the right to honor a victim This yes
el derecho al honor una víctima Esto sí
which is to make a fool of oneself and mock
que es hacer el ridículo y mofarse de
a
una
Javi Oliveira says yes he can
sentencia Javi oliveira sí puede
be called The
llamarse El
condemned is spoken of and carried out with almost
condenado se habla y se lleva con casi
all people or with all
todas las personas o con todas las
people who have sued me and those
personas que me han demandado y esas
people are putting her on
personas la van la van poniendo a ella
up to date on how the procedures are going
al día de de cómo van los procedimientos
how I dress to the court of of of
de cómo voy vestido al juzgado de de de
What time do I have to declare in? I don't know.
a qué hora tengo que declarar en no sé
where we are going to see if from now on
dónde vamos a ver si a partir de ahora
Well, on the part of Joan Planas, yes.
bueno por por parte de Joan planas sí
that Joan Planas has already come out to defend her
que Joan planas ya ha salió a defenderla
Ok, on the part of Joan Plana I already know that
vale por parte de Joan plana ya sé que
yes okay, that is, Joan flat was not me
sí vale o sea Joan plana se estuvo no me
I can believe it
lo puedo creer
racel don't you
racel no te
I believe Mother of God on Johan's side
creo madre de Dios por parte de Johan
plan yes Johan planas was yes Johan
plan sí Johan planas se estuvo si Johan
plan was celebrating and saying that
plan estuvo celebrando y diciendo que
It was karma that the death of the suicide of
era karma el fallecimiento el suici de
about Adria's girlfriend who is not going to say
de la novia de adria que no va a decir
Joan Plana Joan Plana is her war
Joan plana Joan plana es su guerra
against Javi Oliveira and against the environment
contra Javi oliveira y contra el entorno
by Javi Oliveira or the youtubers with whom
de Javi oliveira o los youtubers con los
that he was fighting that if he was going to continue
que él se peleaba que si se va a seguir
talking with Tania Claro Claro
hablando con Tania Claro claro
Of course, and by the way, game over, game over
claro y por cierto el game over el game
over I, like many people, go through it
over yo como mucha gente me lo paso por
there we spend it there okay because
ahí nos lo pasamos por ahí vale porque
what matters is
lo que importa es
what a ruling of the
lo que dice una sentencia de la
Barcelona provincial court already
audiencia provincial de Barcelona ya
You can take the game over and broadcast it
podéis [__] el game over y difundirlo
wherever you want
por donde queráis
okay because there is a FJ sentence that is that
vale porque hay una sentencia FJ es que
There is no better way to stop so much game
no hay más vale dej de tant Game
decided
decidido
[Music]
[Música]
take this good this
tomar Esto bueno esto
with what has
con con lo que ha
exploited with what has been exploited
explotado con lo que ha explotado
I obviously haven't been able to remember the
evidentemente no he podido recordar el
I couldn't help but remember the case of
no he podido evitar recordar el caso de
Carlos
Carlos
Salgado This young man who has a future
Salgado Este joven Quién es tenes futuro
in the gossip, kid, my country was formed
en el salseo chaval mi país se formó un
hurricane after a tremendous fart that
huracán después de tremendo pedo que se
I sent you a kiss from Spain
mandó desde España te quiero un beso
King, let's remember the case of Carlos
Rey vamos a recordar el caso de Carlos
Salgado
Salgado
What I'm going to tell you today is going to
lo que os voy a contar hoy os va a
I have to ruin the whole week
arruinar toda la semana tengo que
warn that after finishing watching
advertir que después de terminar de ver
you will surely stay with this video
este vídeo seguramente os vais a quedar
with a very bad feeling But still you
con muy mal cuerpo Pero igualmente Os
I ask that you see it in its entirety. Although it is going to
pido que lo veáis entero Aunque va a
It will take a long time to see it until the end because
quedar largo verlo hasta el final porque
These are things that need to be known
son cosas que se tienen que saber
surely to many of you who are
seguramente a muchos de los que estáis
watching this video to other people no or
viendo Este vídeo a otra gente no o
the name of Carlos Salgado will sound and
sonará el nombre de Carlos Salgado y
I say this because the case of this
esto lo digo porque el caso de este
man has become very media-savvy
hombre se ha hecho muy mediático ha dado
many interviews on television in
mucha entrevistas en televisiones en
newspapers and such Since During the
periódicos y tal Ya que Durante los
recent years has experienced the greatest
últimos años ha vivido la mayor
nightmare for any parent recently
pesadilla para cualquier padre hace poco
More than a decade ago this gentleman started a
más de una década este señor inició una
relationship with a foreign woman from the
relación con una mujer extranjera de la
which resulted in the birth of his daughter
cual tuvo fruto el nacimiento de su hija
Carolina as life is not a fairy tale
Carolina como la vida no es un cuento de
Had Well, for ha or for B that relationship is not
Had Pues por ha o por B esa relación no
It went well and ended in divorce.
fue bien y terminó en divorcio el
divorce was very contentious from the beginning
divorcio fue muy conflictivo desde el
first moment to such an extent that the mother
primer momento a tal punto que la madre
he even prevented the visiting regime
llegó a impedir el régimen de visita
For Carlos, not only that, but also
para Carlos no solo eso sino que además
filed a lawsuit against Carlos for
interpuso contra Carlos una demanda por
alleged sexual abuse of the girl
supuestos abusos sexuales a la niña
a claim that was of course dismissed
demanda que por supuesto fue desestimada
from the first moment and despite
desde el primer momento y a pesar de
This in September 2016 things were
esto en septiembre de 2016 las cosas se
they got much worse by disobeying
pusieron muchísimo peor desobedeciendo
to the judge and social services
al juez y a los servicios sociales la
Carolina's mother took the girl and left
madre de Carolina cogió a la niña y se
He took her to his country, Kyrgyzstan.
la llevó a su país kirguistán kirguistán
It is a country that belongs to Central Asia
es un país que pertenece a Asia central
where the International Convention does not apply
donde no rige el convenio Internacional
of the HAA of child abduction
de la haa de sustracción de menores de
1980 therefore Carlos has it
1980 por por lo tanto Carlos lo tiene
very difficult to get her daughter back
muy difícil para recuperar a su hija
Carlos saw this coming and in
Carlos Esto se lo veía venir y en
He had repeatedly warned the
reiteradas ocasiones había advertido al
judged that this could happen but
juzgado de que esto podía pasar pero
By the time the law acted the girl was no longer
para cuando la ley actuó la niña ya no
I was in Spain, I have to let you know.
estaba en España tengo que comunicaros
that I have had the opportunity to meet
que he tenido la oportunidad de reunirme
with Carlos and he has introduced me to all the
con Carlos y me ha presentado todos los
court documents that I have
documentos judiciales que le he
requested to verify that all the
solicitado para comprobar que todo el
The course of this story is as follows
transcurso de esta historia es como se
has counted and I have to say that it is not
ha contado y tengo que afirmar que no
It is only as it has been told
solamente es que sea como se ha contado
but it is even worse among others
sino que todavía es peor entre otras
things the sentence Don un has taught me
cosas me ha enseñado la sentencia Don un
judge grants him sole custody
juez le concede la custodia en exclusiva
from Carolina and they take away her homeland
de Carolina y le retiran la patria
power to the mother Hello Carolina today is
potestad a la madre Hola Carolina hoy es
January 7
7 de enero de
2020 today you turn 12 years old and surely you already
2020 hoy cumplís 12 años y seguro que ya
you are a grown woman
estás hecha to una mujercita
Unfortunately it's been a long time since I last
Lamentablemente Hace mucho tiempo que no
See you It's already the third birthday that
nos vemos Ya es el tercer cumpleaños que
I can't celebrate it
no lo puedo festejar
with you but I have hope that
contigo pero tengo la esperanza de que
at some point we will see each other again
en algún momento nos volvamos a ver nos
let us meet again and may we be able
volvamos a encontrar y que podamos
celebrate all the birthdays you have left
festejar todos los cumples que te quedan
This man has not been able to see anyone for 3 years.
este hombre lleva 3 años sin poder ver a
his daughter this man has been with him for 3 years
su hija este hombre lleva 3 años
Living in hell as a father I can
viviendo en infierno como padre os puedo
affirm that any of us if
afirmar que a cualquiera de nosotros si
if we were given a choice, surely
nos dieran a elegir seguramente
we would choose before you tear us away
elegiríamos antes que nos arrancas las
four limbs before separating
cuatro extremidades antes que separarnos
of our children Carlos with the help of
de nuestros hijos Carlos con ayuda de
A YouTuber has opened a crowdfunding campaign
una youtuber ha abierto un crowdfunding
because they need money to travel to
porque necesitan dinero para viajar a
Kyrgyzstan and at least see it
kirguistán y por lo menos verla e
try to manage in that there at least
intentar gestionar en ese ahí al menos
that the law forces the mother to
que la ley le obligue a la madre a
allow him to see his daughter to allow him eh
permitirle ver a su hija a permitirle eh
let him have a relationship with his father and
dejarle tener relación con su padre y
This is because bringing it back to you
esto porque ya traérsela de vuelta a
Spain has already completely ruled it out.
España lo tiene totalmente descartado ya
that as I tell you in that country then the
que como os digo en ese país pues las
laws do not agree with those of
leyes no se ponen de acuerdo con las de
Spain and it is almost impossible worth it
España y es casi imposible vale el
YouTuber Johan Plana offered to do it for him
youtuber Johan plana se ofreció hacerle
an interview to publicize your
una entrevista para darle difusión a su
case I rather think it was For
caso yo más bien pienso que era Para
take advantage of the virality of the moment but
aprovechar la viralidad del momento pero
Well the important thing is that I was going to do it
bueno lo importante es que lo iba a
help because from one day to the next he decides
ayudar pues de un día para otro decide
not just waste time
no solamente tirar a la basura el tiempo
loaned by Carlos to give him the
cedido por Carlos para darle la
interview but also refused to
entrevista sino que además de negarse a
publishing that interview begins to
publicar esa entrevista comienza a
insult him, say very harmful things to him and
insultarlo a decirle cosas muy dañinas y
to try to convince people that
a intentar convencer a la gente de que
Don't donate money to Carlos saying
no le donen dinero a Carlos diciendo
things like he wants the money for
cosas como que quiere el dinero para
spend it
gastármelo
I am a hypocrite, we have already seen that you
soy un hipócrita a ti ya hemos vicho que
No, I mean, this tweet seems mind-blowing to me.
no O sea este tweet me parece alucinante
how to rub it in a father's face
cómo restregar por la cara a un padre
who has lost his daughter that things
que ha perdido a su hija que las cosas
They're not doing well. Wow, you scoundrel.
no le van bien Wow Sinvergüenza
illiterate does not care about his daughter what
analfabeto no le importa su hija lo que
What matters is being the center of attention
le importa es ser el centro de atención
using his daughter uses his daughter to be
usando a su hija usa a su hija para ser
the spotlight is asking
el centro de atención está pidiendo
money to travel with a feminist
dinero para viajar con una feminista el
day I was with the father we wanted to go
día que estuve con el padre queríamos ir
to a very posh Putin But he told me that
a un Putin muy pijo Pero me dijo que
I would wait for crow funding. This was
esperara al crow funding Esto fue
totally denied at the moment by the
totalmente desmentido al momento por el
Carlos himself since the day he was
propio Carlos ya que el día que estuvo
with Joan Plana recording the interview
con Joan plana grabando la entrevista
It was more than a year ago and the crow funding
fue hace más de un año y el crow funding
They didn't open it until January, okay, so
no lo abrieron hasta enero vale o sea
lies have very short legs
las mentiras tienen las patas muy cortas
Joan flat after exposing this
Joan plana después de exponer esta
lie began to say that it was
mentira empezó a decir que era
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
Sarcasm is longer, okay, you can see it.
Sarcasmo es más largo vale podéis ver el
gin over whole and there you see all the
gin over entero y ahí veis toda la
history but well you know what he did
historia pero bueno sabéis Qué hizo
Tania against this man Carlos
Tania contra este hombre Carlos
Tania began to
Tania se puso a
Tania started attacking Carlos
atacar Tania se puso a atacar a Carlos
Salgado for defending Joan Plana to his
Salgado por defender a Joan plana a su
friend Joan flat to a man who
amigo Joan plana a un hombre al que la
mother of his
madre de su
daughter falsely reported abuse
hija denunció falsamente por por abusos
the girl was falsely accused of abuse
a la niña por abuso lo acusó falsamente
He finally ended up abusing the girl.
de abusar de la niña al final terminó él
winning custody and motherhood
ganando la custodia y la madre la madre
He kidnapped the girl and took her to
la secuestró a la niña y se la llevó a
Kyrgyzstan
kirguistán
and well, like me, I'm planning to attack this one
y bueno como yo en plan ataca este
man because he fought with him and so on
hombre porque se peleó con él y demás
Well Tania did it
pues Tania lo
Tania attacked a man Carlos
ataca Tania atacó a un hombre a Carlos
Salgado who has his daughter kidnapped
Salgado que tiene a su hija secuestrada
to this man who had received a
a este hombre que había recibido una
complaint
denuncia
false claim of abusing his daughter to try
falsa de abusar de la hija para intentar
take it off having what
quitársela teniendo lo que
has how it is
tiene cómo lo
you see, I
veis total yo
when when this happens
cuando cuando pasa esto
Hey, when does this happen, that I put the tweet?
eh cuando pasa esto de que pongo el twit
People weren't getting into a mess on Twitter.
no se estaba liando en Twitter la gente
had it ...
lo había lo había difundido lo había
I sincerely think that
yo sinceramente lo que me pienso es
that no one is going to support this no O
que que nadie va a apoyar esto no O
be a
sea un
abuse an abuse to a
abuso un abuso a una
minor continuous over time
menor continuado en el tiempo
from a 40 year old person to a girl of
de una persona de 40 años a una niña de
11 until the
11 hasta los
15 what is your name
15 cómo se llama
that and that Tania defended
eso y que Tania defendía
that saying that there was no
eso diciendo que no había
evidence goes beyond disgust man you
pruebas va más allá del asco hombre tú
You'll tell me Alice
me dirás Alicia
when this news
cuando esta noticia
I thought that
sale Yo pensaba que
It would be a case where everyone
sería un caso en el que todo el mundo
I would more or less agree
estaría más o menos de acuerdo
No, I mean, I thought they weren't going to come here.
no O sea yo pensaba que aquí no iban a
support
apoyar a
Tania, let's see, I understand that the accounts of
Tania a ver entiendo que las cuentas de
Javier canino Wilson the stalkers who
Javier canino Wilson los acosadores que
that they are doing it no no yes the
que lo están haciendo no no si la
would support people are harassers of al
apoyarían la gente son acosadores de al
Veira doesn't see my face but I am
veira no me estan su cara pero estoy
watching on Twitter
viendo en Twitter a
people
gente
supporting them, I don't know if in more places but
apoyándoles no sé si en más sitios pero
on Twitter at least people
en Twitter por lo menos gente
supporting you all my support Tania a kiss to
apoyándola todo mi apoyo Tania un beso a
you to the
ti a los
yours I'm getting sick
tuyos me estoy poniendo hasta malo
telling it
contándolo
No, I swear to you that when I
No aini yo te juro que yo cuando me
when they told me when we talked about
cuando me contaron cuando hablamos de
This after the live okay eh I'll tell you
esto después del directo vale eh yo te
I swear I was saying this, they're not going to do it
juro que yo decía esto no lo van a
support this is not going to support it
apoyar esto no lo va a apoyar
Nobody for you Javi but for me
nadie por ti Javi pero por mí
they support me they support
apoyan por mí apoyan
That's what I've done to them in life.
eso o sea qué les he hecho en la vida
What have I done to the people in the
Qué les he hecho yo a la gente en la
life so that they are able to
vida para que por sean capaces de
defend
defender
This is all my support Tania, a kiss to you
esto todo mi apoyo Tania un beso a ti a
the
los
yours people with children
tuyos gente con hijos
Hey, if they support Sancho, it's not for you. Not everything.
eh si apoyan a Sancho por ti no No todo
whatever it is, it's already done
lo que sea es que ya ha quedado
proven that it can already be clear worse
demostrado que ya puede ser claro peor
that there is nothing like this in life
que esto no hay nada no en la vida no
There is nothing worse than this
peor que esto no hay nada
No, I don't understand that when Loli is
No yo entiendo que cuando Loli se
He invented cancer. Well, nothing about that at all.
inventó el cáncer Pues nada en eso todo
against me that Loli invents a
en contra mí que Loli se inventa un
cancer against Javi that Loli
cáncer en contra de Javi que que Loli
He says that the other thing about the 240 is
dice que que lo de los 240 la otra en
against Javi
contra de Javi
that everything everything everything that is everything
que todo todo todo lo que sea todo lo
that it is around me that they turn against me
que sea en torno mío se ponen en contra
but whatever comes out
pero salga lo que
come out What harm have I done to all that
salga Qué daño le he hecho yo a toda esa
people who are capable of defending
gente que son capaces de defender
these are the arguments
esto los argumentos
worth the arguments that we are
vale los argumentos que es que estamos
taking out private life and that we are
sacando la vida privada y que estamos
using a relative to
utilizando a un familiar para
attack her how
atacarla cómo
as she herself has spread for 8
cómo ella misma ha difundido durante 8
years a campaign even a collection of
años una campaña incluso una recogida de
signatures on the
firmas en la
who defends and claims that he is her husband
que defiende y afirma que es su marido
a child sexual abuser of a minor
un abusador sexual de menor de una menor
Do you know what sexual abuse is?
sabéis lo que es un abuso sexual a una
under 11 years old 12 years old 13
menor de 11 años 12 años 13
years you know what it is or not Or we are not
años sabéis lo que es o no O no estamos
what we are up to
en lo que estamos
talking This is not a private matter Eh
hablando Esto no es un tema privado Eh
This is a topic that made headlines
Esto es un tema que fue titulares de
news at that time was suitable for
noticias en aquella época fuera apte de
that she was able to do this
que fuera apte de que ella hiciera esta
campaign and had this campaign until the
campaña y tuviera esta campaña hasta el
yesterday in their networks collected
día de ayer en sus redes recogida de
Sign it and put it all over Facebook.
Firma lo pusiera en todo Facebook en
all pages this is not This is not a
todas las páginas esto no Esto no es un
issue
tema
private is that there are people who are
privado es que hay gente que está
Saying now, well, this opens us up
diciendo ahora Bueno pues esto nos abre
the way clear so that we can
la vía libre para que nosotros podamos
open Investigate the Private Life of
abrir Investigar la vida Privada de
Javi's alanne from I don't know what to have
alanne de Javi de no sé qué tener
balls to have balls but not to love
[__] tener [__] pero no a m a d
You have a hug and greeting Javi, I send you
tienen que un abrazo y saludo Javi se te
loves a lot and by the way These are
quiere mucho y por cierto Estos son
actors you paid you don't fool me it's very
actores que pagaste no me engañas es muy
strong is very strong Jorge a kiss
fuerte es muy fuerte Jorge un beso
Thank you very much, uncle.
Muchas gracias tío
one thing this person has done in
una cosa que esta persona ha hecho en
public and has spread in public and has
público y ha difundido en público y ha
made a campaign asking for diffusion This
hecho una campaña pidiendo difusión Esto
it is not a private thing O
no es una cosa privada O
Let's see wings. He put an example today.
sea a ver alas Ne puso hoy Un ejemplo
very good on Twitter not every day
muy bueno en Twitter no todos los días
news comes out every day
salen noticias todos los días salen
news
noticias
of of Hey then
de de Oye pues
Look, three kids have raped a girl.
mira tres chavales han violado a una
young in I don't know what
joven en no sé qué
disco
discoteca
a man from Murcia has sexually assaulted
un un murciano ha agredido sexualmente a
a lady in I don't know
una señora en no sé
where every day in every
dónde todos los días en todos los
newspapers publish this type of
periódicos salen este tipo de
news Who is the
noticias Quién es el
that is to say who
que o sea a quién
or to whom
o al que
abuse I'm really freaking out
abusa Yo es que estoy flipando de verdad
I mean, the problem with all this is
Yo es que el problema con todo esto es
that these people have the same right to
que esta gente tienen el mismo derecho a
vote than others or
voto que los demás o
I've been feeling bad for a while now.
sea estoy con un mal cuerpo desde hace
two or three
dos o tres
days Look, you annoying fly for
días Mira pues mosca cojonera por
example says that for her the worst thing is
ejemplo dice que para ella lo peor es
bring it to light, annoying fly by
sacarlo a la luz mosca cojonera por
example that looks at least says it
ejemplo que mira por lo menos lo dice
with his photo and his annoying fly face
con su foto y su cara mosca cojonera
He says it's worse to bring it to light than
dice que es peor sacarlo a la luz que
that to use in one
que usar de una
less how it is
menor cómo lo
You see he has even become a member for
veis se ha hecho hasta miembro para
say it
decirlo
Hey, annoying fly, I understand that you don't
eh mosca cojonera que entiendo que no
will have
tendrá
family says the worst thing is taking him out
familia dice que lo peor es sacarlo a la
light
luz
Yes yes I know that she is a follower of the one
Sí sí ya sé que es seguidora de la de la
Peppa can't be anyone else
Peppa no puede ser de otro
annoying fly mode says that for me it
modo mosca cojonera dice que para mí Lo
It's worse to bring this guy to light.
peor es sacarlo a la luz este tipo este
type of
tipo de
comment Well I've seen it in several
comentario Pues lo he visto en varias
occasions Well I've seen some tweets
ocasiones Bueno he visto algunos twits
that directly say all my support
que directamente dicen todo mi apoyo
Tania, a kiss for you and yours.
Tania un beso para ti y los tuyos
that the worst thing is to bring it to light well in
que lo peor es sacarlo a la luz bueno en
First of all, we haven't taken it out yet.
primer lugar es que no lo hemos sacado a
the light neither me nor anyone from Twitter nor
la luz ni ni yo ni nadie de Twitter ni
No other YouTuber has done this.
ningún otro youtuber lo esto lo ha
published and spread by Tania
publicado y lo ha difundido Tania
asking for diffusion, annoying fly
pidiendo difusión mosca cojonera
but it seems stronger to you
pero o sea a ti te parece Más Fuerte
tell a secret, that is, in the case of
contar un secreto o sea en el caso de
that it was an intimacy that one to one
que fuera una intimidad que un a una
minor for a lot of
menor durante un montón de
years I've been freaking out
años estoy flipando
man I'm freaking out but it's that it has
tío estoy flipando pero es que lo ha
posted in chat eh No it was not archived
puesto en el chat eh No no se archivó
annoying fly turned all the years of
mosca cojonera cumplió todos los años de
Moscow prison annoying fly is that to the
prisión mosc mosca cojonera es que a lo
The biggest problem you have is that you haven't
mejor problema que tiene es que no has
read the sentence no annoying fly
leído la sentencia no mosca cojonera
How it was filed
Cómo que se archivó
we filed it was fulfilled
nos archivó se cumplió la
prison very little for my taste because
prisión muy poco para mi gusto porque
for what he did to that minor very
para lo que le hizo a esa menor muy
little by little, some annoying fly comes and writes it down.
poco y viene mosca cojonera y lo escribe
here with your photo
aquí con su foto
eh I understand that it will be the no fly
eh Yo entiendo que será la no mosca
cojonera didn't spend two years in jail
cojonera no estuvo dos años a la cárcel
but but what are you saying fly
pero pero qué estás diciendo mosca
cojonera spent two years in jail and
cojonera estuvo dos años en la cárcel y
he was not convicted what are you talking about
no fue condenado qué estás hablando
annoying fly that's it
mosca cojonera eso es
lie was
mentira estuvo
eight annoying flies
ocho mosca cojonera
don't pay attention to him don't pay attention to him I
no le hagáis caso no le hagáis caso Yo
I understand that it will be people who do not have
entiendo que será personas que no tengan
remedy and
remedio y
point is already there they do not have
punto ya está no tienen
remedy has no solution did not have
remedio no tienen solución no tuvo
The solution is to imagine yourself in
solución es que imaginaros imaginaros en
In any case, imagine that this was something
todo caso imaginaros que esto fuera algo
private as they are defending a kiss
privado como están defendiendo un beso
Auri Auri, what are you getting into now?
Auri Auri a que ahora te vas poniendo
more of my side Auri as they go by
más de mi lado Auri conforme van pasando
the
las
things
cosas
God, look, I'm going to give an example, okay?
Dios mira voy a poner un ejemplo vale
Imagine if it were a
imaginaros En el caso de que sea una
intimacy that was something private to the
intimidad que fuera algo privado de la
life of the poor
vida de la pobre
Tania, imagine if it was an intimacy
Tania imaginaros que fuera una intimidad
Damn, what a bastard Javi is.
ostia Pues que cabrón el Javi que ha
told the intimacy but we would continue
contado la intimidad pero seguiríamos
condemning him of Tania or not
condenándolo de Tania o no lo
we condemn the annoying fly that is that
condenamos mosca cojonera que eso que
you're saying it's a lie fly Look
estás diciendo es mentira mosca Mira
a real annoying fly
mosca cojonera de verdad
I hope it's because you haven't read the
espero que sea porque no has leído la
sentence I hope it is because you have not
sentencia espero que sea porque no has
read the sentence annoying fly
leído la sentencia mosca cojonera
Look without going any further, annoying fly
Mira sin irte más lejos mosca cojonera
I'm not going to waste time with you.
es que no voy a perder tiempo contigo
Look, there are screenshots of it.
Mira es que es que hay capturas de su
page of her blog that she talks about
página de su blog la que ella habla de
It's been a pain in the ass for 4 years, no matter what.
lleva 4 años mosca cojonera da igual lo
that you want annoying fly and but
que tú quieras mosca cojonera e pero
annoying fly
mosca cojonera
keep banning banning dude because you're into me
sigue banear banear tío que a mí estas
Things turn me on. It's that these things turn me on.
cosas me ponen Es que a mí estas cosas
They make me feel sick, annoying flies
me ponen malo moscas cojonera
Look this is Paul talking about the
Mira esto es Pablo hablando de la
judgment
sentencia
Okay, I'm reading one, look at what you
vale Estoy leyendo una mira lo que tú
you defend, annoying fly, what you are
defiendes mosca cojonera lo que tú estás
defending annoying fly
defendiendo mosca cojonera
I am reading a sentence that they give me
Estoy leyendo una sentencia que me dan
an abusive stepfather wants to vomit
ganas de vomitar un padrastro que abusa
of his 11-year-old stepdaughter since the
de su hijastra de los 11 años desde los
years old, her partner, mother of the girl
años su pareja madre de la niña
tatal impregnates her twice and makes her
tatal la embaraza dos veces y la hace
aborting hits you hard
abortar le pega una
I can't take it anymore, man, really.
paliza no puedo más tío de verdad
Beltrn eh
Beltrán eh
I can't take it anymore, I can't take it anymore, I can't take it anymore
no puedo más no puedo más no puedo más
Uncle, who appears here to say that
tío Que aparezca por aquí a decir eso
man, but there are people, there are a lot of them
tío pero es que hay gente hay mucha
people like annoying flies like that eh Hey what
gente como mosca cojonera así eh Oye que
It is a topic
es un tema
private Hey it's a private topic How
privado Oye que es un tema privado Cómo
You are going to attack him with a private topic OR
Vais a atacarle con un tema privado O
be that this lady has been here for two [ __ ] years
sea que esta señora lleva dos [__] años
with a Sentence
con una Sentencia
Having said some insults to a man
De haberle dicho a un señor unos insulto
and a lady with a broom and I don't know
y a una señora pelo escoba y no sé
what But this
qué Pero esto
not a kiss Tania all my support to you and
no un beso Tania todo mi apoyo a ti y a
yours
los tuyos
nor is it a private issue because it is an issue
ni es un tema privado porque es un tema
that she spreads is a topic that she
que ella difunde es un tema que ella
makes it public nor is it a topic
hace hace público ni es un tema
private nor is it using a relative to
privado ni es usar un familiar para
attack
atacar a
Tania, you may have a relative.
Tania tú puedes tener un familiar
Imagine a father, a brother, a cousin
imagínate un padre un hermano un primo
that commits a crime, imagine a
que Cometa un delito imagínate un
murderer Imagine you have a relative
asesino Imagínate que tienes un familiar
which is a
que es un
killer okay Imagine your father is
asesino vale Imagínate que tu padre es
a
un
rapist okay imagine your father is a
violador vale imagínate tu padre es un
rapist me personally in my case
violador yo personalmente en mi caso
lisardo a kiss Thank you very much uncle yo
lisardo un beso Muchas gracias tío yo
Personally in my case for me my
personalmente en mi caso para mí mi
father would be dead if my father had
padre estaría muerto si mi padre hubiera
done that or my father, a brother, an uncle
hecho eso o mi padre un hermano un tío
For me personally, he would be dead.
para mí personalmente estaría muerto
but I am not to blame for what has happened
pero yo no tengo culpa de lo que haya
made him You do not choose the
hecho él Tú no eliges a la
family you understand me There are a lot of
familia me entiendes Hay un montón de
famous people who have a family member who has
famosos que tienen un familiar que han
done I don't know what I don't know how much but of course
hecho no sé qué no sé cuánto pero claro
you are not to blame for what your your your has
tú no tienes culpa de lo que ha tu tu tu
family The problem is that this aunt
familiar El problema es que esta tía a
I knew this man from two
este hombre lo conocía de dos
days he met him in the in the in the middle of the
días lo conoció en el en el en mitad del
procedure in which first
procedimiento en el que primero se
filed and then
archivó y luego se
reopened and defended it to an uncle who
reabrió y lo defendió a un tío que
knew him for two days and defended him and
conocía de dos días y lo defendió y
I wanted to make him pass for
quería hacerlo pasar por por
innocent No, it's not even something
inocente No no es ni algo
private is neither something private nor is it
privado ni es algo privado ni es
use a
utilizar a un
family we can all have the bad
familiar todos podemos tener la mala
fortunate to have a relative who has
fortuna de tener un familiar que haya
done something and it's not your fault Of course
hecho algo y tú no tienes la culpa Claro
It's not your fault But you're not
está Tú no tienes la culpa Pero tú no
you choose your family of course you don't choose
eliges a tu familia claro tú no eliges a
your family
tu familia
but the problem is that this lady
pero el problema es que esta señora
meet this man with that and
conoce a este hombre con eso y lo
defends a two-day-old guy who
defiende a un tío de dos días que
I knew him for two days at that time and
conocía de dos días en ese momento y lo
defends him and goes with him and fights for him and
defiende y se va con él y lucha por él y
is with
está con
What are you really telling me?
él qué me estáis contando de verdad si
It's that I can't
es que yo no puedo
Hey, what are you doing to me?
eh qué me estáis
counting I think if a peseta gave each
contando pienso si una peseta diera cada
Spanish but not me where they have to
español pero no a mí a donde tienen que
I should thank you for the tact you have
debería agradecerte El tacto que has
had from minute one to try
tenido desde el minuto uno para tratar
This news would have been the opposite
esta noticia al contrario hubiera sido
devastating you are a good person oliveira
devastador eres buena persona oliveira
man if it had been something of mine
hombre si hubiera sido alguna cosa mía
Even if it had been private forward
Aunque hubiera sido privada palante se
He deserves it because he pisses off
lo merece porque le toca las narices a
this one and the other one and they would be supporting it and
este y al otro y lo estarían apoyando y
challenging all the
retando todos los
Besides, this is tremendous, apart from that, I don't
demás es tremendo esto aparte yo no
I am mentioning at no time no
estoy mencionando en ningún momento no
I have not put any data
he puesto ningún dato
The anonymous person I'm talking about
de la persona anónima estoy hablando de
so remember when you said that this
tan Recuerdas cuando dijiste que esta
people would be able to defend Jos
gente sería capaz de defender a José
Breton to go against you Javi
bretón con tal de ir en tu contra Javi
Well, for example, a button. Well, that's it.
bueno para muestra un botón Bueno ya lo
we saw two or three days ago also with
vimos hace dos o TR días también con
Daniel Sancho who were rejoicing
Daniel Sancho que se estaban alegrando
that Daniel Sancho left me for a
de que Daniel Sancho me fuera por una
demand that in the end is not
demanda que al final no es a
m
m
I'm going to be tremendous, I swear to you.
voy que es tremendo te lo juro que
talking to wings the other day I was thinking
hablando con alas el otro día Yo pensaba
that with this topic
que con este tema
No, I thought that with this topic
no Yo pensaba que con este tema
No, I say with this topic, not in this topic.
no yo digo con este tema no en este tema
they are not going to put on
no se van a poner
a in this topic they are not going to put
a en este tema no se van a poner a
justify turning it around I don't know what
justificarle a darle la vuelta no sé qué
I don't know how much and I find that
a no sé cuánto y me encuentro con que
yes and I find that yes, that is
sí y me encuentro con que sí O sea
amazing uncle flip what have I done to you What have you
flipante tío flip qué os he hecho Qué ha
made by Javi Oliveira or so but of course
hecho Javi oliveira o sea pero claro
because what I would do
porque yo lo que haría
It would be in any case not to pronounce myself if not
sería en todo caso no pronunciarme si no
I want to speak out on the subject but leave
quiero pronunciarme del tema pero salir
to show support
a mostrarle el apoyo
Uncle, I can't believe it today.
tío Es que yo hoy no doy crédito te lo
I swear I thought that the 240 or the
juro pensaba que lo de los 240 o lo del
invented LOL cancer would be like the
cáncer de LOL inventado sería como el
top of the
tope no de la
support something you know but but this
apoyar una cosa que sabes pero pero esto
what the [ __ ], all my support
qué [__] como que todo mi apoyo
Tania says sisuka I sincerely believed
Tania dice sisuka yo sinceramente creía
that they were going to put themselves in profile but
que se iban a poner de perfil pero
Man I didn't even expect that
hombre Yo no esperaba ni siquiera que
These are the accounts of the stalkers of the
las cuentas estas de los acosadores del
Wilson and others but no no no
Wilson y demás pero no no no
justifying is not that it is a topic
justificando no es que es un tema
private is that it is the disgusting intimacy
privado es que es la intimidad asco
but not to me where they have to and here and
pero no a mí a donde tienen que y aquí y
This is the one that raises the finger at you
esta es la que levanta el dedo contra ti
Yes, this is it because I told him broom hair
sí esta esta porque le dije pelo escoba
to a youtuber and insulted another one who
a una youtuber y insulté a otro que me
he is insulting me
está insultando a mí
first you know when it was a topic
primero sabéis cuándo era un tema
private it of
privado lo de
Tania, do you know when it was a private matter?
Tania sabéis cuándo era un tema privado
the thing about
lo de
Tania which was private because nobody knew
Tania cuá era privado porque nadie se
I had realized that I had made it public
había dado cuenta que lo tenía público
on her networks when Loli threatened her
en sus redes cuando Loli la amenazó
When Loli threatened her I'm going to take this out
cuando Loli la amenazó voy a sacar esto
from your husband when Loli threatened her there
de tu marido cuando Loli la amenazó ahí
Yes, it was a private matter because it was not
sí era un tema privado porque no
We knew he was in public in his
sabíamos que estaba en público en sus
networks and in Chain campaigns now
redes y en las campañas de Chain ahora
people have found it because it has so much
la gente lo ha encontrado Porque tan ha
given a clue so that
dado pista para que lo
find but when Lolly threatened her
encuentren pero cuando Lolly la amenazó
By telling it now it has come out without
con contarlo ahora ha salido sin
threats eh Now he has been found
amenazas eh Ahora se lo ha encontrado la
people and that's it but Loli threatened her with
gente y punto pero Loli la amenazó con
tell it there where they were where they were
contarlo ahí dónde estaban dónde estaban
all those who say it is a topic
todos los que dicen que es un tema
private that should not be
privado que no se debe
find out where the outraged people were
sacar dónde estaban los indignados por
the topic
el tema
private when Loli threatened her with
privado cuando Loli la amenazó con
take it out there nobody said anything about it is
sacarlo ahí nadie dijo nada de [__] es
that is private is threatening her with a
que es privado esta amenazándola con un
topic nobody said
tema nadie dijo
nothing, this that you are seeing on the screen
nada esto que estáis viendo en pantalla
direct from ard
directo de ard
Troy I have seen people from the community
Troya he visto a gente de la comunidad
The ard of Troy is good, the ard of Troy itself is
ard de Troya bueno está el propio ard de
Troy challenging things in favor of Tania that
Troya retando cosas a favor de Tania que
Tania's privacy the audio that
la privacidad de Tania el audio que
Everyone was waiting for the relative to speak
todos esperaban habla el familiar que
They are looking for this is the Troy ard that
tanto buscan Este es ard de Troya que
with Tania Mira direct from Tania
junto a Tania Mira directo de Tania
They went to look for Loli's sister
se fueron a buscar a la hermana de Loli
garden to extract information from him that
huerta para sacarle información de que
If Loli had cancer she didn't have it or she had it
si Loli tenía cáncer no lo tenía o lo
that it be and they published the audios with the
que sea y publicaron los audios con la
Loli's sister with the name of the
hermana de Loli con el nombre de la
Loli's sister with the face of the
hermana de Loli con la cara de la
Loli's sister and with intimacies of
hermana de Loli y con intimidades de
Loli where were all of them?
Loli dónde estaban todos los de o sea
Those of you who are outraged today that
los que hoy estáis indignados con que
it would be necessary
habría que
to keep quiet about sexual abuse
callarse un abuso sexual a una
minor where they were here here they did not
menor dónde estaban aquí aquí no les
This seemed to be to tell Loli Loli a
parecía esto para decirle a Loli Loli un
kiss here no one said anything about it
beso aquí ninguno dijo nada de la
privacy of the subject privacy nor when
privacidad del tema privacidad ni cuando
Loli threatened Tania with taking it out, which was
Loli amenazó a Tania con sacarlo que fue
the first one who threatened to take it out
la primera que amenazó con sacarlo ni
when Tania and Troy burned they went to
cuando Tania y arde Troya se fueron a
to get intimate details out of Loli's sister
sacarle intimidades a la hermana de Loli
What's more, do you know what they did here?
es más sabéis que hicieron Aquí estos
two characters who are very today
dos personajes que hoy están muy
outraged with the
indignados con las
privacy of all audios that
privacidades de todos los audios que
they had from the sister of
tenían de la hermana de
Loli published All except those in which
Loli publicaron Todos menos en los que
Loli's sister was talking about Loli
la hermana de Loli hablaba de que Loli
cancer had been invented, it's worth looking at
se había inventado el cáncer vale mirar
what is this
esto qué está
giving
dando
Lois Hello sister and already at the time we
lois Hola hermana y ya en su momento nos
He said what the flight was saying
dijo que lo que el vuelo estaba diciendo
It was true that the one who had cancer is the one
era verdad la que ha tenido cáncer es la
Nocio's sister, she and I have been
hermana de nocio ella y yo he estado
covering it up for this time
tapándolo este tiempo por
you don't hear it
no lo oís
by the sister and already at the time we
por la hermana y ya en su momento nos
He said what the flight was saying
dijo que lo que el vuelo estaba diciendo
It was true that the one who had cancer is the one
era verdad la que ha tenido cáncer es la
LOL's sister hasn't been her and I have
hermana de LOL no sido ella y yo he
been covering it up for a while because I don't
estado tapándolo este tiempo por no
discover it and that
descubrirla y que la
destroy and you are already seeing the payment that
destrocen y ya está viendo el pago que
this
está
giving talk to the sister and taking out the
dando hablar con la hermana y sacar lo
audio to cover up the
audio para taparle la
mouth to Jordi to
boca al Jordi al
grandfather
abuelo
Come on, says Alicia Jai, you love me.
vamos dice Alicia Jai tú me quieres
saying that Troy is justifying
decir que de Troya está justificando
This outrageous thing by Tania. Look at the profile.
esta barbaridad de Tania Mira el perfil
from that of Troy
de al de Troya
today Look at the profile of al de Troya today
hoy Mira el perfil de al de Troya hoy
Look, the first thing that ard has done
Mira Bueno lo primero que ha hecho ard
of Troy in Loli's live show has been
de Troya en el directo de Loli ha sido
I have very clear and in what
poner tengo muy claro y en lo que
I know Tania that she is not going to
conozco a Tania que ella no va a
defend an abuser, and even less so if there is
defender a un abusador Y menos si hay
minors involved
menores de por medio
all my support to Tania and whoever has
todo mi apoyo a Tania y el que tenga
accounts that the
cuentas que las
pay Look what he said about Troy in the
pague Mirad lo que decía de Troya en el
yesterday not the day before yesterday Look at it
día de ayer no antes de ayer Mirad lo
what I was saying about Troy the day before yesterday
que decía de Troya antes de ayer
reacting to this tweet of mine to
reaccionando a este twit mío para
defend himself that he does not defend the
defenderse de que él no defiende al
Carlota Prado's abuser Look what
abusador de Carlota Prado Mirad lo que
He said abusers are a mental disorder
decía abusadores es un trastorno mental
In most cases the issue of
en la mayoría de los casos el tema de
rapists and abusers is a disorder
violadores y abusadores es un trastorno
mental in most cases is a
mental en la mayoría de los casos es un
mental disorder and they are aware
trastorno mental y ellos son conscientes
that they are not cured that they are going to
de que no se curan de que van a
reoffend sooner or later then
reincidir antes o después entonces
many of
muchos de
They prefer not to go out on the street
ellos prefieren no salir a la calle
before hurting someone but it is
antes de hacerle daño a alguien pero es
that we say is like an impulse that
que digamos que es como un impulso que
noed
noed
control but they still release it because
controlar pero aún así lo sueltan porque
has behaved well for whatever reason
se ha porta bien por lo que sea por las
conditions that are because the law has made it so
condiciones que sea porque la ley lo han
released and they have relapsed into their own thing
soltado y han vuelto a reincidir lo suyo
It would mean putting him in life imprisonment but
sería meterlo en cadena perpetua pero
Here too there is no such formula, that is to say
aquí tampoco existe esa fórmula es decir
that here in Spain we are unprotected
que aquí en España estamos desprotegidos
even the prisoners themselves are
incluso los propios reos están
unprotected Because if they
desprotegidos Porque si a ellos le
I would rather live my whole life in
encantaría mejor vivir toda la vida en
prison and not harm the one who is
la cárcel y no hacer daño Al que está
out because they see themselves incapable of
fuera porque se ven incapaces de
control yourself but
controlarse pero
In Spain we have not reached that point
en España no Hemos llegado a ese punto
still
todavía
then no to the transgression of the
entonces no a la transgresión a las
laws of any kind whatsoever
leyes de ningún tipo de ningún
type this piece of scoundrel who
tipo este pedazo de Sinvergüenza que
uses the no is no and says that it is
utiliza el no es no y que dice que se
feels harassed by Peppa
sienta acosado por Peppa
Beltrn I hope that in his life he doesn't have
Beltrán Espero que en su vida no tenga
I hope you go through that in your life
que pasar por eso espero que en su vida
nor anyone
ni nadie
from your environment has to go through that
de su entorno tenga que pasar por eso
because the law of no is no is no
porque la ley del no es no no es una
nonsense is not worth posting on Twitter
tontería no es para colgar un Twitter un
video that is applied to him that is not for
vídeo que se se aplica él que no es para
he and had nothing to do with what he is
él y no tenía nada que ver lo que es el
message that Peppa wanted to say in that
mensaje que Peppa quiso decir en ese en
that live with what he has wanted
ese directo con lo que él se ha querido
apply or it is embarrassing but not
aplicar o sea e vergonzoso pero que no
never have to use that law so much
tengan que utilizar nunca esa ley tanto
for as against because there are many
a favor como en contra porque hay muchos
There are many cases, there are many cases.
casos hay much hay muchos casos hay
many teenagers
muchos adolescentes
there are many couples, there are many people
hay muchas parejas hay muchas personas
who do not dare to report because they
que no se atreven a denunciar porque se
He thinks that they will not pay much attention to him
piensa que no le van a hacer caso tanto
men as women and there are cases that
hombres como mujeres y hay casos que
just for touching someone's ass
simplemente por tocarle el culo a una
girl have
chica tienen
[Music]
[Música]
grief
pena
Ah, so this is the woman from the coceno
Ah o sea esta es la mujer del coceno
I come not because this is the channel of the
vengo no porque este es el canal del
I'm coming here. Okay, so look what I'm doing.
coceno vengo Vale pues Mirad lo que
I was putting the SEO silo I come today
estaba poniendo el el silo seo vengo hoy
Tania is not in Loli's chat
en el chat de Loli Tania no está
sola stop garbage channels
sola stop canales basura
These are not dudes, they are not worth it
esto son no tío es que no valen para
nothing what they say is not worth what they do not no
nada lo que digan no valen lo que no no
They do not have a coherent criterion
no tienen una coherencia un criterio no
no no no no it depends on the hate where
no no no no es depende del odio donde
I took them and we are ready to defend this.
les lleve ya está peramos defender esto
Uncle Tania is not here
tío Tania no está
I ask myself a few questions after
sola me hago unas preguntas después de
see one of the most nauseating cynicisms
ver uno de los cinismos más vomitivos
that I have seen in the time I have been here
que he visto en el tiempo que llevo aquí
if the case sentence had been counted
si el caso sentencia se hubiese contado
in a newscast that has been told in a
en un telediario que se ha contado en un
newscast
telediario
but not to me where they have to in what
pero no a mí a donde tienen que en que
sewer in contrast is kiss
alcantarilla en contraste est beso
Gerardo or the news program of
Gerardo o programa de sucesos de
television that could have happened
televisión que podría haber sucedido
Perfectly Yes yes there is news eh
perfectamente Sí sí hay noticias eh
We have news of this case, that is, this one
tenemos noticias de este caso o sea este
If the news came out, eh, someone
caso salieron las noticias eh alguien
I would be stoning the presenter for
estaría lapidando al presentador por
Telling it someone would be ignoring that in
contarlo alguien estaría obviando que en
the facts proven in the sentences
los hechos probados de las sentencias
authentic accounts
cuentan auténticas
atrocities someone would be using the
atrocidades alguien estaría usando el
cheap moralism that is
moralismo barato de que se está
invading the privacy of the convicted person
invadiendo la privacidad del condenado
someone would be supporting the couple and
alguien estaría apoyando a la pareja y
defender of this subject are questions
defensora de este sujeto son preguntas
is that they are supporting the couple uncle and
es que están apoyando a la pareja tío y
defender
defensora
and to all my love and my
y a todo mi cariño y mi
support and she has released a statement
apoyo y ella ha sacado un comunicado
Today she released a statement
hoy ella ha sacado un comunicado
official announcement of actions today
hoy comunicado oficial de acciones
legal I love the official statement
legales me encanta el comunicado oficial
you know like she's uh a company
sabes como si ella fuera eh una empresa
or something like that is absolutely not
o algo por el estilo no es absolutamente
unacceptable that on the part of certain
inaceptable que por parte de ciertos
individuals On platforms such as YouTube and
individuos En plataformas como YouTube y
Twitter has started a campaign of
Twitter se hayan iniciado una campaña de
dissemination of private information
difusión de información Privada de una
third person
tercera persona
anonymous No information available
anónima No hay ninguna información
Deprived of any anonymous person to the
Privada de ninguna persona anónima a la
An anonymous person is not even being told
persona anónima ni siquiera se le está
mentioning okay eh And the information is
mencionando vale eh Y la información es
a campaign that Tania made a kiss Yes
una campaña que hizo Tania un beso Yes
Furthermore, Tania gave every luxury of details
además Tania dio todo lujo de detalles
so that people could find the
para que la gente encontrase la
sentence I think he put the number of
sentencia creo que puso el número de
He also sentences the name of the
Sentencia también el nombre del
magistrate
magistrado
worth it for the sole purpose of trying
vale con el único propósito intentar
silencing me would damage my reputation and
silenciarme dañar mi reputación y
harass me
acosarme
This behavior is not only immoral
este comportamiento es no solo inmoral
immoral but it is also illegal and not
inmoral sino que también es ilegal y no
I'm going to allow you to continue, I'll leave it at
voy a permitir que continúe dejo en
clear the following diffusion of
claro lo siguiente difusión de
information without consent this is
información sin consentimiento esto es
a direct violation of my rights to
una violación directa de mis derechos a
privacy and intimacy and each of
la privacidad e intimidad y cada una de
These people will be reported
estas personas será denunciada
legally denounced man
legalmente hombre denunciada legalmente
why illegally denounce the truth
porque denunciar ilegalmente la verdad
It's just that it's a bit bad
es que está un poco está un poco regulín
I don't know if that exists, I won't allow it.
no sé yo si eso existe no permitiré que
my private life or that of third parties is not used
se use mi vida privada ni la de terceros
like a gun for a gun
como un arma para un arma un
Total weapon that says that send that
arma Total que dice que mandar que
wants to report cyberbullying
quiere denunciar por acoso cibernético
They won't silence me, they will all be
no me van a callar todos serán
identified and that is to say that he is going to report
identificados y O sea que va a denunciar
to everyone who is posting this
a todo el mundo que esté poniendo esto
He's not going to report anyone, okay?
no va a denunciar a nadie vale o sea
This is when you remember when you avoid
esto es cuando os acordáis cuando evita
Dynamite told the lie that he was going to
Dinamita dijo la mentira que iba a
denounced Marta Riesco and it was a lie
denunciar a Marta riesco y fue mentira
I told you from the first day
que os lo dije desde el primer día os
I said I'm not going to report anything because in the
dije no va a denunciar nada porque en el
judged what Marta is going to put on Mira
juzgado lo que le va poner Marta es Mira
what you told me
lo que me has dicho
you be you Imagine that a person arrives
tú sea tú Imagínate que llega una
complaint of a potato that has made a
denuncia de una papa que ha hecho una
campaign to spread these
campaña para difundir estos
facts that she has asked to be disseminated
hechos que ha pedido difusión ella a
these facts and has given the names
estos hechos y que ha dado los nombres
even from the judges so that people
hasta de los jueces para que la gente
find the sentence worth And also
encuentre la sentencia vale Y además
she is dedicated to pointing the finger
ella se dedica a señalar con el dedo
inquisitor to everyone and that you
inquisidor a todo el mundo y que te
comes to report why you are
viene a denunciar porque lo estás
commenting and it seems to you
comentando y te parece
disgusting here he has answered
asqueroso aquí le ha contestado
Pablo, well, I'll tell you several things about
Pablo pues te cuento varias cosas sobre
This is one of the official announcements
esto uno lo de lo de comunicado oficial
It makes me laugh, officer, what are you?
me hace hasta gracia oficial de qué eres
a company It's like I communicate
una empresa Es como si yo comunico
officially that I go to the bathroom an mms of
oficialmente que voy al baño una mms de
someone who wants to speak in difficult and
alguien que quiere hablar en difícil y
don't know There is no information
no sabe No hay ninguna información
private from the moment she
privada desde el momento en el que ella
He disseminated all this information
le dio difusión a toda esta información
on chain.org can't go against its
en chain.org no puede ir contra sus
own actions good not only in
propios actos bueno no solamente en
chain.org eh on their Facebook page and
chain.org eh en su página de Facebook y
in a lot of places it's okay or it's not okay
en un montón de sitios vale e no va
Report anything, Russell is not going to report anything
denunciar nada russel no va a denunciar
nothing and you can talk about this
nada y podéis hablar de esto
calmly, evidently with respect
tranquilamente evidentemente con respeto
and do not put any names or data
y no pongáis ni los nombres ni los datos
of any person who is not public
de ninguna persona que no sea pública
Okay, but of course you can.
vale sin más pero claro que se puede
commenting on this is a campaign that she
comentar esto es una campaña que ella
did not to me have to if instead of
hizo no a m a tienen que si en vez de
If you were you, I wouldn't tell you your face.
tanta fueras tú no te cuento cara
vomiting if instead of me it were me
vomitando si en vez de tan fuera yo
man but it's not that it's that
hombre pero es que no es eso es que
They were saying that this opens the way to
estaban diciendo que esto abre la veda a
that they can investigate my family or
que puedan investigar a mi familia o a
alanne's family and it's like clear
la familia de alanne y es como claro
shoot to see what happens shoot to see
tira a ver qué es lo que pasa tira a ver
man the first thing is that you are not going to
hombre lo primero es que no Vais a
find an abuser
encontrar una abusa
minors but pull pull to see what it is
menores pero tira tira a ver qué es lo
What happens? Well, basically, if you take out
que pasa Pues básicamente que si sacas
something private we are going to report you and it
algo privado te vamos a denunciar y se
your hair is going to fall out you know and you feel one
te va a caer el pelo sabes y siones una
photo of someone Look at the Dallas lo
foto de alguien Mira el Dallas lo
condemned
condenaron
In Dallas he was sentenced
en el Dallas lo condenaron
ao no a a tien that they know it
ao no a a tien que ellos lo saben la
privacy is relative to that of others
privacidad es relativa la de los demás
It is public if it affects me, not if I
es pública si me afecta a mí no si me
It really bothers you, of course, if you're taking one out
mol molesta claro si estás sacando una
information that bothers me but of course it is
información que me molesta pero claro es
that no one is taking out a lizard kiss
que nadie Está sacando un beso lizardo
Nobody is taking information out of
nadie Está sacando una información de
This turkey has many things about this turkey
esta pava hay muchas cosas de esta pava
eh There are many things and they are not being
eh Hay muchas cosas y no se están
taking out that I think they will come out because
sacando que yo creo que saldrán porque
doesn't stop doesn't stop doesn't stop Searching for
no para no para no para de Buscar de
pointing out others for taking things from you
señalar a los demás de sacarle cosas a
the other aunt having that or so you
los demás tía teniendo eso o sea que tú
You have the right to be with a
estás en tu derecho de estar con un
aggressor, okay, you are within your rights
agresor vale que tú estás en tu derecho
You will know your problem is but of course not
tú sabrás tu problema es pero claro no
have Don't create a YouTube channel of
tenga No te creas un canal de YouTube de
get into taking the [ __ ] out of the
meterte de sacarle las [__] a los
where were all the indignant ones?
demás dónde estaban todos los indignados
with privacy when Loli threatened to
con la privacidad cuando Loli amenazó a
Tania with taking this out when Tania left
Tania con sacar esto cuando Tania se fue
to Loli Huerta's family and began
a por la familia de Loli Huerta y empezó
to take out audios when Tania made a
a sacar audios cuando Tania hizo un
straight in pajamas at night
directo en pijama por la noche
threatening Ine and Elena that he was going to
amenazando a a lne y a Elena de que iba
to take out all the [ __ ] I found
a sacar toda la [__] que encontrase de
where the indignant ones were with them
ellas dónde estaban los indignados con
privacy dude what are you really
la privacidad tío De verdad qué estáis
defending what the [ __ ] are you defending
defendiendo qué [__] estáis defendiendo
Have you even stopped to think?
os habéis parado a pensar ni siquiera
that you are defending, Uncle Ins,
que estáis defendiendo tío Inés un
kiss that each person will be reported
beso que cada persona será denunciada
legally Well yes because to report
legalmente Pues sí porque denunciar
illegally it looks ugly, let's continue
ilegalmente queda feo vamos que sigue
trying to speak in difficult and not
intentando hablar en difícil y no le
defamation and damage to reputation come out
sale difamación y daño a la reputación
Call me crazy but I think what he does
Llámame loco pero creo que lo que hace
damage to a person's reputation is
daño a la reputación de una persona es
that she be condemned for
que la condenen por
penetrate a girl
penetrar a una niña
not that anyone tells it but it is not
no que alguien lo cuente pero es que no
It's not even that someone tells it that
es ni siquiera que alguien lo cuente que
even if someone told it being real
aunque lo contase alguien siendo real
I have my doubt that something will happen, okay?
Tengo mi duda de que pasara algo vale si
You don't say the name and you don't identify
tú no dices el nombre y no identificas a
the anonymous person you understand me but
la persona anónima me entiendes pero
Of course, if you say Tania has a partner
claro si tú dices Tania tiene una pareja
who has done this and Punishment condemned
que ha hecho esto y Castigo condenada
for freedom a kiss
por libertad un beso
welcome that is a is a
bienvenida que es una es una
reality by the way how is that that
realidad por cierto cómo es eso de que
The publications will be supported by
las publicaciones serán respaldadas por
a lawsuit is underway for defamation, let's go
una demanda anda por difamación vamos
that you support the publications of
que tú respaldas las publicaciones de
These people, well, everyone agrees.
esta gente Pues todos de acuerdo
So it doesn't say they will be identified and
Entonces no dice serán identificado y
judge by law again you try
juzgad por la ley otra vez intentas
speak in a difficult way and you can't do it will be
hablar en difícil y no te sale serán
judged by a court But not by
juzgado por un tribunal Pero no por
no law or will be judged according to
ninguna ley o serán juzgado de acuerdo a
the law makes a fool of my lawyers and
la ley haces el ridículo mis abogados y
I from experience When someone speaks
yo por experiencia Cuando alguien habla
of my lawyers usually only have
de mis abogados habitualmente solo tiene
one and he doesn't pay Tania it's your decision
uno y no le paga Tania es tu decisión
Being with a rapist is up to you. But
estar con un violador es cosa tuya Pero
accept it and don't hurt yourself anymore
acepta un y no te hag más daño a ti
The more you bring it out into the open the more
misma Cuanto más lo sacas a la luz más
people find out clearly This is a
gente se entera claro Es que esto es un
a topic that was perhaps buried deep inside
tema que a lo mejor estaba enterrad simo
This is a topic that perhaps was
esto es un tema que a lo mejor estaba
bury simo and that person is there
enterrad simo y y esa persona pues está
living I don't know working or will be you know
viviendo no sé trabajando o estará sabes
what I'm telling you but it's his wife who
lo que te digo pero es su mujer la que
is taking this out, it is his wife who does not
está sacando esto es su mujer la que no
for
para
What Jorge, I'm not understanding you about
de el qué jorgo no te estoy entendiendo
the question
la pregunta
Anica, the brutal sentence, that is, the
Anica lo de la sentencia brutal O sea la
I was reading the sentence yesterday and
sentencia yo la estuve leyendo ayer y
I was even trembling
estaba hasta temblando
reading it tremendous
leyéndola tremendo
tremendous
tremendo
tremendous to see then that you get involved
tremendo a ver entonces que tú te metas
with someone's physical appearance is
con el aspecto físico de alguien está
Well, a kiss, Miss, but if I say that
bien Un beso Miss Pero si yo digo que
You are like the earth flattened by the
eres como la tierra achatada por los
Poles that is unforgivable Javi
polos eso es imperdonable que Javi
losing a civil lawsuit is very serious
pierda una demanda civil es gravísimo
but that you live with a pedophile is
pero que tú vivas con un pederasta es
normal I don't know if they are more pitiful or disgusting
normal No sé si dan más pena o asco
Pablo Pablo What a pleasure, eh Pablo, you have
Pablo Pablo Que gusto eh Pablo le ha
given well eh man
dado bien eh hombre
Uncle, how are you?
tío cómo vas
How are you going to defend this, man? And it is that
A cómo va a defender esto tío Y es que
That's what I'm telling you, man. One thing
es lo que os estoy diciendo tío una cosa
It's one thing for you to have a brother
es una cosa es que tú tengas un hermano
Imagine a brother, a father, that you
imagínate un hermano un padre que tú
you have a brother who has done this to you
tengas un hermano que haya hecho esto tú
You don't choose your family You don't have
no eliges a tu familia Tú no tienes
blame for what your family has done
culpa de lo que tu familia haya haga
have made or have such a person in
haga hecho o de tener una persona así en
the family But this is not a person
la familia Pero esto no es una persona
that she has not chosen this is a
que ella no ha elegido esto es una
person she meets in the middle of The
persona que ella conoce en mitad de El
the first one I think was first filed no
el primer creo que primero se archivó no
I know why because he first entered
sé el Por qué Porque primero entró en
A provisional one is that she gave all
una provisional es que ella dio todos
the data all that people have
los datos todo eso la gente ha
found the sentence because she in
encontrado la sentencia porque ella en
Blogs tell it all.
los blogs eso lo cuenta todo lo cuenta
everything that was first in a
todo que primero estuvo en un
provisional for I don't know how many months
provisional durante no sé cuántos meses
which was then archived and then re-archived
que luego se archivó y luego se volvió a
reopen because something happened and the
reabrir porque pasó una cosa y la
generality opened it I am not going to
generalidad lo abrió Yo es que no voy a
go into detail, I really tell you and
entrar en detalle de verdad os lo digo y
Besides, it's very unpleasant and look at this
aparte es muy desagradable y mira esto
that's it
ya está
Look, look, Gabi Oliveira, I have a lot.
mira mira Gabi oliveira tengo mucha
[ __ ] prepared to get you out of al
[__] preparada para sacar de ti de al
Ortega's are looking for me. Don't you
de Ortega me lo están buscando No te
Don't worry about Elena de Ortega, they are worrying me.
preocupes de Elena de Ortega me lo están
looking for you I think it's been like you were
buscando te creo que hace como estuviste
I don't know if they told me about two years without
no sé si me han dicho unos dos años sin
talk to her I don't know something they have told me
hablarte con ella No sé algo me han
having said that
dicho de eso
Hey, I have a lot of [ __ ] to get out of you.
eh tengo mucha [__] para sacarte
Okay, this is really a pain, huh?
vale manda huevos esto eh
family is a real pain, this is family.
familia manda huevos esto eh familia
This was after Loli had finished her
Esto fue después de que Loli htas la
threatened to release this that we know
amenazara con sacar esto que sabemos a
day of
día de
Today, look, Gabi Oliveira, I have a lot of
hoy Mira Gabi oliveira tengo mucha
[ __ ] prepared to get out of you
[__] preparada para sacar de ti de
Alande de Ortega is looking for me.
alande de Ortega me lo están buscando No
Don't worry about Elena de Ortega, I'll tell you
te preocupes de Elena de Ortega me lo
They are looking and I think it does as
están buscando y creo que hace como
you were, I don't know if they told me about two
estuviste no sé si me han dicho unos dos
years without talking to her, it's not something I
años sin hablarte con ella no algo me
they have said about that
han dicho de eso
Hey, I have a lot of [ __ ] to get out of you.
eh tengo mucha [__] para sacarte
Okay, having that, how do you get like that?
vale teniendo eso cómo te pones así con
the people
la gente
Man, I'm freaking out, how disgusting all this is.
tío estoy flipando qué asco da todo esto
tremendous what they are defending look
tremendo lo que están defendiendo mira
Here you have for example one Wait I'm going
aquí tienes por ejemplo una Espera voy
Listen first to what Carmen has said
Escuchar primero lo que ha dicho Carmen
I really don't know if you disgust me or not.
verd que no sé si me das entre asco y
shame I'm a little bit between those
vergüenza Estoy entre un poco entre esas
two things between disgust and shame
dos cosas entre el asco y la vergüenza
because you are really pathetic
porque eres patética de verdad que eres
pathetic and now I understand how you are so
patética y ahora entiendo cómo eres tan
unhappy and the frustration you have
infeliz y la frustración que tienes
above To have turned to hatred
encima Para haberte volcado en el odio
that you have for Javi and stop living and
que le tienes a Javi y dejar de vivir y
stop living a normal life overturned
dejar de hacer una vida normal volcada
in the hatred you have for Javi but
en el odio que le tienes a Javi pero
Of course I understood last night I understood
claro he entendido anoche entendí
I understood many things, I understood
muchísimas cosas lo entendí lo entendí
I understood many things. Yes, I was.
entendí muchas cosas Eh sí es que estaba
it was just as it had been
estaba tal y como ya había que estaba
the ones that were already there I mean there were already quite a few
las que ya había O sea ya había bastante
people who po It's that I say I stay there
gente que po Es que yo digo me quedo ahí
I remain a bit of a listener in
un poco de oyente me quedo de oyente en
the end the worst of the worst unforgivable is
fin lo peor de lo peor imperdonable es
that is unforgivable It is that justifying
que es imperdonable Es que justificar
That justifies a crime against a minor
eso justificar un delito hacia una menor
That's the worst part, since it's already lower.
eso es lo peor ya que ya más bajo ya es
impossible lower is impossible but
imposible más bajo es imposible pero
It is better to accuse clearly
está mejor acusar a claro a la
generality to the State to the judges Claro
generalidad al Estado a los jueces Claro
clear clear clear man of course
claro claro claro hombre por supuesto
of course of course it's everyone's fault
por supuesto por supuesto la culpa es de
everyone is to blame
todo el mundo la culpa es de todo el
world
mundo
No, no, Marta hasn't said it.
no no lo ha dicho Marta no lo ha dicho
but when you are saying that it is
pero cuando tú estás diciendo que se la
They have invented that I don't know what that everything
han inventado que no no sé qué que todo
So, well then why do they accuse
tal Pues bueno entonces por qué acusan a
a person on the basis of what it is
una persona en base a de que se lo
invent someone gets 8 years of
inventan le cae a alguien 8 años de
prison based on inventions No way no
prisión a base inventos No como que no
It's difficult here in Spain for you to fall
es difícil aquí en España que te caiga
come on, it's quite difficult for you
vamos que es bastante difícil que te
a major sentence falls now and
caiga una condena importante Ya y lo
We all know that no, but well, it's that
sabemos todos pues no pero bueno es que
There are cases, of course, that are cases that are
hay casos claro es que hay casos que es
that is so cool Mania is so cool Mania
que está cogo Manía está cog Manía
There is always women, we are very bad
siempre está las mujeres somos muy malas
and we want to harm everyone, we are very
y queremos perjudicar todas somos muy
bad except for her who is very good and
malas menos ella que es muy buena y se
has hooked Javi's leg and
ha enganchado a la pierna de Javi y
until you give it until until you don't
hasta que no le de hasta hasta que no
reaches the marrow, it will not stop but the
llega al tuétano no va a parar pero el
the rest are very bad, they are invented
resto de son muy malas se inventan
accusations, clear, clear, clear, the
acusaciones Claro claro claro las
women, well you already know, you already know that
mujeres pues ya sabéis ya sabéis que las
women are very bad, the minors are
mujeres son muy malas las menores son
very bad, they are all very bad judges
muy malos todos son muy malos los jueces
we are all bad we are all bad
somos malos todos todos somos malos
Well, well, it's embarrassing
bueno bueno es que da vergüenza de
true But well what I tell you
verdad Pero bueno lo que os digo
I understand a lot because your
entiendo mucho pues su
frustration that has no other life
frustración que no tiene otra vida me
I imagine to know to know what will happen next
imagino a saber a saber lo que se cerá a
know what their ways will be like
saber lo que se cocerán sus maneras sus
forms your way of expressing yourself that
formas su esta forma de expresarse que
It is clear in the environment in which
tiene Pues claro en el ambiente en el
that surrounds itself In the environment in which it is
que se rodea En el ambiente en el que se
surrounds Clear because I understand
rodea Claro pues lo entiendo
perfectly now last night I understood
perfectamente ahora anoche entendí
many things of Well, everything, eh
muchísimas cosas de Pues de todo eh
Of course, now I understand perfectly that
claro Ahora entiendo perfectamente que
He was scared when the other told him that
se acojonado cuando la otra la dijo que
You also have to have little head to
también hay que tener poca cabeza para
tell something like that to the other to give her
contarle algo así a la otra para darle
weapons to the other knowing that she is a
armas a la otra conociéndola que es una
weather vane and is more dangerous than a
veleta y que tiene más peligro que una
bomb box because she is so
caja de bomba pues ella está es tan
list T that gave you that has given you
lista T que le dio que le ha dado
ammunition to the people and told him about his
munición a la gente y le ha contado su
life I imagine your life and miracles I don't know
vida me imagino su vida y milagros no sé
If I don't know, she will know. She will know.
si es que no sé ella sabrá ella sabrá
because in that head the truth is that
porque en esa cabeza la verdad que
try to be clear, try to reason, that is
intentar claro intentar razonar o sea
How can she reason? It's impossible.
como puede razonar ella es imposible
you have to be like her who is like
tienes que estar como ella que está como
Machn's maracas, that is, he is
las maracas de Machín o sea es que está
fatal the obsession he has with Javi is
fatal la obsesión que tiene con Javi es
that doesn't let her live, doesn't let her breathe
que no la deja vivir no la deja respirar
He doesn't let her eat, he doesn't let her be.
no la deja comer es que no la deja ser
really happy that I should
feliz de verdad que debería
we tried, it's been two years
tratáramos lleva eh dos años lleva
Trento treatment I'm not saying it
Trento tratamiento no lo estoy diciendo
I'm joking, I'm completely serious
de broma lo digo totalmente en serio
This is the obsession that Javi has that
esta la obsesión que tiene de Javi que
I think it is not
creo que no está
living But not to
viviendo Pero no a
and on top of that he threatens you, he has balls
a y encima te amenaza tiene huevos de
King Kong facets of his life that
King Kong facetas de su vida que
surely they will be very important
seguramente serán muy importante las
is parking due to unhealthy obsession
está aparcando por la obsesión enfermiza
that he has for Javi and for the obsession
que tiene por Javi y por la obsesión
sickly that she has for Javi because she is
enfermiza que tiene por Javi pues está
as it is, it will come out
quedando como está quedando va a salir
Here all your family exposed will go
aquí toda su familia expuesta van a
go out here until prompter but nothing that
salir aquí hasta apuntador pero nada que
Continue with Javi's session here
siga Que siga con la sesión de Javi aquí
the only one that is looking like [ __ ]
la única que está quedando como el culo
It is she, she and her environment because it is that
es ella ella y su entorno porque es que
call the condemnation to Javi having her
llamar el condenas a Javi teniendo ella
What he has already commands is that he commands, let's go
lo que tiene ya manda es que manda vamos
It's a real shame that you, having what you have
manda huevos que tú teniendo lo que tien
bleaching what bleaches and
blanqueando lo que blanquea y
justifying what justifies calls
justificando lo que justifica llames
You condemn Javi because he has fought with
condenas a Javi Porque se ha peleado con
I don't know who insulted, I don't know how much
no sé quién ha insultado no sé cuánto
Send send balls of shame of
Manda manda huevos de vergüenza de
shame but well no I mean no
vergüenza pero bueno no le O sea no
Don't expect anything from this whole group. I mean
esperéis nada de todo este grupo O sea
Don't expect this whole group to condemn
no esperéis que todo este grupo conden
nothing nor does it seem like an aberration to you, nothing nor
nada ni le parezca aberración nada ni
Nothing. They are welcome with the hatred they have for him.
nada De nada ellos con el odio que le
They have Javi, me FJ Elena lasne already with
tienen a Javi a mí FJ Elena lasne ya con
They don't care about anything, let's defend it.
eso les da igual todo vamos defenderían
Well, they would defend Daniel Sancho if
a Bueno defenderían a Daniel Sancho si
whatever was necessary and to whomever it was
hiciese falta y a quien fuese
They would defend themselves as long as they can give us
defenderían con tal de si nos pueden dar
to us who are worse
a nosotros que nosotros somos peores
because of course we meet in the
porque es que claro nos juntamos en los
geeky tubers and that should be punishable
friky tubers y Eso debería estar penado
with permanent revisable prison sentence, that's worse
con prisión permanente revisable eso peo
It is other little things because it seems that it is not
es otras cositas pues parece ser que no
because for you to get 8 years of
porque para que te caigan 8 años de
prison
prisión
cloth, cloth, cloth so that it falls on you
telita telita telita para que te caiga
But of course this is not clear as always.
pero claro esto como siempre no Claro é
It has not been the case, it was others who are
no ha sido se la lo eran otros que es
that he has a grudge against him, which is clear
que le tiene manía que es que claro
clear clear clear clear clear clear
claro claro claro claro claro des
Shame on you for moving that thing
vergüenza que vamos que muevas eso que
you have like in your mouth that which you have to
tienes como de boca eso que tienes que
It's a garbage pit that you move to
es un pozo de basura que lo muevas para
criticize Javi Call condemnations to
criticar tú a Javi Llamar condenas a
There are many Javi and forklift drivers.
Javi y carretillero hay muchos
Tania told me something about the cart drivers
carretilleros la Tania me decía algo de
forklift driver to me pay attention to this Alexis
carretillero a mí atentos a esta Alexis
This harassment account is worth looking at what
esta cuenta de acoso vale fijaros lo que
This guy has been in his house all day
pone tío este lleva todo el día en su
profile going around to see if it finds
perfil dando vueltas a ver si encuentra
something eh To justify why please
algo eh Para justificar porque por favor
Well Javi you made peace with Dross
pues Javi hiciste las pases con Dross
Uncle, I understand perfectly why not
tío entiendo perfectamente por no
you show your face Alexis I understand or
muestras tu cara Alexis lo entiendo o
look what a topic says here already
sea mira lo que pone aquí un tema ya
judged and that sentence served and now
juzgado y cumplida esa sentencia y ahora
They come from false moralists out of revenge
vienen de falsos moralistas por venganza
personal and his Circus is a topic already a
personal y su Circo es un tema ya es un
subject already judged and fulfilled that
tema ya juzgado y cumplida esa
sentence already Why sea a
sentencia ya Por qué mar un
kiss is a topic already judged look at the
beso es un tema ya juzgado mirar el
tweet Alexis two days before everything
tweet Alexis dos días antes de que todo
came out
saliera
eh two days before everything came out
eh dos días antes de que todo saliera
Check out del's tweet
Mira el tweet de del
same according to Mr. Javi Oliveira this
mismo según el señor Javi oliveira esto
hence
por lo que
They have condemned him here in the first instance
lo han condenado aquí en primera
instance are unimportant nonsense
instancia son tonterías sin importancia
simple insults judge for yourselves
simples insultos juzguen vosotros
Judge this matter for yourselves
mismos juzguen vosotros mismos este tema
no insults have been judged
no se ha juzgado no unos insultos no
anarchy
anarquía
Uy uy uuu some insults anarchy for
Uy uy uuu unos insultos anarquía por
God, what did I say to him? Oh oh oh oh, for the flirt?
Dios Qué le dije Uy uy uy uy pel coba u
oh oh oh for God's sake
u u u por Dios
Let's get out of here, from this channel. Let's go to
Vámonos de aquí de este canal Vámonos a
where abuses are defended Miguel
donde se defienden abusos Miguel
pastrana How handsome you are
pastrana Cómo estás guapísimo un
tremendous kiss eh is that they have little
beso tremendo eh es que tienen poca
shame after all
vergüenza después de todo
dude imagine comparing
tío imagínate comparar
Javi Oliveira, now convicted after
Javi oliveira el ahora condenado después
of having attacked Miare and many others
de haber atacado a miare y a muchas
other girls for alleged complaints
otras chicas por supuestas denuncias
false accusations against his friend now that he is
falsas contra su amigo ahora que es
against someone you don't like
contra alguien que le cae mal la
alleged false complaint is valid what
supuesta denuncia falsa es válida qué
alleged false accusation
supuesta denuncia falsa supuesta
false accusation uncle in the sentence in
denuncia falsa tío en la sentencia en
The proven facts tell you what is
los hechos probados te dice lo que está
has been tested and what it recognizes
a probado y lo que reconoce el
denounced
denunciado
mother
madre
mine and this
mía y esto
that all our support to Tania this
qué todo nuestro apoyo a Tania esto
has to
tiene que
stop let's remember
parar vamos a recordar
to
a
Of course, let's give Loli this clip of the
claro vamos darle a Loli este clip de la
first time it was known that there was something
primera vez que se supo que había algo
Here I have said and I consider that not
por aquí qu he dicho y Considero que no
He has insulted her since I have not fallen so much
la ha insultado ya que no he caído tan
under of me name a disease without
bajo de de me nombrar una enfermedad sin
have no [ __ ]
tener ni [__]
idea and if you have an idea then it is
idea y si tiene idea pues entonces es
a real criminal lying like that
una delincuente de [__] mintiendo así
just for a little bit of Caso come and go
solo por un poquito de Caso venga váyase
you go for a walk for a while, whatever suits you
usted a pasear un rato que le vaya
nice t next time I swear eh the
bonito t la próxima te lo juro eh la
Next time I swear we'll explain it.
próxima te lo juro que explicamos el
audio of my husband and we ask you what
audio de mi marido y te preguntamos que
why don't you have any
por qué tú no tienes ninguno
Come on, I swear I'm not going to say it because I think I'm going
venga no te lo juro porque creo que voy
that I have not yet lost all
que todavía no he perdido toda la
dignity as you are worth So don't you God
dignidad como tú vale Así que no te Dios
Of course I still have a host left Of course of course
Claro todavía me queda ostia Claro claro
that Tania is not going to say. Of course.
que no va a decir n la Tania Claro que
He's not going to say anything, but nothing, nothing, you already know.
no va a decir nada pero nada nada ya te
I say it myself
lo digo yo
Oh, there's the bomb.
[__] Ah está la bomba
Ugh, let's see, some things are coming to me.
Uf a ver a mí me llegan algunas cosas
but I'm not going to get involved in her things
pero yo no me voy a meter en cosas ella
she has meddled in my affairs, she has
se ha metido en cosas mías ella se ha
involved in my own affairs and I would almost see myself
metido en cosas mías y casi que me vería
I with the right Look what I tell you
yo con el derecho Fíjate lo que te digo
I could almost see the right one. Look
casi que me vería yo el derecho Fíjate
what I tell you but I'm not going to do that, I'm going to do that
lo que te digo pero no voy a así yo voy
to do things right if you have a husband
a hacer las cosas bien sí tiene marido
Hey, I didn't say that she doesn't have a husband.
eh que no tiene marido yo no lo he dicho
Eh yes it has or well it must have I don't know
Eh sí tiene o bueno debe tener No lo sé
if you haven't separated a few days ago
si no se ha separado Hace unos días
has
tiene
husband I think Maybe she's not married no
marido creo A lo mejor no está casada no
I know
lo sé
but if she has a husband
pero si marido sí tiene
I believe and
creo y
[Music]
[Música]
family now in pajamas and tell Loli
familia ahora en pijamita y dile a Loli
If you have it, come have a tit and throw it.
que si tiene venga ten [__] y tira Que
We will tell the story well because of course you
contaremos bien la cosa porque Claro tú
you're going to expose my family But
vas a exponer a mi familia Pero
We will tell you why Maybe you don't
contaremos por qué A lo mejor tú no
you can expose it And how about you too
puedes exponerla Y qué tal también te
we can ask how loneliness is going
podemos preguntar qué tal va la soledad
on certain occasions How to carry it
en según qué ocasiones Cómo se lleva
Ok Natania
vale natania
Come on with all your chichi, you expose another
Vamos con todo tu [__] tú expon otra
see my family if you have a [ __ ]
vez a mi familia si tienes [__] tú
put it and we'll see if you're in
ponlo que veremos a ver si tú estás en
the same situation you would first have to
la misma situación primero tendrías que
have your neighborhood
haber barrio tu
home first you should have
casa primero tendrías que haberte
be careful of what you have
cuidado de lo que tienes
I hid
escondido yo
Look Tania, they should arrest her because she is a
Mira Tania que la detengan que es una
evil and ambitious liar no longer
mentirosa malvada y ambiciosa ya no la
I can bear that
puedo soportar que lo
stop me, he stole the cma, he took it
detengan me ha robado la cma ha llevado
my soul and I can no longer
mi alma y yo ya no puedo
[Music]
[Música]
but I'll leave it there
más ahí lo dejo
In the meantime we will think
t Mientras tanto iremos pensando
Tania's studies of what they were
los estudios de Tania de qué eran
lawyer
abogada
criminologist where she got it in a course
criminóloga dónde se lo sacó en un curso
intensive and today This was the first
intensivo y hoy Esto ella fue la primera
who threatened her with this topic and now
que la amenazó con este tema y ahora
when the topic comes up without any threat
cuando sale el tema sin ninguna amenaza
all ours
todo nuestro
support me they are recording me eh how I have
apoyo a mí me están grabando eh cómo he
I put it here in this tweet to me
puesto yo aquí en este tweet a mí me
are
están
recording
grabando
Ah, let's see how Mr. Javier continues.
Ah a ver cómo sigue el señor Javier
Oliveira lying, cheating and scamming
oliveira mintiendo engañando y estafando
Let's see, is there anyone here who doesn't know?
a ver hay alguien aquí que no sepa es
Where is this because we are going eh From
Dónde está esto porque vamos eh De
I'm really not in the center.
verdad de verdad no estoy en el centro
from de Palma eh I already know
de de Palma eh Ya lo
I say that I have been the first one who has
digo que yo he sido la primera que he
tried to stop wars I said no
intentado frenar guerras he dicho no
go around there or rather listen that that that to
vayas por ahí o sea oiga que que que a
see I have tried everything
ver yo lo he intentado de todas las
ways it makes me sad that it comes out But not because
maneras me da pena que salga Pero no por
her but because of the situation that she
ella sino por la situación que ella
I can have behind me, you understand what it gives you
pueda tener detrás me entiendes lo te da
It's a shame that she's leaving, but not because of her, but because of
pena que salga Pero no por ella sino por
the situation behind which
la situación que tiene detrás la cual
You, madam, are one of the greatest
usted señora es una de las mayor ces de
that it came out okay Ah that the culprit
que haya salido vale Ah que la culpable
It's consolation in the end, it's worth it, it's worth it.
es consuelo al final vale vale usted
lady is one of the main
señora es una de las principales
guilty of its release and if not the
culpables de que haya salido y si no el
day that this is clarified Well, here
día que se aclare esto Pues que aquí
everyone around you
todos los que tiene usted a su alrededor
all those who are
todos esos que están
There they will have to teach and say no.
ahí tendrán que enseñar y decir no ha
been Loli Mira has been Loli Loli has
sido Loli Mira ha sido Loli Loli ha
sung that they have one
cantado que la de tengan una
dangers Silvia says Javi can
peligros Silvia dice Javi se puede
publish the sentence the sentence now
publicar la sentencia la sentencia ya
is published in the
está publicada en el
poderjudicial.com the sentence is
poderjudicial.com la sentencia está
published and the data to find it
publicada y los datos para encontrarla
Tania publishes them in
los publica la Tania en
I can't be submissive and ambitious anymore.
subl y ambiciosa ya no la puedo
control I don't know where there
controlar yo no sé en qué parte de ahí
It is seen that all that is denoted that they
se ve se denota todo eso Que ellos
They want to take out and and and accuse me of that
quieren sacar y y y acusarme a mí de que
Tania has to leave Antonio from her house
Tania tiene que barar de su casa Antonio
has to leave his house because
tiene que barar de su casa porque
were exposing my people to
estaban exponiendo mi gente la gente a
bringing up personal issues of mine
sacando temas personales de mi
life is very good Loli you have messed up you have
vida muy bien Loli te has liado te has
made a mess and here you are saying it
hecho un lío y aquí lo estás diciendo
Antonio and Tania were indeed releasing songs.
Antonio Y Tania sí estaban sacando temas
personal details of your life Antonio and Tania yes
personales de tu vida Antonio Y Tania si
They were taking out your private things in
estaban sacando cosas privadas tuyas en
its channels
sus canales
And this is the last time I repeat it.
Y esta es la última vez que lo repito
because I have that
porque yo eso lo tengo
forgotten Ah you have forgotten that is
olvidado Ah eso lo tienes olvidado es
that Loli insists that I am
que Loli insiste en que yo estoy
lying When I say that she threatened to
mintiendo Cuando digo que ella amenazó a
Tania, with telling this, look at Loli just in case
Tania con contar esto mira Loli por si
the click we just saw is of no use to you
no te sirve el click que acabamos de ver
Just now here you have another one
hace un momento aquí tienes otro una
person I think is very fake and very bad
persona creo que es muy falsa y muy mala
person like you I tell him and now if he knows
persona como tú se lo digo y ahora si se
It's like the 2000 are gone. Okay, you're
va mir como si se van los 2000 Vale Eres
very
muy
bad and be careful not to let this out of you
mala y cuidadito a salirte de ti esto
This is not a threat because it would not be
Esto no es una amenaza Porque no sería
I already told you
yo ya te lo
I say it wouldn't be me who read it the same as with de
digo no sería yo lo lea igual que con de
tro because that's what I'm here for To moderate
tro porque para eso estoy Para moderar
But now they come to me and tell me two things
pero que ahora me vengan a m a decir dos
or three that I knew and Maria what
o tres que yo sabía y María lo que
It happened, we didn't know anything at first
pasaba no sabíamos nada primeramente
because we were even soft by the
porque estábamos bladas hasta por el
WhatsApp and
WhatsApp y
second says perhaps The question would be the
segundo dice quizás La pregunta sería la
have ever ceased to have the
han dejado de tener alguna vez la
Peppa and Loli's relationship is now a Gossip
relación Peppa y Loli ahora sol Cotilla
I doubt it I doubt it I already doubt it because I already
lo dudo lo dudo ya lo dudo porque ya me
He said that what I filled his head with was
dijo que que le llené la cabeza era
I had treated her 50 times better. Okay.
yo la había tratado 50 veces mejor Vale
Well, that's fine. Well, it's even more fake.
pues ya está muy bien Bueno ta más falsa
The one who filled my head was her
la que me llenaba la cabeza era ella
but the one who had spoken against me
pero la que me había hablado en contra
Peppa's if it was her
de Peppa si era ella
Eha Tania, tomorrow you'll set up another one.
eha Tania mañana te montas otro
show But this time a little more
espectáculo Pero esta vez un poco más
credible there with the ones you take eln and you
creíble ahí con los te coges elín y te
you put it on, you cover your face and when you
lo pones te tapas la cara y y cuando te
You take it off and you're left looking like a total figure.
lo quites ya te quedes echa un figur tod
eh with the rhyme like yesterday he said then
eh con el rimen cómo ayer dijo luego lo
we'll see
veremos
that he had treated 50 times better than me
que había tratado 50 veces mejor que yo
and yesterday on the flight I thought I understood
y ayer en el vuelo me pareció entender
that an audio was put on as if there was
que se puso un audio como que hab
sent audios V piece I think that
enviado audios V trozo creo quea que
that does not leave the
que no se salga del
Guy Joe Hunter, I'm going to tell you something.
ticho Joe Hunter os voy a contar una
story there is a lady who lives
historia hay una señora que vive
obsessed with talking about a YouTube day
obsesionada con hablar de un YouTube día
and night to which he dedicates his content
y noche al que dedica Su contenido de
compulsively looking for any
forma compulsiva buscando cualquier
nonsense to turn around and call
chorrada para darle la vuelta y llamar
his attention makes him sing absurd songs
su atención le hace canciones absurdas
with one like a fifteen-year-old to the boy
con ia una como una quinceañera al chico
who likes school Hey Hey today Tania
que le gusta el cole Oye Oye hoy Tania
has responded to this controversy with a
ha contestado a esta polémica con una
ia's song
canción de ia
uncle
tío
uncle they give him a sentence that he is
tío le sacan una sentencia de que está
Married. Well, I don't know if she is married.
casada Bueno no sé si es casada ella lo
call husband in that flo they take one out
llama marido en eso flo le sacan una
sentence that she is married to
sentencia de que está casada con
a man convicted of abuse
un hombre condenado por abuso a
minors and the girl does one to you
menores y la chiquilla te hace una
song with girl outraged by her
canción con nia indignada por su
privacy
privacidad
The lady has read that she did not understand
la señora se ha leído que no comprendido
a law book for dummies and they are
un libro de derecho para tontos y se las
gives the impression of being a scholar and expert in sentences
da de erudita y experta en sentencias
she has the freedom to speak outside of them
ajenas ella tiene la libertad de hablar
to give an opinion and point the finger at everything
opinar y señalar con el dedo todo lo que
makes his favorite YouTuber insult
hace su youtuber favorito insulta
slander and shout shout shout a lot without
calumnia y grita grita grita mucho sin
However, the learned lady has not had
embargo la señora erudita no ha tenido
enough time on your channel to read
tiempo suficiente en su canal para leer
analyze and present a sentence that
analizar y exponer una sentencia que
I had it very close at hand, it is something
tenía muy a mano se trata de algo
terrible for what someone very close to me said
terrible por lo que alguien muy allegado
She was sentenced and imprisoned in her
a ella fue condenado y encarcelado en su
day was responsible for spreading it everywhere
día se encargó de difundir por donde
It could be that this sentence was unfair and not
pudo que esa sentencia era injusta y no
would have minded appearing in the
le hubiera importado aparecer en los
means to give it visibility in fact
medios para darle visibilidad de hecho
The sentence is unfair because to me
la sentencia sí es injusta porque a mí
It seems to me that the things they put and that
me parece que las cosas que ponen y que
are narrated in that
se narran en esa
sentence is not paid with 8 years of
sentencia no se pagan con 8 años de
dece the things that sentence narrates
carce las cosas que narra esa sentencia
they are not paid with 88 years in prison
no se pagan con 88 años de cárcel
Hey, the sentence is unfair.
eh la sentencia es injusta
eh I don't know if I'll do another live stream for you
eh No sé si Os haré otro directo
reading it like she did with mine
leyéndola como ella hizo con la mía
It depends if it continues and more things that
Depende si sigue vale Y más cosas que
there is but it is a
hay pero es una
barbarity is barbarity And I
barbaridad es una barbaridad Y a mí me
It seems very strong if this Joan Planas does it
parece muy fuerte si esto Joan planas lo
I knew if this Loli would
sabía si esto Loli lo
I knew, I don't know if I don't know who else would know.
sabía no sé si no sé quién más lo sabría
the truth But it seems very heavy to me well
la verdad Pero me parece muy heavy bueno
and that this is being supported now that
y que se esté apoyando esto ahora que
people sending support like we have
gente mandándole apoyo como como hemos
seen it seems to me
visto a mí me parece
incredible the penalty is absurdly low
increíble la pena es Absurda de lo baja
which is totally Nati but listen to me
que es totalmente Nati pero escúchame
that is not, I am not telling you the
que no es están no os estoy contando los
details eh Because I don't have either
detalles eh Porque es que tampoco tengo
you win the truth but it is a very thing
ganas la verdad pero es una cosa muy
strong what is narrated are several things
fuerte lo que se narra son varias cosas
very strong for this aunt then
muy fuertes para que esta tía luego
out there saying that it was that that
fuera por ahí diciendo que era que que
that no, that there wasn't
que no que no había
test is strong
prueba es fuerte
Uncle now doesn't like it to be known
tío ahora ya no le gusta que se sepa
because it affects an anonymous person
porque afecta a una persona anónima era
anonymous when she presented her case in
anónima cuando exponía su caso en
chain.org anonymity and privacy
chain.org el anonimato y la privacidad
are of K and p we can talk about
son de K y p se puede hablar de
other people's sentences that are made public
sentencias ajenas que se hacen públicas
yes or no Don't worry that another expert
sí o no No te preocupes que otra experta
in law offers you its help although already
en derecho te ofrece su ayuda aunque ya
We know what you think about your money, let's see.
sabemos lo que opinas de su dinero a ver
Tomorrow, Friday, we will do a live show.
mañana viernes haremos un directito
went to see a lawyer to take
fuera a a ver a un abogado para tomar
measures already more than one degree higher than
medidas ya más un grado más superior a
it
lo
What has happened with these people but
que a lo que se ha con esta gente pero
not only that but I intend to put him in
no solamente sino que pienso ponerle en
contact with taa PM Mrs. Loli Werta
contacto con taña PM señora Loli werta
I'll tell you to your face, put the money in
ya se lo digo a la cara métase el dinero
Tomorrow Friday we will do a ass
por el culo mañana viernes haremos un
Dania has the firm of
directito Dania tiene el bufete de
Joan Plana's lawyer once said it
abogado de Joan plana lo dijo una vez
but Loli since you have so much
pero Loli ya que tienes tanta
Loli's disposition to take this clip for
disposición Loli cogerle este clip por
Please and let him know that I know that
favor Y hacérselo llegar que yo sé que
You on Twitter let them know
ustedes en Twitter se lo hacéis llegar
Loli, since you are so willing
Loli que ya que tienes tanta disposición
to go tomorrow afternoon to do a
de ir mañana por la tarde a hacer un
direct to see a lawyer tell him about
directo para ver a un abogado dile de
way that you present yourselves in the cause that
camino que os presentéis en la causa que
I have you on, okay, we have the
os tengo puesta vale que tenemos el
trial in 2026 And you are in time to
juicio en el 2026 Y estás a tiempo de
introduce yourself that even though you are now
presentarte que aunque ahora estés
declared in rebellion by the court
declarada en Rebeldía por el juzgado
Okay
vale
and you still have time if you love yourself
e todavía estás a tiempo si te quieres
defend if the trial is not held without
defender si no se hace el juicio sin que
You defend yourself, okay, but man, what are you doing?
te defiendas vale pero hombre que ya que
You're going to find a lawyer for Tania tomorrow.
vas mañana a buscarle un abogado a Tania
eh To defend her from what she has
eh Para defenderla de de esto que tiene
No
no
and that for you their privacy is violated
e que para ti se se vulnera su intimidad
Okay, so on the way, grab the lawyer and
Vale pues ya de camino coge al abogado y
Hire him also to appear in the
contrátalo también para personar en la
cause Hey, it would be nice if you
causa Oye que estaría bien que te
personify and introduce yourself as it has been
personar y te presentaras que ha sido
notified of the claim and you have decided not to
notificada la demanda Y has decidido no
personarte is worth what you say about that
personarte vale que lo que dice t de que
it is archive it is not
es archiva no es
true man
verdad hombre
self-criticism accused you of having H accounts
autocrítica te acusó de tener cuentas H
they have them accused you of having
ellos las tienen te acusó de tener
bullying groups they have it He accused you
grupos de acoso ellos lo tienen Te acusó
of having poop with eyes hidden and they
de tener caca con ojos oculta y ellos la
What they have against you is that
tienen lo que tienen en tu contra es que
you are Light of them and
estás Luz de ellos y
georgio review a kiss yesterday they sent me
crítica georgio un beso Ayer me mandaron
a good one I'm not going to say what But
un bueno no voy a decir el qué Pero
someone saying that it's me I see you until
alguien diciendo que soy yo te veo hasta
the cataplines with this man georgio
los cataplines con esto hombre georgio
This was this is serious this is serious
Esto fue esto es serio esto es serio
This topic is very unpleasant and very
este tema es muy desagradable y muy
Seriously I hope he stays here eh And what
serio Espero que se quede aquí eh Y que
the girl, if I were her, what would I do?
la tipa yo si fuera ella yo lo que haría
It would be you know what it is. So that is
sería sabéis qué es lo que es O sea que
[ __ ] what are we talking about, abuse
[__] que estamos hablando un abuso a
minors that she defended if she were her
menores que ella defendió si fuera ella
What I would do would be
yo lo que haría sería
I'm going to ask for the right to be forgotten.
irme pedir el derecho al olvido Que se
delete all presence of her on the internet
borre toda presencia de ella en internet
and not appearing on the internet anymore that would be
y no aparecer más por internet eso sería
what a person would do with
lo que lo que haría una persona con
shame it won't be
vergüenza no lo va a serer
Yesterday I heard someone who was
em ayer escuché a alguien que estaba
saying Well they sent it to me in the
diciendo Bueno me lo mandaron en el
group that does not mean that we have this
grupo que no que es que esto lo hemos
removed because we are low on ratings
sacado porque estamos bajo de audiencia
and how He Forgives
y como Perdona
eh Sorry under of
eh Perdona bajo de
Contra hearing
audiencia de Contra
who I think I am in real life is the one
quién creo que en directo soy soy el
first or the
primero o el
second bass are we go now those who
segundo bajo están vamos ya los que
they are below me they are below me
están por debajo de mí están por debajo
from 1000 below 1000
de 1000 por debajo de 1000
spectators That is to say, it makes no sense
espectadores O sea no tiene sentido la
obsession with the audience I have
obsesión con la audiencia que tenga yo
What a guy, don't look at the audience that
que tío que no miréis la audiencia que
I have to not have to, it suits me very well
tenga yo que no tenga que a mí me va muy
Although I did it for the audience, it is
bien que yo lo hacía por audiencia es
as if I have put it in
como si lo he puesto en
Twitter what a shame really what
Twitter qué vergüenza de verdad lo que
you are supporting uncle what is happening
se está apoyando tío lo que se está
supporting let's take a look at the
apoyando vamos a echar un vistazo al
straight what Loli did defending her and
directo que hecho Loli defendiéndola y
Then we changed a little bit now
Luego cambiamos un poquito ya
the third no and we go to the
el el tercio no y nos vamos a al
gossip to see what she answered
chismorreo a ver qué le ha contestado la
Pepa to the Troy air
[__] al ar de Troya
and all the people who go in
y de todas las de la gente que va en
against wars and all that nonsense
contra de las guerras y de todo el rollo
This makes me feel very sorry, eh. You also feel it.
este me da mucha pena eh También te lo
I have to say It was you ma'am It was you
tengo que decir Fuiste tú señora Fuiste
You were the first to come out with a
tú la primera que salió junto con un
gentleman with problems also moderately
señor con problemas también medianamente
You were of the same type
del mismo tipo Fuiste
You were the one who, when I told you that if you
tú fuiste tú la que al decirte que si te
would change the name on a channel where it was
cambiara el nombre en un canal donde era
moderator deir you decided to leave ma'am and
moderadora deir decidiste irte señora y
It was you who went looking for attention
Fuiste tú la que fuiste buscando casito
for a viewing and selling Amiga
por una visualización y vendiendo Amiga
It was you. Oh, okay, there are several.
fuiste tú Ah vale es que hay varias
people who had not had this either
personas que esto también no lo habíamos
mentioned
mencionado
eh was part of the nonsense of the
eh fuera parte de la tontería de la
privacy that is already dismantled
privacidad que ya eso queda desmontado
at the moment that it is Tania who has
en el momento que es Tania la que le ha
spread this and made it public
dado difusión a esto y lo hizo público
ok collecting signature making a
vale recogiendo firma haciendo una
collecting signatures is valid apart from the
recogida de de firmas vale aparte de la
I have already dismantled your privacy too
privacidad ya os he desmontado también
that this is what this is used for
que esto se que esto sea utilizar
relatives to attack someone not
familiares para para atacar a alguien no
do not use relatives to attack
no utilizar familiares para atacar a
someone is when I am mentioned to
alguien es cuando a mí se me menciona a
my children eh When when has been called
mis hijos eh Cuando cuando se ha llamado
Loli Huertas's sister could be
la hermana de Loli huertas podría ser
also use relatives Juan mi
también utilizar familiares Juan mi
vegue welcome a kiss there are many
vegue bienvenido un beso hay muchos
cases that could be used
casos que podrían ser utilizar
relatives
familiares
illegitimately okay to me there are many
ilegítimamente vale a mí hay muchas
occasions that I have seen on youtuber
ocasiones que yo he visto en youtuber
that are mentioned and family members are brought in
que se mencionan y se meten a familiares
of the people who do not come to
de la gente por medio que no viene a
The story is fine, but in this case no one is there.
cuento vale pero en este caso nadie está
By including the family member, we'll at least
metiendo al familiar vamos por lo menos
Of those I have seen, no one has given his
de los que yo he visto nadie ha dado su
name your identity no one has given anything
nombre su identidad nadie ha dado nada
There is talk about the campaign that has
se está hablando de de la campaña que ha
Tania's fact and the defense she makes
hecho Tania y de la defensa que hace
Tania, that crime is worth it, that is, me.
Tania de ese delito vale o sea yo Por
example I repeat it again just in case
ejemplo yo lo vuelvo a repetir por si
Someone hasn't seen it before But
alguien no lo ha visto antes Pero
Any of us can have a relative
cualquiera podemos tener un familiar un
father, an uncle, a grandfather, a brother is worth it
padre un tío un abuelo un hermano vale
Even a child who goes wrong in life
Incluso un hijo que se tuerza en la vida
and that and that it is problematic and that there is
y que y que sea problemático y que haya
committed serious crimes okay But that You
cometido delitos gordos vale Pero eso Tú
It's not your fault you don't choose your
no tienes culpa tú no eliges a tu
family is worth it, family is mandatory
familia vale la familia es obligatoria
You are worth the most you can do, I am.
vale tú lo máximo que puedes hacer yo
For example, if it happened to me that I
Por ejemplo si a mí me pasara que yo
I have a son or a father who does the same.
tengo un hijo o o un padre que hace lo
same as this person has done and for
mismo que ha hecho esta persona y para
I would have obviously died
mí habría muerto evidentemente
I think a son too
yo creo que un hijo también
not a son no I think a son
no un hijo no yo creo que un hijo
I don't know the truth, [ __ ] what
también No lo sé la verdad [__] Qué
This topic is not complicated but man
complicado no es este tema pero hombre
a father a brother does this and for me
un padre un hermano hace esto y para mí
would have obviously died but here he
habría muerto evidentemente pero aquí el
The issue is not that he is a relative and she is not
tema no es que sea un familiar y ella no
It's your fault, no, no, no, the issue here is that
tenga culpa no no no aquí el tema Es que
This is a guy she knows and I know it
esto es un tío que ella conoce y lo se
He puts a guy he doesn't know to defend him
pone a defenderlo a un tío que no conoce
because look Because he feels like it
porque mira Porque le da la gana se
stays with his version or whatever
queda con la versión de él o lo que sea
Okay, but the version of him in the
vale pero es que la versión de él en el
judged in
juzgado en
the end in the end is that whoever does not understand it
fin en fin es que quien no lo entienda
I can't do anything anymore because it's going to happen
yo ya no puedo hacer nada porque lo va a
justify
justificar
man you know what are you doing
tío sabes o sea pero qué estáis
defending my God of my life What
defendiendo Dios mío de mi vida Qué
you are defending that you are
estáis defendiendo que estáis
defending the biggest thing that is not known
defendiendo ya lo más gordo que no se
can
puede
Defending the sentence is worse for me
defender la sentencia para mí es peor
that of Daniel Sancho, uncle of
que la de Daniel Sancho tío de
true madam The one you told it to
verdad señora La que se lo has contado a
people and it was you lady who has been
gente y Fuiste tú señora La que has sido
informing this whole pack so that
informando a toda esta manada para que
They could attack Tania. It was you.
pudieran atacar a Tania Fuiste tú
regardless you feel sorry and you don't
independientemente te da pena y no te
It was sad when your partner threatened him in
dio pena cuando lo amenazó tu pareja en
straight up what a nerve dude they are
directo qué morro tío es que son
tremendous eh Ah that was consolation to
tremendas eh Ah que fue consuelo al
the end is the one who has snitched and the
final la que la que se ha a chivado y la
who threatened Tania with telling it. Oh, okay.
que amenazó a Tania con contarlo Ah vale
okay okay okay okay okay I thought that
vale vale vale vale vale Yo me creía que
It had been you Loli, I believed it, it's true
había sido tú Loli yo me crea es verdad
Loli that you didn't that you sang that it
Loli que tú no que tú cantaste que lo
stop by the ar of Troy it is true it is
detengan por ar de Troya es verdad es
true damn, how badly we thought
verdad [__] que mal pensado fuimos
because it has been you, madam, it has been you
porque has sido tú señora has sido tú la
that you have spoken to people telling them that
que has hablado con gente contándole ese
Topic: Mrs. Vale, now laugh a little while ago
tema señora Vale ahora rí hace un ratito
and since his lord had in his future
y ya que su señor tuvo en su futuro
problems Tell him to stop threatening and
problemas Dígale que deje de amenazar y
the faster the better to act because what
más rápido es mejor actuar porque lo que
She doesn't have such a big lady, she is just a
no tiene taña señora es que es una es
that is as cowardly as you are worth That
que es tan cobarde como ustedes vale Esa
It's the part that Tania doesn't have. Tania goes
es la parte que no tiene Tania Tania va
Tania shows her face and Tania shows her face
de cara Tania da la cara y Tania enseña
What he is talking about is not going away and
de lo que está hablando no se va y se
makes a Union to the pack in exchange for
hace una Unión a la manada a cambio de
sell what you have sold to her, madam
vender lo que usted le ha vendido señora
and you are madam have you been together
y es usted señora ha sido usted junto
with your partner more your partner than you
con su pareja más su pareja que usted el
that the one who passed the information to everyone
que el que pasó la información a toda
This herd of
esta manada de
people just because you were very
gente solo solo porque estaba usted muy
I am happy to be a moderator with her name
a gusto siendo moderadora con su nombre
and was asked to remove it
y se le pidió que se que se quitara el
name so that there would be no attacks
nombre para que no hubiera ataques
her channel she has gone through topics
su canal ella ha pasado por temas
similar the fact is that we have not
parecidos el caso está en que no hemos
seeing the way your partner has
visto esas formas que tiene su pareja de
address people in other ways
dirigirse a la gente en otr en otras
people we have seen in their
personas las hemos visto en su
couple his partner said on another channel that
pareja su pareja dijo en otro canal que
just like mine I could give
al igual a los míos le podía dar
Shame on you for going out on the street, ma'am.
vergüenza salir a la calle pues señora
What I don't know is how you don't give it to him
Lo que no sé es como no le da usted
ashamed to go out on the street with one
vergüenza salir a la calle con una
person like the one next to you
persona como la que tiene al lado
and now go and tell it to the lawyer. Oh, okay.
y ahora vaya y se lo al abogado Ah vale
I tell you that it is you who has to
conzuelo que a ti es la que te tiene que
It's embarrassing to have such a person around
dar vergüenza tener una persona así al
side okay it's true Julia damn in the end
lado vale es verdad Julia [__] al final
I have not clarified that point, it was about the
no he aclarado ese punto estaba lo de la
privacy is that I was reading a
privacidad es que estaba leyendo un
WhatsApp that they have me
WhatsApp que me han
sent me a message that they just sent me
mandado que me acaban de mandar un
WhatsApp that leaked the so-so WhatsApp
WhatsApp que filtró la tan un WhatsApp
with anarchy eh
con anarquía eh
There is the point of privacy that they are
está el punto de la privacidad que están
saying people is the point of
diciendo la gente está el punto de
use the family they are saying
utilizar a la familia que están diciendo
people and there is the issue that there are people
la gente y está el tema de que hay gente
also that he is saying that is why
también que está diciendo que por eso
Tania sympathized with Antonio David
Tania simpatizaba con Antonio David
because she was fighting for her cause
porque ella estaba luchando por su causa
your injustice man Forgive me but
su injusticia hombre Perdóname pero
Come on Antonio, listen to those of you who are here.
vamos Antonio d escucha a los que estáis
saying that and let's go I think Antonio
diciendo eso y vamos yo creo que Antonio
If David heard that, he would go into a fit.
David si escucha eso entraría en brote
eh Because I would enter, so let's see
eh Porque yo entraría o sea vamos a ver
Someone is comparing the complaint that
alguien está comparando la denuncia que
Antonio David was given this with
se le puso a Antonio David con esta con
This case of this gentleman who came in 8 years
este caso de este señor que entró 8 años
Well, 8 years are not 8 years, I don't know.
bueno 8 años no son 8 años más no sé
how many
cuántos
They have sent me a WhatsApp that has
por Me han mandado un WhatsApp que ha
Tania accidentally leaked on a live stream
filtrado Tania sin querer en un directo
with Alexis with anarchy
de con el Alexis con el anarquía
starts talking to him privately
se pone a hablarse con él por privado
by WhatsApp
por WhatsApp
Hey man, man, man, man, to Antonio Avil
eh hombre tío hombre tío a Antonio avil
They wanted him, they wanted to report him for
lo querían lo querían denunciar por
gender violence because she spoke badly
violencia de género porque hablaba mal
of the woman on TV and that caused her
de la mujer en la tele y eso le causaba
psychological problems to the woman wanted
problemas psicológico a la mujer quería
claim woman of course they are telling me
alegar mujer claro me lo están
comparing
comparando
Uncle, they're comparing me to a
tío me lo están comparando con con una
person convicted of violence
persona condenada por violencia de
gender and for abuse of a minor It is that not
género y por abuso a una menor Es que no
I want to start narrating the details that
quiero ponerme a narrar los detalles que
Put the sentence for the moment but what
Pon la sentencia de momento pero lo que
narrates the sentence is brutal and how it
narra la sentencia es brutal y cómo lo
They catch And what things the girl did to him or
pillan Y qué cosas le hacía la niña o
be it is
sea es
brutal is brutal what is happening
brutal es brutal lo que se está
defending is brutal what is being done
defendiendo es brutal lo que se está
defending the people who are
defendiendo la gente que lo está
truly defending from
defendiendo de verdad de
true because it is you madam who has
verdad porque es usted señora La que ha
taken out and the one that has begun to join
sacado y la que ha empezado a unirse a
all these people and to have something to give
toda esta gente y para tener algo que le
made a claim to be given the
hiciera reclamo para que le dieran la
little window you have used a friendship
ventanita ha utilizado usted una amistad
that you and your Tanio had with PM lie
que tuvo con tanio PM mentira usted y su
husband or partner or with whom you live or
marido o su pareja o con el que vive o
with which
con el que
It's clear that I already have it.
sea que ha Claro pues ya me lo he
removed is that if I didn't take it off, no
quitado es que si no me lo quitaba no
I was going to be able to follow the
iba a poder seguir el
straight [ __ ] dude
directo [__] macho tío
[ __ ]
[__]
Uncle I just did it anyway
tío Le acabo de hacer en fin
nothing neija that I have thrown at him I have done to him
nada neija que le he ech le le he hecho
case to one of
caso a a uno de
cryptocurrencies Oh
criptomonedas Ay
true Well it turns out that a long time ago I
verdad Pues resulta que hace tiempo yo
so much a song that was that
tanto una canción que era que la
stop her because she is a dangerous and evil woman
detengan que es una peligrosa malvada y
ambitious I can't control her
ambiciosa yo no la puedo controlar que
Arrest him, he stole my car.
lo detengan me ha robado la car por
Antonio Because they were the two people for
Antonio Porque eran las dos personas por
Antonio tells the two people that today I
Antonio dice las dos personas que hoy Yo
I don't remember that, but it's a shame
de eso no me acuerdo pero por [__]
I have to say this
esto lo tengo que decir
They exposed the voice and messages of a
expusieron la voz y mensajes de de una
person I think we all know it here
persona creo que aquí todos lo sabemos
No, here we all know what he was going for.
no aquí todos sabemos lo a lo que iba
bar of your house Antonio bar of your house
bar de tu casa Antonio bar de tu casa
because eh they had because it had happened
porque eh sa habían porque había pasado
what had happened to a goatherd with a
lo que había pasado un cabrero con una
YouTube call pm with Antonio called
YouTube llamada pm con Antonio llamado
Troy
ar de Troya
Well these people took it to Twitter.
bien esta gente lo lo llevó a Twitter lo
took as they already knew and did not know the
llevó como ya lo sabían y no sabían la
way to get it out they take this song and
forma de sacarlo cogen esta canción y
They start to say that Loli has returned
empiezan a decir que Loli vueltas ha
said things he has done things I don't know
dicho cosas que ha hecho cosas que no sé
what that he has threatened her that he is
qué que que la ha amenazado que está
scared Tania pm is not scared of
acojonada Tania pm no está acojonada de
none of the ways nor there are nor do I believe
ninguna de las maneras ni ni hay ni creo
that there is no one who can
que haya nadie que la pueda
scare is not scared at all
acojonar no es acojonada de ninguna de
dude, but he starts lying.
illo pero es que es que se pone a mentir
this way uncle
de esta forma tío
that she didn't threaten Tania how come she didn't
que ella no amenazó a Tania cómo que no
Loli Loli But what are you talking about if
Loli Loli Pero qué estás hablando si
we have seen the clas Here is the same
hemos visto los clas Aquí esta misma
late and says come on, throw it with all of you
tarde y le dice venga tira con todos tu
Chichi but Ah I'll load you after the
[__] pero Ah te cargo luego de las
consequences uncle really are are
consecuencias tío de verdad Son son
too much Oh I really did listen to him
demasiado Ay De verdad le he hecho caso
to one and why do I pay attention to him?
a uno y para qué le hago caso
Uncle, I've listened to one and why?
tío le he hecho caso a uno y para qué le
I pay attention
hago caso
really
de verdad
ah
ah
Claudia, don't worry, it doesn't happen.
Claudia tranquila no pasa
nothing What does Auri say? I read the sentence
nada Qué dice Auri leí la sentencia
around 2 in the morning I was left
sobre las 2 de la madrugada quedé
horrified all night chatting with
horrorizada toda la noche chateando con
another person we couldn't sleep like that
otra persona no podíamos dormir así
until it threatened until it dawned
hasta que amenazó hasta que amaneció es
tremendous is
tremendo es
tremendous is tremendous is tremendous
tremendo es tremendo es tremendo
Auri but it is
Auri pero es
terrifying is terrifying is of
terrorífico es terrorífico es de
movie of
película de
terror and that's it and here's a live one for you
terror y ya está y te aquí un directo la
colleague saying that she did not threaten
colega diciendo que ella no amenazó a
Tania that she sang that to Antonio
Tania que ella le cantó eso Antonio
ways Maybe this kind of people
maneras A lo mejor esta clase de gente
like the one in Corrillo has it
como la que hay en el Corrillo la ha
I could have tried to silence him
podido intentar intentar callarle la
mouth because it is the only thing these people
boca porque es lo único que esta gente
knows how to do is the only thing these people
sabe hacer es lo único que esta gente
knows how to do
sabe hacer
Hey, these people have a lot to do.
eh esta gente que tiene muchísimo que
to be very quiet than to be quiet And still the
callar muchísimo que callar Y todavía la
that will come to him And still those that will come to him
que le va a venir Y todavía las que le
They are coming, oh oh, they are going to put us
están por venir uy uy nos van a poner
demand Uy uy uy Loli and you when
demanda Uy uy uy Loli y tú cuándo
you pick up yours my
recoges la tuya mi
weapon Mira n 40 I said I was alone
arma Mira n 40 yo dije que estaba sola
for a reason because I had a
por un motivo porque yo me tuve un
message from someone very close to me where
mensaje de alguien muy levado a mí donde
He said to leave me alone and that and that
decía que me dejaran en paz y que y que
everything they were telling was a lie
todo lo que estaban contando era mentira
why and when I attacked Tania
porque y cuando yo ataqué a a Tania
Tania had no message when
Tania no tuvo ningún mensaje cuando
other channels attacked her nor did Tania have
otros canales la atacaron ni Tania tuvo
no one goes, goes, goes, goes, goes, goes
a nadie anda anda Anda anda Anda va
making it up as you go along you know
inventándose sobre la marcha sabes
Claudia Javi says those symptoms of
dice Claudia Javi esos síntomas del
Virgo sign, my husband already knows them.
signo Virgo ya los conozco mi marido
When something happens to him, something is wrong.
cuando le sale algo le pasa algo está de
I can't help it anymore, man. I'm bad.
mala ya no lo puedo evitar hombre estoy
very angry I'm in a bad mood yes I'm very
muy [__] estoy de mala sí estoy muy
pissed off But oh well, nothing happens.
[__] Pero bueno no pasa nada he
left atesa watching the issue that
dejado atesa vigilando el tema que
came out to say what for example to me
saliera a decir lo que por ejemplo a mí
In audio another person told me that you have
en audio me dijo otra persona te ha
answered baby was alone
contestado nene estaba sola
But at no time that kind of
Pero en ningún momento esa clase de
Solitude since if in the case that
Soledad ya que si en el caso de que
if what they are saying is true
fuera verdad eso que están diciendo
I wasn't alone either, baby. So, apate.
tampoco estaba sola nene Así que apate
hate cy hate un
hate cy hate un
cqui with this meacham morro Elisa Rivero
cqui con esto meacham morro Elisa Rivero
Hey, with Loli, does Loli come out and say this or not?
eh con Loli salga Loli a decir esto o no
Loli comes out to say nothing and fills the fridge
salga Loli a decir nada llenan la nevera
every month they are a channel of harassment are a
cada mes son un canal de acosar son un
channel that mistreats you psychologically
canal que te maltrata psicológicamente
to the level that they would make Palmas with the
al nivel de que harían Palmas con las
ears and would spend a year crushing
orejas y se tirarían un año machacando
pounding pounding if you did one
machacando machacando si tú hicieras una
nonsense would look to see if after
tontería mirarían a ver si después de
doing that nonsense has a higher level
hacer esa tontería tienen un nivel más
high can reach a higher level
alto pueden llegar a un nivel más lejos
They invent the owner of this channel
se inventan El señor dueño de este canal
has a complaint filed that is
tiene tiene una denuncia puesta que es
a complete falsehood a complete falsehood
toda una falsedad toda una falsedad
and man but but you have read it for what
y hombre pero pero la has leído por lo
less than that is all It is a falsehood And for
menos que es todo Es una falsedad Y por
what you haven't answered and why you are not
qué no has contestado y por qué no estás
person in the case
persona en la causa
But wait alanne look what she said
Pero espera alanne mira lo que ha dicho
the owner of this channel has me
el señor dueño de este canal tiene me
has a complaint filed that is all
tiene una denuncia puesta que es toda
a falsehood that we have a complaint against
una falsedad que le tenemos una denuncia
since it is a complete lie. Ah well.
puesta que es toda una falsedad Ah pues
nothing, I made the videos with
nada los vídeos los he hecho yo con
Artificial intelligence
Inteligencia artificial
uncle who is all the falsehood and the colleague
tío que es toda la falsedad y la colega
has not answered the
no ha contestado a la
demand And now
demanda Y ya
He is and he says this in public and he
está y esto lo dice en público y se
She remains so calm and that's it and in the
queda tan tranquila y y ya está y en el
the court does not present a complete falsehood
juzgado no se presenta toda una falsedad
And he really thinks I'm scared
Y se cree De verdad que estoy acojonada
But if it's a tip boy But don't you
Pero si es una propina chico Pero no te
you have realized that it is a simple
has dado cuenta de que es una simple
alms which in such a case that
limosnita lo que en tal caso de que
If everything went wrong, I had to give you Ah al
fuera todo mal te tenía que dar Ah al
Anne who is a little charity man because the
Anne que es una limosnita hombre pues la
It is true that we have asked him
verdad es que sí que le hemos pedido
little for what he has done
poco para lo que ha hecho
Of course, here he is telling you already.
Claro pues aquí te lo está diciendo ya
that I didn't care about him. Not showing up because the
que le di igual No personarse porque las
will pay what is prolonging the
va a pagar lo que está alargando el
time no no alanne if it is that here you already
tiempo no no alanne si es que aquí ya te
He is saying that the 15,000 euros that
lo está diciendo que los 15000 eur que
They are asked in the lawsuit that they will
se le piden en la demanda que los va a
pay and that's it, it's a little charity.
pagar y punto que es una limosnita te lo
He is already saying that he is going to pay for it. Well
está diciendo ya que lo va a pagar Pues
nothing Loli let's go let's do it
nada Loli vamos vamos haciendo la
second for the second alms because
segunda para la segunda limosnita porque
there is for a second and for a
hay para una segunda y para una
third for what you are going to have to
tercera para lo que tú vas a tener que
pay Ah for what I'm going to have to
pagar Ah para lo que yo voy a tener que
you and other people will have to pay
pagar vas a tener que pagar tú y gente
of your
de tu
herd that is a little lemon for what
manada que es una limonita para lo que
I'm going to have to pay Oh and now
yo voy a tener que pagar Ah y ahora al
I'm going to say in the end
final voy a decir
something you don't realize that I say
algo tú no te das cuenta de que yo digo
we are going to
vamos a
put it but anyway this is it
ponerlo pero de todas formas esto lo
We'll leave more for the end than
vamos a dejar más para el final que
Now we are with Tania Tania
ahora estamos con Tania Tania
Hey
eh
said the boy said Oh the LoL what
dijo el chico dijo Ay la LoL lo
threatened I don't know what on Twitter
amenazado no sé qué pues en Twitter
they started r that r that I don't know what that
empezaron r que r que no sé qué que
condemns that this that that the other
condena que esto que lo otro lo otro
come come come come come everything
venga venga venga venga venga todo
because they already knew it as well as himself
porque ellos ya lo sabían como el propio
Javi oliv that as from time to time the
Javi oliv que como de vez en cuando las
croquettes have to be made
croquetas se las tiene que estar
eating the croquettes carefully
comiendo car cadas las croquetas se las
is eating faces I don't know if they will be
va comiendo carad no sé si serán de
cod or chicken ham but the
jamón de bacalao o de pollo pero las
troquet that eats this this cer are
troquet que se come este este cer están
expired because at the time of
caducadas porque en el momento de se
says ja himself I already did
dice el propio ja Yo ya lo
I know I knew that the husband had one
sé yo sabía que el marido tenía una
condemn man as if you didn't leave him
condena hombre como que no lo dejaste tú
Of course what I didn't expect was that
claro lo que no me esperaba yo era esa
barbarity or rather the thing about having one
barbaridad o sea lo de que tenía una
condemnation you know what I believed that
condena sabéis lo que yo me creía que
I don't think I already said it here the other day
era No creo que ya lo dije aquí el otro
day I thought it was a sentence of
día yo creía que era una condena de
gender violence alone and you'll see
violencia de género solo y verás tú
When I say alone it's not to take away weight.
Cuando digo solo no es por quitarle peso
but of course it is that next to what it is
pero claro es que al lado de lo que es
actually not clear next to what
en realidad No claro al lado de lo que
It's actually nothing what I
en realidad no es nada la la lo que yo
I believed that it was a sentence of
me creía es que era una condena de
gender violence you know the good stuff
violencia de género sabes del palo bueno
is that gender violence can be
es que una violencia de género puede ser
from insults to harassment of a
desde unos insultos a un acoso a una
assault on support, you understand me?
agresión a una manutención me entiendes
Then I didn't know how serious it was.
Entonces no sabía de qué gravedad yo lo
what I thought was that it would be a sentence
que pensaba era que sería una condena
that for whatever reason he had had some
que por lo que sea había tenido unos
months in jail or some time in the
meses en la cárcel o algún tiempo en la
jail is worth it
cárcel vale
I was already thinking, [ __ ] why would you
em que ya pensaba yo [__] para que te
put in jail for violence
metan en la cárcel por violencia de
gender you must have done something very
género tienes que haber hecho algo muy
very very fat very very very fat because
muy muy gordo muy muy muy gordo porque
I have seen people who have done things
yo he visto a gente que ha hecho cosas
serious and have sentenced him to two years of
graves y le han condenado a dos años de
prison and he doesn't get in, do you understand me?
prisión y no entra me entiendes las
we have seen here on YouTube but of course
hemos visto aquí en YouTube pero claro
so that you go to jail or it is
para que entres en la cárcel o bien Es
that you have more background or that you have
que tienes más antecedentes o que has
done something
hecho algo
Pardiaco when I read that here in the
pardíaco cuando yo leí eso aquí en el
straight from the other day I was left
directo del otro día yo me quedé de
stone and when we were seeing more and
piedra y cuando fuimos viendo más y
we were seeing more I stayed before
fuimos viendo más yo me quedé antes de
yesterday of stone is that it is the worst thing that
ayer de de piedra es que es lo peor que
There may be. I think it is the
puede haber Es que yo creo que es el
worst crime I think it's the worst
peor delito Yo creo que es el peor
crime is the worst the worst There can be no
delito es lo peor lo peor No puede haber
nothing worse And
nada peor Y
still be What is the level of a
todavía sea Cuál es el nivel de un
people who get this so big and this
personas que sale esto tan gordo y esta
comes out to defend her the other comes out to
sale a defenderla el otro sale a
defend it also in Troy
defenderla también el la de Troya le
show your support a kiss Tania I don't know
muestran su apoyo un beso Tania no sé
that some on Twitter too and Tania
qué algunos en Twitter también y Tania
makes songs with intelligence
hace canciones con Inteligencia
artificial in front of those people we are
artificial ante esa gente estamos
family doesn't love me, they have to follow me
familia no a m a d tienen que yo sigo
with the pm He still dares to call yours
con la pm Aún se atreve a llamar a tus
followers of South American scum is that
seguidores gentuza de Sudamérica es que
It's all wrong with these people Javi cuo disgusting
es todo mal con esta gente Javi cuo asco
without words I hadn't fallen right?
sin palabras no había caído verdad no
I had fallen host man is that they are
había caído [__] tío es que son
too much eh that's all that's already
demasiado eh es que es todo es que ya
You're putting things together and they're coming to you.
vas hilando cosas ya se te van viniendo
things on your mind
cosas a la cabeza
Of course, Tamia is scared Tamia
Claro yce que tamia se acojonado tamia
She's not scared because I didn't even have one.
no está acojonada porque yo no tenía ni
[ __ ] idea of this that they have come up with a lie
[__] idea de esto que han sacado mentira
So Oliveira, you've thrown yourself
Entonces oliveira te has tirado la
pool but of the 10 Met and you have fallen of
piscina pero de los 10 Met y has cao de
small belly Because I didn't have a [ __ ]
barriga chico Porque yo no tenía ni [__]
idea of what you're doing, go on, go on
idea de esto que estáis anda Anda anda
Go Loli go go go Loli for God's sake
Anda Loli anda anda Anda Loli por Dios
Come on Loli, for God's sake, stop lying one day.
anda Loli por Dios deja de mentir un día
truly of your life my daughter that I have
de verdad de tu vida hija mía que tengo
Here are some conversations of yours about how
aquí Unas conversaciones tuyas de cómo
You tell Marta that you made up what she said.
le dices a Marta que te inventaste lo de
grenade to defend it And now you are
granada para defenderla Y ahora te estás
inventing that you were going to Troy
inventando que ibas para ar de Troya
Come on, did you threaten Tania? We saw everything.
anda amenazaste a Tania lo vimos todo lo
we saw it yesterday and we saw it again today
vimos ayer y lo hemos vuelto a ver hoy
I wasn't going to go to Troy you start
no iba para ar de Troya te pones a
tell him to pull, come on, pull with all your might
decirle tira venga tira con todo tu
Chichi, what you and your husband did and
[__] eh lo que hacías tú y tu marido y
What you have at home, go man for it
lo que tienes en casa anda hombre por
God taking out and juando and this is already had
Dios sacando y juando y esto ya se tiene
that you brake and how you are going to brake
que frenar y cómo se va a frenar voes
going tomorrow Friday to Palma where
yendo mañana viernes a Palma donde
We'll make a direct trip out to see a
haremos un directito fuera a a ver a un
lawyer a direct to go see the
abogado un directito para í a ver al
lawyer, I really mean we are
abogado yo de verdad o sea estamos
talking about child abuse eh
hablando de un abuso a menores eh
We are talking about child abuse
estamos hablando de un abuso a menores
that the girl was 11 years old
de de que la chiquilla tenía 11 años
until I was 15 and these people
hasta que tenía 15 y esta gente te
They respond with a song of
responden con una canción de
Intelligence
Inteligencia
artificial and this lady making a
artificial y esta señora haciéndose un
directly going to see a lawyer
directito yendo a ver a un abogado
when she has not hired a lawyer or
cuando ella no ha contratado abogado ni
for the
para el
yours before these people
suyo ante esta gente
We are advocating to take action now
estamos abogado para tomar medidas ya
plus one degree higher than what yes yes
más un grado más superior a lo que sí sí
one more degree, one more degree, much higher
un grado más un grado más muy superior
much higher but we have to go to a
muy superior más tenemos que ir a un
highest degree but not only that
grado más superior pero no solamente eso
but I intend to put you in touch with
sino que pienso ponerle en contacto con
taa
taña
PM to see what can be done with everything
PM para ver qué se puede hacer con todo
This is what can be done with everything
esto pu lo que se puede hacer con todo
This is asking for the right to
esto pedir el derecho al
forgetfulness is worth it if you have a little bit of
olvido vale si se tiene un poco de
shameful to ask for the right to be forgotten
vergüenza pedir el derecho al olvido
Ok, but since it doesn't have it, it will continue.
vale pero como no la tiene pues seguirá
and Iran is taking out more things because there are
e Irán sacando más cosas porque hay
many more things like it doesn't have it then
muchas más cosas como no la tiene pues
More things will come out because it is obtuse
Irán saliendo más cosas porque es obtusa
and he hits the wall against the
y se va dando contra la pared contra la
wall against wall what there is
pared contra la pared lo que hay
You're not going to freak out, you're going to freak out, huh, because
No vais a flipar Vais a flipar eh Porque
given because it is all It is the whole life of
dado porque es todo Es toda la vida de
her whole life is a show
ella toda la vida de ella es un show
spoken that I have it here we are going to
hablado que lo tengo aquí lo vamos a
put it we are going to take it directly in and he
poner lo vamos a [__] directo en y él
He has also spoken about matters of his
también ha hablado de asuntos es su
channel that is responsible for me
canal que es el responsable que a mí me
I don't give a damn about this [ __ ] channel
la suda me la sopla el canal este [__]
channel that if you want me to throw it away, let me
canal que si quiere que lo tire que me
I'm sweating so hard that I'm going to the other side
la suda que la sopla que me voy al otro
I'm going to cook. But what about this guy?
me voy a cocinar Pero que a este tío hay
that see the games and this guy is the
que verle los jugados y este tío es el
that he is playing with people that I
que está jugando con la gente a que yo
I want to see you in court Loli but what
te quiero ver en juzgado Loli pero que
go Of course you have to see me in the
vayas Claro que hay que verme en los
judged as if you have received the
juzgados como que te ha llegado la
notification and you have not appeared Claro
notificación y no te has personado Claro
that you have to see you have to see me in the
que hay que verte hay que verme en el
judged but sees but
juzgado pero ve pero
introduce yourself to others So then no
preséntate a los demás Así que luego no
come crying saying that you are
venga llorando diciendo que se está
playing with his work and his bread
jugando con su trabajo y con su pan
because that's the guy who's playing
porque es es Es el tío que está jugando
with bread, work and people
con el pan el trabajo y y las personas
close to others So I Loli
allegadas a los demás Así que yo Loli
Huertas I think what came out in the
huertas creo que lo que salió en la
sixth and her stalker is a fake plot
sesta y su acosador es una falsa tramada
for him to get more followers that
por él para conseguir más seguidores eso
This is what I think about the views
es lo que yo pienso a las vistas a
views that this gentleman is hammering
vistas de que este señor está machacando
I live alone because he approached everyone
vivo solo porque é se acercó a todo el
that is approaching and we have confirmed it
que se acerca y lo tenemos comprobado
which is to everyone who approaches and you go
que es a todo el que se acerca y las vas
you have to pay them but they last
a pagar las tienes que pagar pero duras
By not paying a tip, the tip will be given to you.
No pagando una propin la propin Te la
you can stick it in your ass and not screw it up
puedes meter en el culo y no cagarla en
a week to see if they stop you, there is no need
una semana a ver si te paren no hay que
we have to put an end to this, we have to do it
hay que terminar con esto hay que hacer
that people like Mr. Javier Oliveira
que gente como el señor Javier oliveira
can't do what he does on a channel
no puede hacer lo que hace en un canal
because I come in here warm I see a
porque yo entro aquí calentita veo una
photo and I tell a person Loli Yo
foto y le digo a una persona Loli Yo
I think you don't fit in warm because
creo que tú calentita no entras Porque
you see a
veas un
twit put body I think you're coming
twit puesto cuerpo Yo creo que tú vienes
warm from the
calentita del
Mercadona, the [ __ ] mother who gave birth to you
mercadona la [__] madre que os parió a
Blessed Christ and the [ __ ] mother that I
Cristo bendito y la [__] madre que me
gave birth I also curse everything
parió A mí también me cago en todo lo
that you have been harassed and humiliated
que se meea que habéis acosado humillado
said that I have mistreated my mother that
dicho que he maltratado a mi madre que
You've said everything and there's the aunt
habéis dicho de todo y ahí está la tía
This fresh from the line saying that if there is
esta fresca de la lne diciendo que si ha
said to get off, he gets off
dicho que se baje que se baja los
pants to [ __ ] her that's it
pantalones para que se la follen eso es
lie compose the clique I do it
mentira componer el clique yo sí lo
I have abnormalities And you will see that in
tengo anormales Y eso lo Vais a ver en
a trial
un juicio
is worth a trial in which you are not going to
vale un juicio en el que no te vas a
present cowardly that You will see in
presentar cobarde eso lo Vais a ver en
the [ __ ] scammers trial of the
el [__] juicio estafadores de la
justice you are [ __ ] scammers
justicia sois unos [__] estafadores de
you are playing with justice
la justicia estáis jugando con las
families you are playing with people
familias estáis jugando con la gente
you are harassing you are distorting
estáis acosando estáis distorsionando
You are now Javi I said that I
estáis Ahora sí Javi yo dije que me
I felt blackmailed and that you wanted me to
sentía extorsionada y que queríais que
to cover my mouth and stay in a
que me tapara la boca y me quedara en un
corner and here I am at the end of the year
rincón y aquí me tenéis al cabo del año
Javier Oliveira, here I am with everyone.
Javier oliveira aquí me tienes con todos
the videos saved there here
los vídeos ahí guardaditos aquí me
You have Javier at the end of the year but it is
tienes al cabo del año Javier pero es
that you are of no use to me here. You are of no use to me, Loli.
que yo aquí no me sirves De nada Loli es
that you have a claim and you have to go
que tienes una demanda Y tienes que ir
to the court and you don't go but what do you
al juzgado y no vas pero es que qué te
you are acting brave in front of
estás haciendo la valiente delante de
These three crazy people who see you
estos tres locos que te ven que
Surely 200 will be slum dwellers from here
seguramente 200 serán villeros de aquí
to see what he says and what he gives you
para ver lo que dice y lo que te da por
I say what I want out of my mouth
solta por la boca yo lo que que quiero
that you go to court, not that you yell at me
que vayas al juzgado no que me chilles
from there yes from there we already have a
desde ahí si desde ahí ya tenemos un
lots of videos that are in the
montón de vídeos que que están en el en
the court in 2026 we have the trial
el juzgado el 2026 tenemos el juicio
You have time to show up if you want.
tienes tiempo a personarte si quieres yo
I'm not in a hurry, we'll give you one
no tengo prisa te vamos a poner una
second no, I think that with this no longer
segunda no yo creo que con esto no ya
look and it cannot be allowed, I have never
mira y no se puede consentir yo jamás he
done all that they say because
hecho todo eso Que ellos dicen la porque
It turns out that they are so extremely
resulta que son tan sumamente
Hey, bad guys who get caught in Malada get
eh malos que se cogen en malada se ponen
five are put to
cinco se ponen a
five people get sick and start crying
malada se ponen cinco se ponen a llorar
because the miniature said that the body
porque la miniatura dicho que el cuerpo
It may be your mother's but you haven't
puede ser de su madre pero no habéis
watched the hundred or so videos with
visto los ciento y pico vídeos con
thumbnails and everything that has been said there
miniaturas y todo lo que se ha dicho ahí
to go out and say hey stop that hasn't been done
para salir y decir eh stop eso no lo ha
no one has seen it or are you the ones who
visto nadie o es que sois esos que los
I will keep behind And you will give him
mantendré por detrás Y le daréis
audience to be able to continue doing
audiencia para poder seguir haciendo
blood these channels have to be
sangre estos canales se tienen que
These channels have to be finished
terminar estos canales tienen que jarse
This has to change the theme of
este se tiene que cambiar la temática de
to be able to say, hey, you messed with me
poder decir eh yo te has metido con mi
with u u Uy uy uy uy uy uy but not to me
con u u Uy uy uy uy uy uy pero no a mí a
where do they have that this crime is from
donde tienen que este delito es de
Donald Trump has already done so
prisión permanente Donald Trump ya lo
He said the other day and so much and so much
dijo el otro día y tanto y tantísimo
especially my minor and I will go to you and
sobre todo menor mío y te voy a irir y
I'm going to break your face, they're going to blow you up
te voy a partir la cara te van a volar
the pu layer and that he ASSUMES But you are
la capa pu y que él ASUME Pero tú eres
silly boy but you are silly I tell you
tonto niño pero que tú eres tonto yo te
I swear that tomorrow I'm going to go, let's go
juro que yo mañana voy a ir parte vamos
to do a live show from here and I'm going to
a hacer un directo dde aquí y voy a
ask to be contacted
pedir que se pongan en contacto con
Tania and I don't know what they will advise us if
Tania y no sé lo que nos aconsejarán si
together with the family or in conjunction
en conjunto con lo de familia o en por
separately what Loli is going to advise you
separado lo que os van a aconsejar Loli
When they hear you, it won't be a no go
cuando te escuchen no va a ser un no va
to be a lawyer's minute is going to be
a ser una minuta de abogado va a ser
another thing but I'm telling you I'm telling you
otra cosa pero te lo digo te lo digo te
I say you've made a mistake boy you've
lo digo te has equivocado chico te has
wrong and I am here silent in my
equivocado y yo estoy aquí callada en mi
cooking and laughing and you're on Twitter
cocina y riéndome y estáis en Twitter
saying that if it was me who did it
diciendo que si he sido yo la que lo ha
taken out that if I have been the one who has done it
sacado que si he sido yo la que lo ha
taken out and in the end ends up finding
sacado y al final termina encontrando
that which he will surely have offered to you
eso que seguro que se lo habrá ofrecido
to someone and
a alguien y
ends up hanging that which hangs
termina colgando eso que cuelga
No, this channel has to stop.
no esto se tiene que parar este canal no
He is super short, he is very tiny
es es super bajito es muy chiquitito
but I have given you food, I have not given you anything
pero te ha dado de comer no te he dado
what a [ __ ] shame Mr. Javier Oliveira no
[__] vergüenza señor Javier oliveira no
I have caused you a [ __ ] shame
te he daado una [__] vergüenza
mind-blowing to have to rely on LoL
alucinante tener que depender del LoL
Huertas And as Alarm said in that live broadcast
huertas Y como dijo alarm en ese directo
not having pain if Loli doesn't come back to you
no tener pema si Loli vuelta no te
name no Loli I would be ashamed
nombra no Loli me daría vergüenza
defending child abuse That would give me
defender un abuso a menores Eso me daría
You're not ashamed of yourself
vergüenza no te da una [__] vergüenza
that you can't go out on the street because
que no puedas salir a la calle porque
you are ridiculous sir I can't go out to the
eres ridículo señor no puedo salir a la
street that I can't go out to the street
calle que no puedo salir a la calle yo
I am the one who cannot go out on the street
soy el que no puede salir a la calle los
who will not be able to go out on the street are
que no van a poder salir a la calle son
those who are defending this that are not
los que están defendiendo esto que no
I'm going out to the street Loli are you
voy a salir a la calle Loli estás
saying while defending what
diciendo mientras que defiendes lo que
You are defending Loli that you have
estás defendiendo Loli que te has
invented a cancer to stir up our
inventado un cáncer para atizar noos que
you started saying that you had one
te has puesto a decir que tenías una
lung surgery while you
operación de pulmón mientras que te
They removed the cancer at the same time that you
quitaban el cáncer a la vez que te
They operated on your chest and you put on one
operaban el pecho y te ponías una
prosthesis what are you going to talk about shame
prótesis qué vas a hablar de vergüenza
Loli
Loli
what are you going to talk about
qué vas a hablar de
shame that you were talking to yourself
vergüenza que te estabas hablando hace
little again with a lady that you
poco otra vez con una señora a la que tú
You yourself explained why he had been
mismo expusiste porque se le había
forgotten to donate 240 miserable euros that
olvidado donar 240 miserables euros que
collected in a live with a victim
recolectó en un directo con una víctima
with a relative who is a victim of cancer, aunt
con un familiar víctima de cáncer tía
What are you going to talk about shame, daughter?
Qué Vais a hablar de vergüenza hija
mine if you had shame you would have
mía si tuvieres vergüenza hubieres
plating You already do a lot you are a
chapado Ase ya un montón usted es un
Ridiculous Ed very
ridículo Ed muy
ridiculous what you did to Tania
ridículo lo que habéis hecho con Tania
pn that no longer has a name or anything like that
pn eso ya no tiene ni nombre ni nada eso
you have to go where you have to go and
ya tiene que ir donde tiene que ir y
this tomorrow morning From there
esto mañana por la mañana Desde allí
I will do a live stream and give the data that
haré un directo y daré los datos que
I only have the phone so that it is
solo tengo el teléfono para que se
Get in touch and see what we can do
pongan en contacto y a ver qué se puede
do because this can no longer be done
hacer porque esto ya no se puede
bear because this can no longer be done
soportar porque esto ya no se puede
hold on because what you can do is
aguantar pues lo que se puede hacer es
ask for the right to be forgotten Loli that is
pedir el derecho al olvido Loli eso es
what can be done with the tanas
lo que se puede hacer con los de tanas
If you don't want them to tell you because the
si no quiere que se lo digan porque los
Tanas will obviously tell you
de tanas se lo van a decir evidentemente
always on the internet alone for
siempre en internet solas para
gentlemen, this channel should always be
siempre señores este canal debería estar
already reported to those people who have
denunciado ya con esa gente que le ha
cattle reported and closed closed for
ganado denunciado y cerrado cerrado para
that he learns where that is to say that the channel
que aprenda donde que o sea que el canal
should be closed for telling you yet
debería estar cerrado por decirle aún
notes I don't remember what they were
notas no me acuerdo Cuáles eran los
Johan's insults, I don't remember
insultos de Johan pl no me acuerdo
what were they but that you give the black eye
cuáles eran pero que te p el ojo morado
that you [ __ ] I don't know how much something like that and
que te follado no sé cuánto algo así y a
the other hair broom that this channel
la otra pelo escoba que este canal
It should be closed. For that reason and yours.
debería estar cerrado Por eso y el tuyo
So Loli, your thing is played
entonces Loli lo tuyo de jugado de
[Laughs]
[Risas]
family guard by the way I'm going to go
guardia familia por cierto voy a ir
opening the chat now ok I'm going to open
abriendo ahora el chat vale voy a abrir
Now I open the chat, okay? But still.
ahora abro el chat vale Pero igualmente
You can become a member, it won't happen
os podéis hacer miembrillo que no pasa
They have nothing, the pot, don't put the [ __ ]
nada tienen la olla no pongan la [__]
Okay, I would have to learn not to be so
vale tendría que aprender a no ser tan
so
tan
a stalker is a stalker who takes people
acosador es un acosador lleva a la gente
Loli, I can't get to the madness, I can't get to you
al al desquicio no consigue Loli yo a ti
It doesn't drive you crazy, you come like this
no te lleva al desquicio tú vienes así
a challenge because you didn't get it you know
un reto porque no lo conseguiste sabes
Why Because those who are by your side
por qué Porque los que están a tu lado
They are as much like you as you have to give it to
son tan como tú hay que darle al
objective and to make and fulfill the objective
objetivo y hacer y cumplir el objetivo
not what one wants
no lo que uno le dé la gana
No, well, I'll be there. Hey, but look, look.
No pues yo ya estaré Oye pero mira mira
look look look look look like like
mira mira mira mira mira como como
finish the thing I was not going to do this
termina la cosa yo este no iba a
answer no one I answer this
contestar a nadie le contesto a esto
because this is something that Loli says that
porque esto es un que dice Loli que
We did not reach the goal because
nosotros no llegamos al objetivo porque
you are some
ustedes sois unos
suckers who never reach the goal
pardillos que nunca llegamos al objetivo
because you are some suckers who have to
porque sois unos pardillos que hay que
hit the target button let's see
darle al botón de objetivo a ver voy a
set a I'm going to set a goal of 10
poner un voy a poner un objetivo de 10
super chat
super chat
from 2 euros for 30 minutes and
a partir de 2 eur durante 30 minutos y
and the objective is going to be sasca to
el y el objetivo va ser sasca a
Lolis okay okay There you have it now
Lolis vale vale Ahí os aparece ahora el
target and Lolis says that you have to
objetivo y dice Lolis que le tenéis que
press the objective button to complete it
dar al botón de objetivo para cumplirlo
Okay, and on the way I'm going to remove the the
vale Y ya de camino voy a quitar el el
member mode and I open it to all of you
modo miembro y os Lo abro a todos
Okay, there you have the objective, okay.
vale por ahí tenéis el objetivo vale
You have half an hour to complete
tenéis media hora para cumplir
who says that you are some who said this
que dice que sois unos qué ha dicho esto
This is not a YouTube channel, this is a
no es un canal de YouTube esto es un
channel of a convicted criminal
canal de un delincuente condenado
condemned already condemned after I already
condenado ya condenado después yo ya
I will be condemned or not I don't know
estaré condenada o no No lo
We know that this channel is a criminal
sabemos que este canal Es un delincuente
convicted no no no no a criminal is
condenado no no no no un delincuente es
What you defend, Loli, is a lawsuit
lo que tú defiendes Loli una demanda
A civilian is not a criminal. It is that
civil no es un delincuente es Es que
Someone asks you for money and I ask you
alguien te pide pasta y a mí me
They sentenced you to 0 euros, let's see which one you put in.
condenaron a 0 eur a ver cuá te lo metes
in the little head
en la cabecita
but he's already telling you, he's already telling you
pero ya te va diciendo ya te va diciendo
Well, they will condemn me or not. I already know.
Bueno a mí me condenarán o no Ya lo
We'll see, he's already been convicted of defamation.
veremos ya está condenado por difamación
no and this is a channel that doesn't stop you from
no y este es un canal que no para que no
stop having me in your mouth that doesn't stop
para de tenerme en su boca que no para
that the day I stopped entering your
que el día que dejé de entrar en su
channel I will face it alive that must have a
canal me lo caré vivo que debe tener un
someone inside who doesn't let him live or
alguien dentro que no lo deja vivir ni
breathing is that it doesn't stop anywhere
respirar es que no para en ningún lado
nowhere anywhere
en ningún sitio en ningún
channel does not stop I am your day I am your night and
canal no para soy su día Soy su noche y
I am your dawn so clear it doesn't stop
soy su madrugada así de claro no para
Mr. Javier, look at you and your gentleman.
seor Javier mira usted y su señor
lawyer have asked for my data in such a way
letrado han pedido mis datos de tal
the way they have come to have to
forma que han llegado a tener que
set up a security camera and record
ponerse cámara de seguridad y grabado
The Boys testifying at a police station
Los Chicos testificando en una comisaría
because they were there Oh Loli What an invention
de por estaban allí Ay Loli Vaya invent
a kiss
un beso
CP I have authorization to put
CP yo tengo autorización para poner
These are these images of a house with
estasa estas imágenes de una casa con
a security camera where they approach
una cámara de seguridad donde se acercan
your people because they watch your channel What's up
su gente porque ve su canal Qué está
What are you doing with your community, sir?
haciendo usted con su comunidad señor
Javier will smell what the hell he's doing.
Javier olira qué [__] está haciendo
You have taken the machine gun and want
usted ha cogido la metralleta y quiere
take them all down or is it below you?
cargárselos a todos o tiene por debajo
someone like Eh To whom paying a
alguien comoas Eh Al cual pagándole un
A little money can make jobs easier for you, huh?
dinerito puede facilitarle trabajos eh
Sir, you are paying me a little money.
señor qu Tas pagándome un dinerito me
It may be that this lady does not even know
puede es que esta señora no se sabe ni
There's no one at the wheel, a kiss
es que no hay nadie al volante un beso
Look Loli, they're giving you a hard time over there.
Mira Loli por ahí te están dando un
little bit of squit look with love
poquito de squit mira con amor
iron you are pressing the objective button
irón le estáis dando al botón objetivo
you have been able to do it is that Loli says
habéis sabido hacerlo es que Loli dice
No, you weren't going to know. Look, Loli.
que no que no ibais a saber Mira Loli
there are fulfilling the
por ahí están cumpliéndose el
you have the objective for the objective Ed
objetivo lo tiene usted por el obtivo Ed
the privilege of having all the
el privilegio de tener toda la
private and personal information of a
información privada y personal de una
person just because he takes someone and
persona solo porque coge a alguien y le
p four duros like some dmos I don't know what
p cuatro duros como unos dmos no sé qué
that to have the privilege of
que las para tener el privilegio de
have all the data You are mixing it up
tener todos los datos Está mezclando es
that you are not understanding it
que ustedes no lo estáis entendiendo
This madness has just lost its steering wheel
esta locura acaba de perder el volante
completely, that is, he goes in a car
completamente o sea va va en un coche
no steering wheel and no brake right now
sin volante y sin un freno ahora mismo
Loli Loli what is mixing is that
Loli Loli lo que está mezclando es que
You will have heard somewhere what
habrá escuchado en alguna parte lo que
left Dallas trying to find out
salió de Dallas intentando averiguar
who was ouf who offered money and
quién era ouf que ofreció dinero y
So Loli is mixing that up with me.
entonces Loli está mezclando eso conmigo
with which I have paid Dallas for
con que yo le he pagado a Dallas para
have her data I don't know she is she is
tener los datos de ella no sé está está
making their 4 o'clock medley
haciendo su popurr de de las 4 de la
Afternoon goal for the Lolis kiss Pili
tarde objetivo para la Lolis beso Pili
Beautiful Carmen, 10 bucks, I appreciate it.
guapa Carmen 10 pavos te la agradezco
but but they have to be two if not no
pero pero tienen que ser de dos si no no
count For the
cuentan Para el
objective the objective How is the family going
objetivo el objetivo Cómo va familia
but they don't have to love me. I'm
pero no a m a d tienen que Estoy
poisoned by the chocolate
intoxicada por el chocolate de la
snack and thank goodness it was without
merienda y menos mal que ha sido Sin
churos Face twisting with laughter
churos Cara revolviéndose de la risa
rolling with laughter
revolviéndose de la risa cara
rolling around with laughter is saying
revolviéndose de la ris está diciendo
that I have paid someone to
que yo le he pagado a alguien para
get your data And it's like lady
obtener sus datos Y es como señora le
We asked for your information because you said that
pedimos sus datos Porque usted dijo que
for the claim that they ask me for the data I
para la demanda que pedirme los datos yo
I'll give it to you and then you [ __ ] yourself
os lo doy yo te lo y luego te cagaste
with the
con la
demand do this Loli
demanda comete esto Loli
zasca Hey, but how far is the goal?
zasca Oye pero Cuánto falta el objetivo
not yet fulfilled were 10
no cumplido todavía eran 10
there were only 10, just one kiss
solamente eran 10 solamente un beso
handsome pendo the crime that you know is
guapos pendo el delito que usted sabe es
That's a [ __ ] fascist crime to face
eso es un [__] delito fasca para cara
crying with laughter face crying with laughter
llorando de risa cara llorando de risa
they have been so extremely sneaky
hab sido tan sumamente rastreros
disgusting and so so extremely habis
asquerosos y tan tan sumamente habis
fallen to the lowest point that exists
caído a lo más bajo que existe una
person who has to be there every day
persona eh de estar todos los días
making videos on all channels
haciendo vídeos en todos los canales
lying and you think you're going to come
mintiendo y tú te crees que vas a venir
to laugh at a Ju and for me to give you one
a reírte de un Ju y y a que yo te dé una
limit yourself because you are going to tell yourself that it is going to happen to you
limita pues te vas a c ir queo te va a
biting in the ass and knocking down hosts
cer por el trasero y tumbando hostias
Well Loli, I disagree. I think you're going to
bueno Loli yo discrepo yo creo que s vas
to pay in the first place because you have not
a pagar en primer lugar porque no te has
presented to the trial is worth Reyes Mayi a
presentado al juicio vale Reyes Mayi un
kiss first of all because you haven't
beso en primer lugar porque no te has
appeared in the lawsuit. Okay then.
personado en la demanda Vale entonces
that's why you're already in Rebellion then. Okay.
eso ya estás en Rebeldía entonces Bueno
there I already believe that I believe that this first
ahí yo ya creo que creo que esta primera
demand if you're going to pay it Loli I think
demanda si la vas a pagar Loli creo que
If you are not going to pay for it, luck is on you.
si no la vas a pagar la suerte para ti
It's that we have asked you for little but of course
es que te hemos pedido poco pero claro
As you continue there will be a second lawsuit
como sigues habrá una segunda demanda el
next year that I am the least
año que viene que yo es que lo que menos
to review everything he has said
de poner a revisar todo lo que ha dicho
throughout this year for the second claim
en todo este año para la segunda demanda
the
la
true But the obo but it has not been
verdad Pero el obo pero no se ha
the objective has been achieved yet but hey
cumplido el objetivo todavía pero Oye
but not
pero no
you stop but how long is it until the
paráis pero Cuánto falta para el
objective has been passed already
objetivo se ha pasado Ya
No, you're not Loli.
no Loli eres
pathetic Loli I think they gave you a
penosa Loli creo que te han dado un
little Sas to my followers
pequeño Sas a mis seguidores
but they don't stop
pero no paran no
stop Loli It seems to me that they have a
paran Loli Me parece que te han un
little
pequeño
squillo in
squillo en
march
marcha
he
el
[Music]
[Música]
I don't promise you that I haven't done it
no os prometo que no lo he hecho a
purpose for which
propósito para que
I promise myself that I haven't done it
me prometo que no lo he hecho a
purpose for you to give me super chat
propósito para que me dierais super chat
Hey, I'm going to show you what it is.
eh os lo voy a enseñar lo que ha
past
pasado
pass the Dallas that doesn't even know who he is
pas el Dallas que no sabe ni quién es
Loli will know if she knows it.
Loli si lo sabrá si lo
You know, I promise you that this is not for me.
sabrá os prometo que esto no me va
man [ __ ] I want to show you something and
tío [__] os quiero enseñar una cosa y
not me
no me
comes out Dedicated to LoL chiscar
sale Dedicado para LoL chiscar
turning from the
revolviéndose de la
laugh okay eh what happened is the
risa vale eh lo que ha pasado es lo
next family I promise you that there has not been
siguiente familia os prometo que no ha
It was on purpose, I promise you it hasn't
sido a propósito eh os prometo que no ha
been on purpose to ask for The Super
sido a propósito para pedir Los Super
chat
chat
Hey, you see, I'm still intoxicated, what happens is
eh ves tú sigo intoxicado lo que pasa es
that B does not laugh at the expensive laughter
que no le B riéndose de la risa cara
rolling with laughter
revolviéndose de la risa cara
rolling with laughter I put it
revolviéndose de la risa lo he puesto
but I haven't pressed the button what do I do?
pero no le he dado al botón qué hago le
I am not very embarrassed yes no but not to
doy de poca vergüenza sí no pero no a
Loli changed her mind
aen Loli cambi de
supermarket let's see It's that the beer from
supermercado a ver Es que la cerveza del
Mercadona, come on, I'm going to start it.
mercadona venga le voy a dar a iniciar
goal to sack for the Loli It has been
objetivo para sacap para la Loli Se ha
An error occurred and it tells me: Oh well.
producido un error me dice Ah pues
then yes I have given it to him But it has been
entonces sí le he dado Pero se ha
an error has occurred, they have to take
producido un error tienen que toma
dove face smiling with eyes
palomita cara sonriendo con ojos
smiling face smiling with eyes
sonrientes cara sonriendo con ojos
smiling is that I can't wait for it
sonrientes es que no me sale espera lo
I'm going back to
voy a volver a
attempt
intentar
No Loli, take it for yourself
no Loli toma para ti
wait
esperar
wait for olona everything is for the cause
esperar para olona todo sea por la causa
all my support FJ
todo mi apoyo FJ
Oliveira now comes out a kiss Rosita Who
oliveira ahora sale un beso Rosita Quién
It has been a kiss from the target of the cause
ha sido Del objetivo de la causa un beso
now now now
ahora ahora ahora
s because this already exceeds all the
s porque esto ya supera todos los
all levels that I limit you, then
niveles todos que yo te una limita pues
you're going to go, he's going to hit you in the ass and
te vas a ir te va a cer por el trasero y
knocking down hosts kid and the other one no longer
tumbando hostias chaval y la otra ya no
I tell you nothing And the other one I won't tell you anymore
te digo nada Y la otra ya no te digo
nothing the recipe does not lie here
nada la receta no se acuesta aquí la
recipe may lie in Seville
receta puede que se acuesta en Sevilla
because this is already beyond all levels
porque esto ya supera todos los niveles
all levels
todos los niveles
all all levels beat this
todos todos los niveles supera esto
sir, forget it
señor olvídese
You disgust me a lot, but not me.
mucho asco que me das pero no a m Yo no
I know what kind of people can follow
sé qué clase de gente puede seguir
seeing this kind of people in
viendo a esta clase de de de gente en
Seriously I don't know what kind of people can
serio No lo sé qué clase de gente puede
keep watching this garbage, this story
seguir viendo esta basura esta hisoria
I understand you, consolation, listen to me, that you
me entiend consuelo escúchame que te
I understand perfectly. There I go.
entiendo perfectamente Ahí te voy a
leave Wait Wait that this is it
dejar Espérate Espérate que que esto es
a brushstroke of what I'm going to put now
una pincelada lo que voy a poner ahora
Mr. Ol This is a brushstroke for Loli
señor ol Esta es una pincelada para Loli
and I'm going to put you on the deel channel for a
y te voy a poner en el canal deel por un
reason why I'm not going to look for yours
motivo porque al tuyo no voy a buscarlo
because I
porque me
It disgusts me, I'm afraid to think that this
repugna tengo miedo pensar que este
Sir is a friend of a Tardas Queas
señor es amigo de un tardas queas
I can't believe what I'm feeling
no me lo puedo creer lo que estoy
listening to me with escape Loli Thanks
escuchando yo con escapar Loli Gracias
beautiful you are listening to what is
guapísima estáis escuchando lo que está
saying that he is afraid that I am
diciendo que tiene miedo que yo soy
friend of a guy named Dallas who pays people
amigo de un tal Dallas que paga la gente
to obtain the
para obtener los
data I can't no
datos no puedo no
I can start over again crying face
puedo Volvemos a empezar cara llorando
laughing face crying laughing face
de risa cara llorando de risa cara
crying with laughter already feels fear I
llorando de risa ya se siente miedo Yo
I already feel scared and it's not a
ya me siento atemorizada y no es una
joke to think that this
broma pensar que este
sir but they don't have to listen to me
señor pero no a m a d tienen que Oye
but the objective is no longer met
pero no se cumple ya el objetivo
Damn, but it hasn't been fulfilled yet.
[__] pero no se ha cumplido todavía el
target has been made ethno is not
objetivo se ha hecho etno no está
talking about mitilin
hablando de mitilin
Yes, Oscar Dominguez says what is happening is serious.
Sí dice Óscar Domínguez es grave lo que
He tells you, but I'm already at this height.
te dice pero es que yo ya está altura Va
for you Loli c there Loli Look at the people the
por ti Loli c allá Loli Mira la gente el
Sasca that is giving you daughter that they have
sasca que te está dando hija que han
exceeded the target three times
sobrepasado el objetivo tres veces
because we had to repeat it, daughter
porque lo hemos tenido que repetir hija
that you are not the only one who knows how to give it to
que no eres la única que sabe darle al
Super chat button
botón de Super chat
Loli says Pili is accusing you
Loli dice Pili te está acusando un
crime eye has not accused me of 28
delito ojo no me ha acusado de 28
crimes this year has put me
delitos lo que lleva de año me ha puesto
of all that there was to have put
de todo lo habido por haber puesto
He has put everything on me above but not
arriba me ha puesto a mí de todo pero no
to me and with the complaint of what
a mí a d tien y con la denuncia de qué
fas escape for
fas escap para
Loli if you are a simple in letter
Loli si tú eres un simple en letrado
when he's here he's a simple [ __ ]
cuando está aquí es un simple [__]
criminal just like
delincuente igual que
They are calling him a criminal every time
ellos le está diciendo delincuente cada
Spanish but not me where they have
español pero no a mí a donde tienen
that God Pili But that is what is clear So
que Dios Pili Pero eso qué es claro Así
It is as it is with those numbers, of course.
está como está con esos números Claro
insulting me, humiliating me without knowing
insultándome humillándome sin saber de
where that guy came from without even knowing who
dónde salía ese tío sin saber ni quién
It's really disgusting to hear it.
es eh con mucho asco que da escucharlo
because he is a lawyer of this kind
porque es un señor en letrado de esta
people who only know how to humiliate and disrespect
gente que solo sabe humillar y faltar el
respect for women
respeto a las mujeres a las mujeres
women Hey but when does it end when
mujeres Oye pero cuándo se acaba cuándo
the [ __ ] thing is over
se acaba el [__]
objective aru a kiss ar rutrum Where
objetivo aru un beso ar rutrum Dónde
is serene
está serene
Uncle: Hey, self-criticism, but you don't let me.
tío Oye autocrítica pero no me dejáis
Hey, I'm going to give you another goal now.
eh os voy a poner otro objetivo ahora
higher Eh Francisco Javier oliveira Te
más alto Eh Francisco Javier oliveira Te
We want a self-critical kiss, gorgeous
queremos un beso autocrítica guapísima
I'm going to give you an adjective now.
os voy a poner ahora un adjetivo os voy
to set a higher goal now, eh
a poner ahora un objetivo más alto eh
Because now you want us to see what
Porque ahora querréis que veamos lo de
Peppa no and others no now you will want
la Peppa no y demás no ahora querréis
that he sees the Peppa thing, not the
que vea lo de la Peppa no la
the PPPA's reply to that of Troy
contestación de la pppa al de Troya
no also no also you will want that
no también no también lo V a querer que
let's see it
lo veamos
No, but I don't have to go to the second one.
no pero no a m a tien que va el segundo
Chile, you don't play with this community.
con esta comunidad no se juega chile
spicy now we're going to put another one
picante ahora vamos a poner otro
target eh I'm going to give you 50 bucks
objetivo eh os lo voy a poner 50 pavos
What do you think is the objective met or not?
qué os parece se cumple o no objetivo de
super chat no there no I'm not going to do it
super chat de no ahí no no lo voy a lo
I'm going to put 100 bucks, that's it
voy a poner de 100 pavos ya está hasta
On Monday we won't see each other anymore.
el lunes ya no nos vemos más por
Here Alberto was handsome, but not to two
aquí Alberto guapo era de dos pero no a
Ti Loli recipe for breakfast sangria
ti Loli receta para desayunar sangría se
makes with two bottles of bozca one
hace con con dos botellas de bozca una
mandarin and two teaspoons of wine
mandarina y dos cucharaditas de vino
Delicious red wine, a kiss Alberto Well no
tinto riquísimo un beso Alberto Pues no
I know if that one will suit him very well.
sé si le va a sentar muy bien ese
breakfast to the woman to see at least
desayuno a la mujer a ver por lo menos
gets up gets up well
se levanta se levanta bien
burning clear
ardiente claro
having received a Dangar, I entered the prison that
pingado un dangar entro en la cárcel que
King is out who the [ __ ] does he think he is
Rey está fuera quién [__] se cree
Who the [ __ ] thinks he's more than just a
quién [__] se cree más que más que un
sad a
triste un
sad because he said that Urdangarin
triste porque ha dicho que urdangarin
He entered prison and the king stayed
entró en la cárcel y el rey se quedó
that was what has come from what has already been said
fuera eso que ha venido de qu ya ya le
lost to the thread goes the 2nd degree
perdido hasta el hilo va el 2s grados
dove face smiling with eyes
palomita cara sonriendo con ojos
smiling Oh
sonrientes Ay
that he is going to pay, that he is going to pay
que que las va a pagar que lo va a pagar
that I'm going to pay it, they don't even have to
que lo voy a pagar ae tienen que ni te
We didn't leave you nor will we leave you a kiss I know that
dejamos ni te dejaremos un beso Ya lo sé
self-criticism, I know, a kiss, beautiful. But
autocrítica ya lo sé un beso guapa Pero
I do have to go to this trial myself.
yo si tengo que ir a este juicio yo
I need someone to protect me
necesito a alguien que me proteja a mí
I'm going to inform the court about these people.
esta gente yo voy a informar al juzgado
of everything that these people from the Ya do
de todo lo que hace esta gente de los Ya
start to rave but not to mad
empezar a desvariar pero no a m a d
They have to kiss him already started to
tienen que besos el se ya empezado a
rave
desvariar
I don't feel sorry for these people and that I
no siento de esta gente y de que yo
I feel afraid afraid of this
siento miedo miedo de esta
These people are scary and they are not a
gente da miedo esta gente y no es una
Joke, I'm not joking.
broma no estoy hablando en broma esta
people are scary to go to
gente da miedo para ir
Here I think I'll ask
aquí yo pienso pedir
protection a kiss Salom that Loli says
protección un beso Salomé que dice Loli
that if it is presented to the player it is worth it or so
que si se presenta al jugado vale o sea
but but all this is saying it
pero pero todo esto lo está diciendo
Here everything was put into its role when it was not
aquí todo metía en su papel cuando no se
has appeared in the case, that is, the trial
ha personado en la causa o sea el juicio
a mini kiss is made without her
se hace sin ella un beso mini
Maleficent, I don't know if it's possible.
Maléfica que yo no sé si se puede
personify at some point I think so
personar en algún momento yo creo que sí
that can be personified at some point
que se puede personar en algún momento
but right now It's in
pero ahora mismo Está en
Rebellion but all this is
Rebeldía pero que todo esto lo está
saying that if he shows up
diciendo ella que si se presenta el
played that if he gets around there in the year
jugado que si le da por ahí en el año
2026 that will ask for protection
2026 que va a pedir protección
Ah okay tesa okay okay I've already got you
Ah vale tesa vale vale Ya te he
understood that you are watching me and
entendido que me lo estás vigilando Y
how is it going
cómo va
tesa Even if I have to pay for it because
tesa Aunque me la tenga que pagar porque
These people, even if I have to pay for it
esta gente Aunque me la tenga que pagar
These people are afraid, look at what they are
miedo esta gente fijaros de lo que es
Maybe he doesn't care about the people
capaz le da lo mismo la gente de
around one person than another
alrededor de una persona que de otra
These people are dangerous, these people are dangerous.
esta gente es peligrosa esta gente se le
go every day every
ve cada día cada
night I don't kiss black girl Hey it's already happened
noche no beso negrita Oye ya se cumplió
the twice hand goal we want today is
el objetivo dos veces mano quemos hoy se
has met the objective twice
ha cumplido el objetivo dos veces
Hey okay okay okay tesa I'm staying
Eh vale vale vale tesa me quedo
Calm down Javi, you can appear yes.
tranquilo Javi se puede personar sí se
can personify and cease the rebellion if it is
puede personar y Cesar La Rebeldía sí se
Maybe not, but of course it doesn't look like it.
puede no pero claro no tiene pinta que
I'm going to do it, nothing else is that
lo vaya a hacer no otra cosa es que lo
go do what you can but of course
vaya a hacer como poder puede pero claro
I don't think he'll do it, not to his face.
yo no creo que lo haga no en su cara en
her ways I think this lady
sus formas yo creo que esta señora lo
What it does is that it is not going to
que lo que hace es que no se va a
appear in the case and the sentence will be issued
personar la causa saldrá la sentencia
esp and and that's it and he will pay if he is
esp y y ya está y lo pagará si lo está
telling you LoL It's that poor Unz
diciendo ya a ti LoL Es que unz la pobre
Thermomix cat crying a kiss
termomix quea de gato llorando un beso
Racel, well, they told Loli no.
racel bueno es que le dijeron a Loli no
I know why they told him that he
sé por qué le han dicho que que se
dedicate yourself to cooking better than not
dedica a la cocina mejor que no de más
gossip that no no people are
salseo que que no no gente es
dangerous would be interested in her leaving
peligrosa le interesaría que saliera
everything from Oli that came from Oli no
todo de Oli que saliera todo de Oli no
she is not alone
está sola no está
She is not alone, nor will she be, nor is she
sola ni está ni lo va a estar ni está
scared since it has more
acojonada puesto que tiene más
the three that there are have more than the
las tres que hay tiene más os que las
three who are sitting next to you and bad
tres que hay sentadas í a tu lado y mal
balls like you but from a town and a half
[__] que tú pero de pueblo y medio
my lord but of much more than you of
señor mío pero de mucho más que tú de
much more than you because who would
mucho más que tú porque quién te iba a
tell you who was going to tell you that
decir a ti quién te iba a decir a ti que
used to scaring children
acostumbrado a estar acojonando a niños
to children in your salsera you were going to come to
a niños en tu salsería te ibas a venir a
a loom wanting to scare women and
un telaro a querer acojonar a mujeres y
that women were going to stand up to you and
que las mujeres te iban a plantar cara y
that you were not going to go with
que no ibas aer con
they
ellos
Rios, I being in the
Rios yo estando en la
Salseria But they are poor Latinos
salsería Pero si son pobres latinos
Loli shows the tests You are a
Loli enseña las pruebas Eres un
liar and now tell me what insult
mentiroso y ahora dime qu insulto
liar I haven't hit a single one
mentiroso no he pegado ni un solo
really harassing insult that I
insulto acosador de verdad que me
mistreats
maltrata
psychologically it tells the one who threatens
psicológicamente dice al la que amenaza
with grabbing the hair If you see her it is
con agarrar de los pelos Si la ves es
she Johana morilla exactly the one that
ella Johana morilla exactamente la que
She is a threat. Hey, but let's pass.
amenaza es ella Oye pero vamos a pasar
already from this p of this lady or what
ya de este p de esta señora o qué
community on top of Pepa when
comunidad encima con lo de [__] cuando
Pepa came here and I received her well that
vino [__] aquí y que la recibí bien ese
same direct I think I think eh I'm wrong
mismo directo creo creo eh estoy mal
but I think this live is where
pero creo que este directo es donde
came up to tell me how dare I
subió a decirme que cómo me atrevo a
welcome Pepa
recibir bien a [__]
bel that that your bank accounts you
belá eso eso tus cuentas bancarias tú
for having a channel for your bank accounts
por tener un canal tus cuentas bancarias
Javi oliveira is aro to Javi oliveira that
es aro Javi oliveira a Javi oliveira que
He also lies in another clip Where is he?
también miente en otro clip Dónde está
This is because we are really going to
esto porque vamos de verdad de
true LoL official Nesle taster
verdad LoL catadora oficial de nesle
but I'm not understanding the thing
pero no estoy entendiendo lo del
chocolate that you are giving me a lot
chocolate que me estáis poniendo muchas
chocolate things and I don't know what it is
cosas chocolate y no sé qué es lo que es
I missed that, what is that something?
eso me lo he perdido eso qué es algo
New is no longer what Mercadona or
nuevo ya no es lo del mercadona o
What? I don't understand about chocolate.
qué Es que no entiendo lo del chocolate
I'm really writing it a lot
de verdad lo estoy escribiendo mucho
podiums to the kitchen not that it is pure
podios a la cocina no que es puro
poison what the [ __ ]
veneno qué [__]
eh I don't know if I continued watching Loli's thing
eh No sé si seguí viendo lo de Loli es
that there are many videos, man, in which no
que son muchos vídeos tío en la cual no
it is left t pm in which it is not left and
se deja t pm en la cual no se deja y
I hope he doesn't let himself befriended, no
espero que no se deje amigar que no
be afraid and one of those people is no
tenga miedo y una de esas personas es no
this
está
alone is not alone and if you have to go, you will
sola no está sola y si hay que ir se
goes and
va y
point that they are defending the
punto lo de que estén defendiendo el
sexual abuse of minors has me
abuso sexual a menores yo a mí me tiene
in shock eh I mean I've seen that I know
en shock eh o sea yo he visto que yo sé
that they were going to defend anything about
que iban a defender cualquier cosa sobre
me or because Good about me that they
mí o porque Bueno sobre mí que ellos
They think that
piensan que
defending him is going against me or something
defenderlo es ir contra mí o alguna cosa
you know about this, but really, I mean
de esta sabes sea pero de verdad O sea
I am not so important that you
no soy tan importante como para que os
you put to defend sexual abuse of
pongáis a defender abusos sexuales de
I tell you the truth, eh, it's that to me
verdad os lo digo eh sea es que a mí el
the fact that people come out to defend this
hecho de que salga gente a defender Esto
me
me
I think if a peseta gave each
tiene pienso si una peseta diera cada
Spanish but not me where they have to
español pero no a mí a donde tienen que
Who can stand this woman's live performances?
quién aguanta los directos de esta mujer
exploding head
cabeza explotando
Well, she has 50 people there watching her, she says.
pues 50 personas tiene ahí viéndola dice
alne than the last time that
alne que la última vez que
came out a little bit
salió un poquito
The injured party said that she had not drunk anything
perjudicada dijo que no había bebido que
had eaten chocolate and had given him
había comido chocolate y le había dado
joy don't [ __ ] with me don't [ __ ] with me that happened
alegría no me joda no me joda eso pasó
who said she was going to be dressed
que dijo que iba que iba puesta de
chocolate
chocolate
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Uncle, they are very special people, eh? They are people.
tío son gente muy especial eh Son gente
very special Well let's finish with
muy especial Bueno vamos a terminar con
Loli, I'm going to the bathroom and you want me to?
Loli voy a ir al baño y queréis que
Let's see what Peppa does or should we leave it for now?
veamos lo de Peppa o lo dejamos ya para
tomorrow or we've been here for 2 hours and
mañana oes ya llevamos aquí 2s horas y
half eh I don't know what
media eh No sé yo qué
do you want us to watch Peppa or
hacer queréis que veamos lo de Peppa o
answering aar of Troy or we leave it already
contestando aar de Troya o ya lo dejamos
for tomorrow she has colors like Heidi
para mañana tiene los colores como Heidi
in it
en El
swing and point the level and degree that
columpio y punto el nivel y grado que
They have already surpassed with so pm I don't know
han sobrepasado ya con tan pm no se
can allow it to be defended
puede permitir hay que que defender a
Tania, we are all going to sign together because
Tania todos juntos vamos a firmar porque
the husband is innocent
el marido sea inocente
Ah allergy I had read joy of course
Ah alergia había leído alegría claro es
that had more meaning joy than
que tenía más sentido alegría que le
had given allergies
había dado alergia el
clear chocolate that I understand that
chocolate claro que yo entiendo A esa
people who say Oh Why haven't they?
gente que dice Oh Porque no lo han
I have lived it for months
vivido yo lo he vivido durante meses
every night every day I have
todas las noches todos los días lo he
I have lived it
vivido lo he
suffered not me I them
sufrido no yo yo los
My poor thing and this can't go on any longer
míos pobre y esto ya no puede seguir
This cannot continue, this cannot continue
Esto no puede segir no puede seguir
Poor what they have already done to a lady
pobre lo que ya han hecho con una señora
with his
con su
family what they have done to the poor
familia lo que han hecho con la pobre
Tania's family
familia eh de Tania
eh How do you think of reading okay how do you
eh Cómo se os ocurre leer vale cómo se
how does it occur to remind Tania that
cómo se ocurre recordarle a Tania que
had a campaign on his profile
tenía en su perfil una campaña una
Signature collection to get her husband out
recogida de Firma para sacar a su marido
from unjust imprisonment after having
de la injusta cárcel después de haber
abused an 11 year old girl eh what
abusado de una niña de 11 años eh lo que
What have you done to poor Tania? And me?
habéis hecho con la pobre Tania eh Y yo
These people are the real ones. I mean.
esta gente es que son de verdad O sea
but the problem is that these people vote
pero el problema es que esta gente votan
No, I mean, these people have the right to
no O sea esta gente tienen derecho a
vote and all that stuff and that's how we are
voto y todas esas cosas y así estamos
no no you can't have respect for yourself
no no no se puede tener respetos por uno
while that one is crushing
mientras ese uno está machacando a
others and that's it and with all his grapefruit uncle
otros y ya está y con todo su pomelo tío
poor Tania and the poor man
la pobre Tania y el pobre
husband poor Tania and poor Ah
marido la pobre Tania y el pobre Ah
Okay, but wait, wait, wait.
bueno pero Espérate Espérate Espérate
Wait Wait eh to finish with
Espérate Espérate eh para terminar con
This topic already eh And now yes for real
este tema ya eh Y ahora ya sí de verdad
So we see this, I went to the bathroom because
O sea vemos esto vi al baño porque
We've been here for almost TR hours.
Llevamos aquí TR horas casi
[Music]
[Música]
And let's see what Peppa said, eh?
y y vamos a ver lo que ha dicho Peppa eh
Because Peppa by
Porque Peppa por
supposed because I tell you that it is very very
supuesto porque os digo que es muy muy
serious is very serious So
grave es muy grave Así
[Music]
[Música]
I don't know, I haven't even spoken with T.
que no sé yo no he hablado ni con T no
I talk to her I don't know what's going to happen
me hablo con ella No sé lo que va a
do what will stop you from doing what
hacer lo que va a dejar de hacer lo que
I don't have any
no tengo ni
idea what happened but of course it's that coming
idea qué pasé pero claro Es que viniendo
whose
de quién
Please forgive me for not believing me.
viene perdonarme que no me crea
nothing I can't I can't I myself
nada yo no puedo yo no puedo Yo me
stuck a case with the desk O
pegado uncho caso con el escritorio O
be that it is very strong very strong very
sea que es muy fuerte muy fuerte muy
What came out of Tania is very strong
fuerte lo que ha salido de Tania es muy
mu mu strong but of course it comes from
mu mu fuerte pero claro es que viene de
Javi Bueno she considers that it comes from
Javi Bueno ella considera que viene de
Javi Because it doesn't come from Javi it comes from the
Javi Porque no viene de Javi viene de la
Tania herself, who is the one who did it
propia Tania que es la que lo ha
published in all its
publicado en todas sus
networks asking for a signature to remove the
redes pidiendo Firma para sacar al
husband from prison And from
marido de la cárcel Y del
poderjudicial.com which is and the
poderjudicial.com que está y la
sentence can be read and is a
sentencia se puede leer y es una
horror movie
película de terror
eh but it comes from Javi then I
eh pero es que viene de Javi entonces yo
on the other side I am on the other side I
al otro lado yo estoy en el otro lado yo
I am on the side where the defense is
estoy en el lado donde se defiende el
another tremendous one eh
otro tremendo eh
These people are crazy
es para volverse loco esta gente
eh Nothing at all, whatever it is, who is it?
eh Nada de nada sea que es que de quien
comes is
viene es
that has been gone for I don't know how many weeks
que se ha tirado yo no sé cuos semanas
Maybe even a couple of months putting
Quizás hasta un par de meses poniendo
continually that I was knocking at him
continuamente que yo le agaba
sexually and that I was afraid to take out
sexualmente y que tenía miedo de sacar
Then I can't believe it.
al per Entonces yo no me puedo creer
nothing, you're not harassing me sexually, you're harassing me
nadaa t me acosas no sexualmente te me
He harassed me, I didn't say anything
acosaba yo no he dicho nada
tremendous sexual eh man they would be of the
sexual tremendo eh tío se pondrían del
whoever's side it was, they would take sides.
lado del que fuera eh se pondrían de de
what it was uncle is that more than this
lo que fuera tío es que ya más que esto
Uncle, more than this has come out. What
tío ya más que esto que ha salido Qué
It is a continued abuse over time
es un abuso continuado en el tiempo a
a minor since she was 11 years old until
una menor desde que tenía 11 años hasta
who was 15 and they are screaming
que tenía 15 y están poniendo el grito
in heaven because it is what it has been
en el cielo porque es que lo ha
commented Javi
comentado Javi
This is privacy, this is yours.
Es que esto es la privacidad esto es su
privacy man Why don't we leave the
privacidad hombre Por qué no dejamos la
own I mean imagine that tomorrow it comes out
propia O sea imaginaros que mañana sale
A piece of news I've already told you before is
una noticia ya os lo he dicho antes es
that news comes out almost daily
que salen casi a diario noticias de
aggressors of rapists Well then
agresores de violadores Bueno pues
Imagine that a news story comes out, or rather
imaginaros que sale una noticia o sea
This is exactly the same as tomorrow
esto es exactamente lo mismo que mañana
On Tele5 there is a news item and it says, well,
en tele5 salga una noticia y diga e Pues
look today three
mira hoy tres
three young people leaving a nightclub
tres jóvenes al salir de una discoteca
They have raped a woman in an elevator
han violado en un ascensor a una
girl and they take these people and they go out in a
chavala y cogen esta gente y salen en un
direct and they say and their followers and they say
directo y dicen y sus seguidores y dicen
or u How bad How bad tele5 How bad the
o u Qué malo Qué malo tele5 Qué malo el
newscast giving this news that
telediario dando esta noticia eso
belongs to the privacy of the three
pertenece a la privacidad de los tres
kids from the three of the three poor
chavales de los tres de los tres pobres
rapists
violadores
Tania took out until the date in which
Tania sacó hasta la fecha en la que
I had a prior hearing when I had
tenía audiencia previa cuando he tenido
trial when I had to testify
juicio cuando he tenido que testificar
in another trial that was not mine Tania has
en otro juicio que no era mío Tania ha
took out everything that was private which has
sacado todo que era privado lo que le ha
gives the
da la
win and I tell you this is just the
gana y ya os digo esto es solo el
I'm starting, but like me, that one will continue.
comienzo eh pero como yo esa va a seguir
will continue will continue will come out
va a seguir va a seguir van a salir
things coming out of course or that is but the level
saliendo cosas claro o sea pero el nivel
is that the level is that is exa is
es ese el nivel es ese es exa es
exactly the same as if it comes out tomorrow
exactamente lo mismo que si mañana sale
a news item on the Tele5 newscast and
una noticia en el telediario de tele5 y
says Hey look
dice Oye mira
that three young people have been raped in a
que que han violado tres jóvenes en una
nightclub in an elevator they raped
discoteca en un ascensor han violado a
a young woman and they all start to open
una joven y cogen empiezan todos a abrir
straight to say Oy Oy Oy how bad
directos a decir Oy Oy Oy qué malos los
from the news, eh, how bad the ones from the
del informativo eh Qué malos los del
informative eh poor privacy poor
informativo eh pobre intimidad pobre
privacy of violators that is a
privacidad de los violadores ese es un
private topic of
tema privado de
They are tremendous, tremendous, man, what is happening here
ellos tremendo tremendo tío lo de esta
people are tremendous That's it, there's no more
gente es tremendo Ya está no tiene más
What these people do is tremendous, man, man.
lo de esta gente es tremendo tío tío En
Seriously really, eh? And I don't know if we'll get there.
serio de verdad eh Y no sé si llegaremos
to do a live reading it eh but the
a hacer un directo leyéndola eh pero la
sentence is the worst thing I've ever seen
sentencia es la peor cosa que he visto
In life, in my almost 40 years, it is a
en la vida en mis casi 40 años es una
sentence worse than that of Daniel Sancho
sentencia peor que la de Daniel Sancho
You can't even imagine, man.
no os podéis ni imaginar tío las
atrocities he did to that little girl
atrocidades que le hizo a esa chiquilla
You can't even imagine, well, Pablo.
no os podéis ni imaginar bueno Pablo
Pablo has said something not in his
Pablo ha dicho alguna cosilla no en su
Twitter no
Twitter no
The only thing that Tania I imagine is that
Yo lo único que si Tania Me imagino que
will take because I already told you that the thing is
tomará porque ya os digo que la cosa es
very serious and very
muy grave y muy
very delicate
delicada muy
delicate, that's what someone told me now
delicada eso me decía alguien ahora por
private
privado
Well I know that without you having it, you will have it
Bueno yo s as sin con ustedes tendrás
I am not saying that I should condemn this.
que que condenar esto no digo yo
condemn nor that I were a
condenar ni que yo fuera un
judge sentenced Javi to Javi yes to Javi to
juez condenó a Javi a Javi sí a Javi a
Javi did say broom hairs once.
Javi sí que ha dicho pelos escoba una
youtuber to Javi yes eh to Javi
youtuber a Javi sí eh a Javi se lo
We remember that he called her broom hair one time
recordamos que le dijo pelo escoba una
youtuber okay We don't know what happened
youtuber vale No sabemos Qué pasó Ni
We know what the [ __ ] was going on because
sabemos qué [__] estaba pasando porque
He told him in 2019 But anyway, let's go
se lo dijo en el 2019 Pero bueno vamos a
be until approximately 2027
estar hasta el 2027 aproximadamente
talking about how Javi has to be kicked out
hablando de que Javi hay que echarlo de
internet let's make groups let's
internet vamos a hacer grupos vamos a
make a group let's make a group of
hacer un grupo vamos a hacer un grupo de
affected by Javi Oliveira and Vamos a
afectados por Javi oliveira y Vamos a
get us all in touch with YouTube
ponernos todos en contacto con YouTube
to tell him that Javi has been sentenced
para decirle que a Javi lo han condenado
twice a
dos veces por
tremendous insult
insultar tremendo
tremendous I do not condemn they condemn the
tremendo Yo no condeno condenan los
judges
jueces
tremendous
tremendo
tremendous I will not condemn anything because I
tremendo yo no condenaré nada porque yo
don't have
no tengo
enough information and although the
suficiente información y aunque la
I had no lie eh lie I have
tuviera yo no mentira eh mentira tengo
why condemn nothing nothing follow me
por qu condenar nada nada me siguen
sending nothing So if you don't have the
mandando nada Entonces si no tenéis la
enough information to convict By
suficiente información para condenar Por
what when the TV factory made
qué cuando la fábrica de la tele hizo
an injustice against Antonio David
una injusticia contra Antonio David
you condemned if you had nothing to do with it and
condenaste si no teníais nada que ver y
it didn't go with
no iba con
you So if you have nothing to
ustedes Entonces si no tenéis nada que
condemn
condenar
eh Why when you were sucking up to me
eh Por qué cuando me hacíais la pelota
condemned everyone to the harasser who posted
condenaba todos al acosador que publicó
photo of my kids and he was stalking me eh
foto de mis hijos y me perseguía eh Por
why did you condemn everyone when I
qué lo condenaste todos cuando me
You sucked up to me if I didn't go with you
hacíais la pelota si no iba con ustedes
and you are not judges if you do not have them
y no sois jueces si si no tenéis ustedes
the power to condemn because you have
la potestad para condenar porque habéis
everyone has given their opinion on the Daniel Sancho case
opinado todos del caso Daniel Sancho
let the judges do their thing
dejar que los jueces hagan su
work no no no we don't have
trabajo no no no nosotros no tenemos
We condemn no eh we
nosotros condenar no eh nosotros
condemn no Peppa we contact
condenar no Peppa nosotros contactamos
with Joan Plana eh Although in his
con Joan plana eh A pesar de que en su
day you supported the game over and there is a
día apoyaste el game over y hay un
comment on your gameover saying
comentario en el gameover tuyo diciendo
that the gameover is a masterpiece
que el gameover es una obra maestra
because it is okay because it is and you
porque lo es vale porque lo es y te
You went to contact John privately.
fuiste a contactarle por privado a John
plans to take it to your channel there yes
planas para llevarlo a tu canal ahí sí
you judge but in a sexual abuse to a
juzgas pero en un abuso sexual a una
minor there I shut up there I shut up The
menor ahí me callo ahí me callo El
Javi Oliveira is convicted Yes yes The
condenado es Javi oliveira Sí sí El
Javi Oliveira is convicted Yes yes because
condenado es Javi oliveira Sí sí porque
said broom hair Uh
dijo pelo escoba Uh
Be careful, they keep sending me photos.
cuidado me siguen mandando fotos fotos
to
a
See, madam, he was already sentenced for little
ver señora ya fue condenado por poco
time because that permanent expression
tiempo porque eso expresión permanente
exactly that they do not have to condemn
exactamente que no tienen que condenar
nothing that already was
nada que ya fue
condemned the issue is that
condenado el tema es que
I was collecting signatures, I understand, saying
taba recogiendo firmas entiendo diciendo
that it was nothing, that there was no evidence that
que no era nada que no había pruebas que
It was a false testimony. That's Tania.
era un testimonio falso Esa es la Tania
and was with this person who had just
y estuvo con esta persona que acababa de
know you know it's tremendous uncle I am
conocer sabes que es tremendo tío Yo es
that you really know that these people do not
que de verdad sees que esta gente no
has no limit has no limit
tiene límite ninguno no tiene límite
none are what
ninguno son lo que
They are nothing more than saying one thing, let's see, say it
son nada más que di una cosa a ver dila
I know you are sending me by by
Sé que me estáis mandando por por
md if there are facts
md si hay hechos
proven, let whoever has it take it out
probados que los saque quien lo tenga
what to take out if they want to take it out
que sacar si es que lo quieren sacar
But this one here is not going to be for
Pero esta que está aquí no va a ser por
many that you send me because Sid is a
muchos que me mandéis porque es Sid una
sentence no way Ah ah and Moca That's not
sentencia ni de coña Ah ah y Moca Eso no
That's not it, that's not it, we don't talk about that.
eso no eh eso no de eso no hablamos
eh That's not that's not Well then yes he did bite it
eh Eso no eso no Bueno pues si lo picó
herself in Chain that people go to
ella misma en Chain que vaya la gente a
Chain and look at him Ah I'm not going to No on that
Chain y lo mire Ah yo no voy a No en eso
I'm not going to enter, that's not Javi's, it's not
no voy a entrar eso no es de Javi no es
No way, it's not from Javi. No way, it's not from Javi.
de Javi ni de coña No ni de coña no es
Javi's if it were that it were that a
de Javi si que fuera que fuera que un
YouTuber has sued Javi for
youtuber ha demandado a Javi por
insults that went because it was that a
insultos que fuera por que fuera que un
YouTuber has sued Javi for telling him
youtuber ha demandado a Javi por decirle
[ __ ] or for saying, "Oh, you have the
[__] o por decirle Uy tienes el
black eye or things like that. Oh there you go.
ojo morado o cosas de esas Uy ahí í
We opened 18 live shows around the world
abrimos 18 directos todo el mundo que
It was a private thing for Javi that was
fuera una cosa Privada de Javi que fuera
an uncle of Javi a cousin of Javi the one who
un tío de Javi un primo de Javi el que
has done
ha hecho
something that was a cousin of Javi or a
algo que fuera un primo de Javi o un
Javi's brother, let's see if we can
hermano de Javi a ver si a ver si nos
we gave privacy a [ __ ]
pasábamos la privacidad por los [__]
or not
o no
How strong they are, man, how strong then
qué fuertes son eh tío qué fuerte pues
that's how you are and that's why they are becoming more and more
así estáis y por eso cada vez se están
unsubscribing more people from your
des suscribiendo más gente de vuestros
mother canals
canales madre
Mine yes I know that x is full of that but
mía sí sé que x está lleno de eso pero
[Music]
[Música]
m but I don't but I don't have that against Javi
m pero yo no pero yo eso no contra Javi
I'm not there
Yo ahí no
I don't, I don't
yo no no yo
not who has taken it out to show the
no quién lo ha sacado que muestre las
tests and such And that and whoever wants
pruebas y tal Y que cual y el que quiera
I would comment on it even if I brought out evidence of it
comentarlo yo aunque sacara pruebas de
I'm not going to comment on that, I'm not
todo yo no voy a comentar eso yo no es
from Javi I
de Javi yo
not this sentence
no esta sentencia
No, because it really seems to me that
no porque de verdad que me parece que
You can't get there. Ah, no, not until
hasta ahí No se puede llegar Ah No hasta
there Not up to there Not up to there I don't know
ahí No hasta ahí No hasta ahí No se
can arrive How are you going to comment on a
puede llegar Cómo Vais a comentar una
whatever the poor privacy of this
cosa sea de la pobre privacidad de esta
people each with his own conscience
gente cada uno con su conciencia cada
one
uno
with each one with his conscience, eh, that is
con cada uno con su consciencia eh o sea
not Tania's conscience eh but the
no la conciencia de Tania eh Sino la
awareness of the one who commented on this
consciencia del que ha comentado esto
Of course Tania's conscience no no no
claro la consciencia de Tania no no no
They are not what they are, family with what
no son lo que son familia con lo
whether or not to do
que haga o no haga
or too much
o demasiado
strong
fuerte
no And in this case yes
no Y en este caso si
sale I don't understand why a youtuber deletes
sale No entiendo a youtuber que elimine
many words and then stop
muchas palabras y luego deje de
of putting this type of stories that
de de poner este tipo de historias que
I already said that they are too delicate
ya digo que son demasiado delicadas
loneliness for a month with us
soledad p cu mes con nosotros
many what youtuber has to
muchísimas qué que youtuber tiene que
censor public sentence that does not
censurar sentencia pública que no
You understand that I had but if you
entiendes que yo tuve pero si ustedes
You have done with the sentence what you
habéis hecho con la sentencia lo que os
I had wanted to but here it has not happened
había dado la gana pero aquí no se ha
commented on the case of Carlota Prado is not
comentado el caso de Carlota Prado no se
has commented on the case of Marta Castillo
ha comentado el caso de Marta Castillo
Marta's case has not been commented on
no se ha comentado el el caso de Marta
riesco How that the one that you
riesco Cómo que el de la que a ti te
like not the one you like
gusta no el de con la que ustedes os
you wear the one from your little group that one
lleváis el de la de vuestro grupito esa
sentence cannot be commented on that
sentencia no se puede comentar esa la
has to censor youtuber but Franco
tiene que censurar youtuber pero Franco
He died many years ago, huh?
murió hace muchos años eh
thanks for solidarity
graci solidad por
renew and says I liked the live show
renovar y dice me gustó el directo de
yesterday it But if I saw you telling me something
ayer it Pero si te vi diciéndome cosa
to
a
what did I put you to
a que te puse
heart wait
corazón espérate
I put my heart into you
te puse corazón
mine don't worry
mío no te preocupes
You wait, Oh, my back will have me
tú espérate Ay mi espalda me vo tener
what to take
que tomar
a
un a
see it seems very serious
ver parece mu grave
I think it is very serious.
Me parece muy grave
but but no, I don't position myself against it
pero pero no no me posiciono en contra
Oh
Ay
niita but has to take one
niita per tiene que tomar una
tablet
pastilla
wait what do you
espérate qué te
spend a little moment, serious, eh
pasar un momentito vana grave eh
Out of respect, I'm not going to take advantage of
por respeto yo no me voy a aprovechar de
something so
algo tan
serious and as delicate as that is
grave y tan delicado como es eso Lo
I'm sorry but
siento pero
not to ask for money for cancer there
no para pedir dinero para el cáncer ahí
We don't give a damn about respect
el respeto nos lo pasamos por el pomelo
no Peppa to ask for money with a
no Peppa para pedir dinero con un
familiar having a relative there
familiar teniendo un familiar ahí el
Respect wasn't that delicate, no Peppa, eh?
respeto no era tan delicado no Peppa eh
with a relative of that kid who is
con un familiar del chaval ese que se
He died of cancer, huh? And we asked for the money and
murió de cáncer eh Y pedimos el dinero y
then we forget for 7 months there is the
luego se nos olvida dur 7 meses hay el
respect no I'm not going to tell you more Peppa
respeto no no te voy a decir más Peppa
Where was the respect when you had
Dónde estaba el respeto cuando teníais a
a spokesman for a foundation against the
un portavoz de una fundación contra el
cancer and you had Loli on call
cáncer y teníais en llamada a Loli
Huerta telling him what was happening to him
Huerta contándole lo que le pasaba a
She said nothing was wrong with her but she was
ella que no le pasaba nada pero se lo
He invented respect there, which is there
inventó ahí el respeto qué ahí el
I respected Loli's privacy.
respeto qué era la privacidad de Loli
was very strong or how was that Peppa
era muy fuerte o cómo cómo era eso Peppa
the little word that you are mistaken Peppa that
la palabrita que os equivocáis Peppa que
You were wrong and said that Peppa
os equivocaste y dijisteis que que Peppa
that Loli had cancer and in the end it was
que Loli tenía un cáncer y al final era
a biopsy that you got wrong
una biopsia que os equivocaste la
I swear, do you remember that you were wrong?
palabrita te acuerdas que os equivocaste
There respect was all the same to you, no. This is true.
ahí el respeto te daba igual no Esto sí
This is because this is clear this is clear that
Esto sí porque esto claro esto Claro que
this F of you
esto F de tú
Not you, I don't even talk to Tania or
no tú que yo ni me hablo con Tania ni
nothing here we gave him but yours
nada aer aquí le dimos pero vuestro
enemy Javi oliveira you don't care if you
enemigo Javi oliveira te da igual si os
you hate each other
odiáis entre
you do not care that
ustedes os da igual que
you get together among all those who hate each other
os juntáis entre todos los que os odiáis
because the important one is Javi Oliveira and
porque el importante es Javi oliveira y
the center Javi Oliveira and that is for him
el centro Javi oliveira y ese es por el
that we are all going
que vamos todos
No, look, we had to talk about this for
No mira t había que hablar de esto por
what had been previously discussed
lo que se había hablado anteriormente de
of
de
It's burning but I'm not going there now. Oh no.
arde pero yo yo no voy ahí ahora Oh no
Because it is also that it is
Porque además Es que es
That is a topic that is not a possibility
que eso es un un tema que que ni de coña
I'm going to touch it, right? Or is it a lie?
lo voy a tocar ah verdad O sea mentira
I'm not going to do it
no lo voy a
play Well, nothing, take the morning to
tocar Pues nada llévate la mañana al
Channel and collaborates with it although some
Canal y colabora con ella aunque algunos
They will surely take the morning and
lo harán seguramente llévate la mañana y
collaborates with her in luxury
colabora con ella de lujo de
I'm not going to go for luxury
lujo no lo voy a
touch but she is sure
tocar pero está segura
It's just that no, I'm not going to touch it exactly.
es que no no lo voy a tocar exactamente
Jos sea dry and around there
mar José seco y por ahí
[Music]
[Música]
No, I don't know, cobalonga, but really.
No pues no sé cobalonga pero de verdad
They just sent me a photo now
que me acaban de mandar ahora una foto
Right now and I feel it in my soul
Ahora mismo y yo lo siento en el alma
that you do it so that I react
que lo hacéis para que yo reaccione yo
not this way
por aquí no
Ah over there No, it's not Javi, I'm not going
Ah por ahí No no es Javi yo no voy a
commit the crime
cometer el delito
of what, why, why not, what crime
de de qué porque porque no qué delito
Because besides that
Porque además que
no what crime are you going to comment if there is one
no qué delito vas a comentar si hay una
sentence Yes but sasusaku is a topic
sentencia Sí pero sasusaku es un tema
very
muy
rugged and I since
escabroso y yo desde
then that is too private intimate and
luego eso es demasiado privado íntimo y
delicate that is not that is not intimate is
delicado que no que no es íntimo es
intimate I know you are not
íntimo Ya lo sé que no os estáis
finding out you're welcome yet
enterando De nada an
mor but it's something I don't know if it's going to be so
mor pero es algo Yo no sé si tan lo va a
say on your channel or not some information
decir en su canal O no una información
that has left the environment very very
que ha salido del entorno muy muy
very very close friend of
allegado muy muy allegado de
Tania And what about
Tania Y de lo que
It happened and so if it will be I think I don't know
pasó y así que si será yo creo no sé
Tania, you are here, I am summoning you.
Tania estás por aquí te estoy invocando
Tania Tania you're here, eh cobadonga
Tania Tania estás por aquí eh cobadonga
If you've seen it on Twitter, well then.
si la he viste en Twitter Bueno pues
I'm a coward, no ...
cobadonga yo por ahí no no
Pepa went through those things that I refuse to go through.
pasó pasar [__] esas cosas que me niego
Pepa is more of a call to ex-boyfriends.
[__] es más de llamar a los exnovios de
your sister okay that is Peppa Peppa
tu hermana vale o sea Peppa Peppa le
Leo's teacher needs to be taken
falta llevar a la profe de Leo le falta
That's right, your sister's ex-boyfriends and
eso sí eh los exnovios de tu hermana y
all those things Yes true Peppa That's true
todos esas cosas Sí verdad Peppa Eso sí
That's no problem, that doesn't have any
eso sin problema eso no tiene ninguna
line nor How little shame you have of
línea ni Qué poca vergüenza tenéis de
true I mean with this topic I think that
verdad O sea con este tema Yo creo que
is that look
es que mira
honestly it speaks more about you than about
sinceramente habla más de ustedes que de
that it's nothing, that is, why
que de que de nada o sea es que para qué
You know what I'm telling you about this topic
sabes lo que te digo o sea con este tema
I think that masks are no longer for what purpose
yo creo que las caretas no ya para qué
not if they didn't know that there was enough
no si no sabían que haa lo suficiente
be a thing uncle a thing that itself
sea una cosa tío una cosa que la propia
Tania has told her that it is nothing of hers
Tania la ha contado que no es nada de su
private life that she has told him that
vida privada que la ha contado ella que
has made it public and that is a thing
la ha hecho pública y que es una cosa
very fat woman who has a sentence and who
gordísima que tiene una sentencia y que
Tania defended what she was doing
la Tania defendió que estaba haciendo
a campaign to defend it even with what
una campaña para defenderlo aún con lo
that there was eh even with what there was and she
que había eh aún con lo que había y ella
He defends him and is a person who is not
lo defiende y es una persona que no es
a relative who is not a relative who is
un familiar que sea no es familiar que
be your brother, your father, or someone who
sea tu hermano tu padre eh o alguien que
you have no choice but to be your family member
no te queda otra que sea tu familiar es
a person who had just
una persona que acababa de
knowing is tremendous
conocer es tremendo
Guys, guys, I'm going to leave, no, I mean.
chicos chicos yo me voy a ir no o sea
It's 12 no what do you want us to see
son las 12 no qué queréis que veamos la
response from the people of Troy is given to us
respuesta de la pppa lar de Troya se nos
it's been late no
ha hecho tarde no
Alan says, neither you as innocent as
dice Alan ni tú tan inocente como
always believing the other day that in this
siempre creyendo el otro día que en esto
They could not put their hatred for you first.
no podían poner por delante el odio a ti
I'll tell you
te lo
I said I didn't get it
dije yo no me lo
I believed I thought that no that in
creía Yo pensaba que no que en
this tremendous
esto tremendo
Hey guys, I don't know what to do. I don't know if
eh chicos no sé qué hacer eh No sé si
go to the salsera It's that the salsera
irme a la salsería Es que la salsería
what is it
qué es lo que
Come on, I'm going to the salseria later.
hay venga me voy luego a la salsería un
a little while but we stay here for a while or
ratillo pero nos quedamos aquí un rato o
what we see the response of these people
qué vemos la respuesta de esta gente
we see the
vemos la
Peppa and Angel's response to the art
respuesta de la Peppa y el Ángel al ar
of Troy or what but I have to go to the bathroom
de Troya o qué pero tengo que ir al baño
wait a second, eh, I've been here for 3 hours 3
un segundo eh que llevo aquí 3 horas 3
We've been going for hours, eh? Yes, Mary, if I do something
horas llevamos eh Sí Mary si hago algo
It will be on the main channel but good
será en el canal principal pero bien
made with her clips but oh well
hecho con los clips de ella pero bueno
I'll do that if it continues if it continues if the
eso ya lo haré si sigue si sigue si la
Tania wants to continue if we continue with him
Tania quiere seguir si seguimos con el
topic if not we leave it here eh Also
tema si no ya lo dejamos aquí eh También
I tell you, eh, for me I already believe that
os digo eh Para mí ya yo creo que
also
también
I think we leave it here, eh? Yes, no, yes.
yo creo que lo dejamos aquí eh Si no si
already the topic also I think we should
ya el tema también Creo que deberíamos
leave it here eh
dejarlo aquí eh
you want to see it
lo queréis ver
don't come let's see it but I'm going to go to
no venga vamos a verlo pero voy a ir al
bath for a minute while
baño un minuto mientras que
to the
al
to to
al al
I've started dripping with the Polo, eh man?
me he puesto chorreando el Polo eh tío o
the water bottle was bad
sea tenía la botella de agua estaba mal
closed and I got the shirt wet
cerrada y me he puesto chorr el polito
Uncle me who came dressed up to be
tío yo que venía arregladito para estar
with you
con ustedes
With this topic I am with the crochet
con este tema estoy con el ganchillo a
100 per hour Well I think the issue is
100 por hora Bueno yo creo que el tema e
What does it say?
Qué dice
tesa tesa but we have to do that
tesa tesa pero eso lo tenemos que
watch tesa tell me some news tell me
vigilar tesa dime alguna noticia dime
Any news? Tell me, is it going well or is it?
alguna noticia Dime pues va bien o pues
is going wrong or what am I suffering from?
va mal o qué estoy sufriendo
Hey, come on, let's see what's up with this one.
eh venga vamos a ver lo de esta
people let's see these people go
gente vamos a verlo de esta gente va
Let's see if we have a laugh.
Vamos a ver si nos echamos unas risas
At least what was said is not valid. I think
por lo menos no lo dicho vale Yo creo
that topic is already a capture
que ya ese tema eh est una captura
screen to all of you who want
pantalla a todos y todas las que queráis
I think we should leave that topic alone.
yo creo que ese tema ya debemos dejarlo
into oblivion Unless this girl
en el olvido A no ser que esta chica
appear again as an elephant in a
aparezca otra vez como elefante en una
junk shop and start getting involved again
cacharrería y empiece otra vez a meterse
with everyone and everything else is valid in what sense
con todos y demás vale en qué sentido
tesa So what's going on what's going on in
tesa O sea qué pasa qué está pasando en
that live
ese directo
Tell me all you want
Cuéntame a todos y todas las que queráis
eh give me memberships and and make you
eh regalarme membresías y y haceros
members or subscribe or super chat os
miembros o suscribiros o super chat os
It seems good not to cut the ha like that
parece bien para no cortar así el ha
My mother said that in the end you know
dicho mi madre que al final Tú sabes
Let's put OK, because I said it.
Vamos a poner Vale pues lo he dicho
Hey, if you want to contribute, let's go here, I don't see
eh si queréis aportar vamos aquí no veo
bang I'm going to get in the middle because I
báng me voy a poner en medio porque yo a
My aje I want to see where can I put myself?
mi aje quiero verlo Dónde me puedo poner
that I see my aje look at my little face
que yo vea a mi aje mira la carita de mi
ae look at my aje's face Look at my a
ae mira la carita de mi aje Mira mi a
Look at my a
Mira mi a
What does Vale do? He has already told her.
A qué hace Vale pues ya le ha dicho la
Peppa okay you can become a member
Peppa vale os podéis hacer miembro le
you like you put you can give super
dais like os ponéis os podéis dar super
chat Okay it will be Peppa a little bit of
chat Okay lo será Peppa un poco de
music montage that I have done and at the end and
música montaje que he hecho y al final y
This live stream is not going to be monetized.
este directo no se va a monetizar Así
that the exact aids that you have are
que las ayudas exas que tengáis o sea
that you may be very welcome
que podáis hacer muy bien recibidas
It is worth it that he has put music to it
quedan vale que le ha puesto música al
straight to the beginning and the direct does not go
directo al principio y el directo no va
Hey, that's a good one, huh. That's a good one, man.
Oye esa es buena eh Esa es buena cabrón
to ask eh
para pedir eh
That's good, I didn't know it. Oh well.
Está buena esa no me la sabía Eh bueno
eh that has been a very hard job
eh que eso que ha sido un trabajo muy
arduous I It has been many many hours of
arduo yo Ha sido muchas muchas horas de
the ones I have not sacrificed in my life
las que no tengo en mi vida sacrificado
many hours of doing other things for
muchas horas de hacer otras cosas para
do things well the way I like
hacer las cosas bien como me gusta
I like to do things
hacerlo a mí me gusta hacer las cosas
well and to my mother I know that too and has
bien y a mi madre Yo sé que también y ha
been looking for a long long time and
sido mucho mucho tiempo buscando y
looking eh direct by direct and looking
mirando eh directo por directo y mirando
because those were things that happened before
porque eso fue cosas que han pasado hace
a lot of time and mom how many hours we
mucho tiempo y mamá Cuántas horas nos
we have thrown we have not thrown here my
hemos tirado no hemos tirado aquí mi
Mom and I reviewing videos and videos 40
madre y yo revisando vídeos y vídeos 40
40 40 50 hours because we have gone to the we have
40 40 50 horas porque hemos ido al hemos
gone to WhatsApp to Why to How
ido al a los WhatsApp a Por qué a cómo
what he said How did he not say in the end because the
qué dijo Cómo no dijo en fin porque la
history always has you can imagine the
historia siempre tiene pued imaginar el
effort that must be made to do
esfuerzo que hay que hacer para hacer
Things are half good, it's not a we don't have
las cosas medio bien no es un no tenemos
We don't have editors or anything like that.
no tenemos Editores ni ni nada de eso eh
We don't have or mini Maleficent which is a
No tenemos o mini Maléfica que es una
Maleficent but small has given away
Maléfica pero pequeñita ha regalado
five members kiss gorgeous you are
cinco miembros beso guapísima se te
loves everyone you love
quiere a todos y todas las que queráis
give away memberships and make you members
regalar membresías y y haceros miembros
Or subscribe super
O suscribiros super
chat Antonio I'm going to show you what
chat Antonio Te voy a enseñar lo que le
taught me an easy thing that they give me a
enseñó una cosa fácil que me ponen un
strike but show the paper or so
strike pero enseñar el papel o sea
look at all the things they have said
fijaros con todas de cosas que han dicho
From all over the world, no one here has taught
de todo el mundo aquí nadie ha enseñado
nothing but Pepa has to teach you one
nada pero [__] tiene que enseñarte una
very easy thing you teach that you were there
cosa muy fácil enseña tú que estaba tú
low not the goal that Loli Loli creates
de baja no el tanto que crea Loli Loli
never taught that it did not occur to me
nunca enseñado que a mí no se me ocurría
say Loli I showed the paper eh aje eh aje
decir Loli enseñ el papel eh aje eh aje
what a pair mother son eh what a pair
vaya par madre hijo eh vaya par
Man, what's up, Salome has given away?
hombre Pero qué pasa Salomé ha regalado
10 others or my Salom don't feel like it today
otros 10 o mi Salomé no tenéis ganas hoy
going to bed eh today is going to have me
de ir a la cama eh hoy me va a tener
here between one and another the many no
aquí entre unos y otros las tantas no
then I'll have to go to the
luego me tendré que ir para la
youth
chavalería
no siol has a dog please don't know either
no siol tiene can por favor tampoco se
Here the rule is until you see the
lo aquí la regla hasta que no ve el
paper I don't believe it Sometimes for a
papel no me lo creo A veces para una
something like that and for others not like that he plays his
cosa así y para otras no así juega su
double standards you have to see that not asking him
doble moral hay que ver que no le pedir
the paper to
el papel a
Loli movements close up angry face
Loli movimentos de cerca cara enfadada
Ugh, with the kids, it's around 1 o'clock.
Uf con la chavalería para a la 1 por ahí
I'm going with the kids, we're going out
me voy con la chavalería vamos a sacar
a little laugh here so that you can
un exactito aquí de risa para que lo
upload Lili is also double standards
suba a Lili también es la doble moral
I know no no but it's that even
sab no no pero es que incluso
Angel does it so that because he is
Ángel lo hace para que porque é está
obsessed with the community of
obsesionado con con la comunidad de
Juanjos a little bit no, we'll see that later.
juanjos un poco no eso ya lo veremos en
I know from the video if not
el vídeo me consta si no
repeat clearly Loli deleted the videos of
repite claro Loli borró los vídeos de
as if they were giving it to him
como quedó como si le estuvieran dando
the reason
la razón
You have to see that Loli is going crazy
a que hay que ver que Loli se le va la
mouth etc.
boca etcétera
etc.
etcétera
let's go with
vamos con
She with her we can give it Let's go
ella con ella podemos darle Vamos a
Let's give it to him, and as I say, you're right.
darle vamos darle y como digo ti razón
root you
raz ti
root
raz
this this what is he saying by
esto esto qu es lo que está diciendo por
Watch the end of that live video
Mira el final de ese directo un vídeo
made by cost him 10
hecho por le costó 10
don't remind me because I don't know
no recuérdamelo que no se me
I forgot what they wanted was that which
olvide lo que querían era eso que me
remove all this comes for the for the the
retirar todo esto viene por el por el el
straight
directo
sit di
seate di
When have you seen Pepa [ __ ] herself?
Cuándo has visto tú a la [__] cagarse
because Mr. Javier Oliveira tells me
porque el señor Javier oliveira me dice
that he's going to put one on me
que me va a poner una
The demand is true, the day has not been screwed up
demanda es verdad no se ha cagado la da
maybe things are as they are not you
igual las cosas como son no ustedes
They believe that he has defecated on some occasion
creen que en alguna ocasión se ha cagado
That's what she said, that's what she said, I didn't say it to her.
eso lo decía la eso se lo dijo No me
I agree who it was, that's what I think it is.
acuerdo quién fue es que eso creo que se
The ar of Troy and Loli said it but in
lo dijo el ar de Troya y la Loli pero en
I don't really think he [ __ ] himself.
realidad yo no creo que se haya cagado
never because I put one on it
nunca porque le ponga una
demand I think I would say this
demanda yo creo que ya diría este
while he puts it on me and it doesn't give it to me
mientras que me la pone y no no me da
Time It will come to me, eh or or or or
tiempo A mí que me llegue yo eh o o o o
His obsession was stronger than that.
podía más su obsesión que eso el que
you were scared
estaba cagado eres
you when you realized before
tú cuando te diste cuenta anteriormente
that Javi had already told him, I know what
que ya le había dicho Javi yo que sé lo
at least five or six times and you told me
menos cinco o seis veces y me dijiste
Pepa, you have a lawyer, but I am
[__] es que tú tienes abogado pero yo es
that I am and Loli also has a lawyer
que estoy y y Loli también tiene abogado
but what about me Antonio? Don't worry that
pero yo qué Antonio No te preocupes que
We will make an arrangement with my lawyer and
ya haremos un arreglo con mi abogado y
so you [ __ ] yourself, me you
así que el [__] te cagaste tú yo tú
When did you see me mess up a lawsuit?
cuándo me vist tu [__] por una demanda
of
de
of nor of anyone There are the live ones
de ni de nadie Ahí están los directos
that when the demand is made,
que cuando se hace lo de la demanda se
keep talking about Javi no no
sigue hablando de Javi que no no
I understand that, I stop talking about Javi.
entiendo eso de dejo de hablar de Javi
But if they are talking about Javi, he already
pero si están hablando de Javi si ya el
first that didn't put the first bofa ago
primer eso no puso el primer bofa hace
a year that I put it I recently in that
un año que lo puse Yo hace poco en eso
You're right, eh, I mean, I don't think so.
Tiene razón eh o sea yo no creo que esta
people will [ __ ] themselves over a lawsuit And I think
gente se cagaran por una demanda Y creo
that gives you
que le da
Same in private, you say Racel.
igual en privado dice racel tú
Do you think I think not? Eh, I think that they
crees Yo creo que no Eh Yo creo que les
it didn't matter much
daba un poco igual
eh when we put the first bur and
eh cuando nos pus el primer bur y
We keep talking because it is a one
seguimos hablando porque que es un un
fake [ __ ] the other guy who only
falso de [__] el otro tío que solo
He threatens with that, the one who [ __ ] himself was him
amenaza con eso el que se [__] fue él
Well, another lie is better, well, let's see.
pues otra mentira más vale bueno a ver
Of course not the truth when I sent him the
claro no a la verdad cuando le mandé el
First, they rectified what I asked for.
primer bofa rectificaron lo que le pedí
In that bofa then of course what are they going to do?
En ese bofa entonces claro A qué van a
fear also the issue is that the
temer además el tema es que que ya el
Last year, of course, I already started to to to
año pasado Claro ya empecé yo a a a
answer with the Freaky topic
contestar con el tema de los Freaky
tubers then of course there they would feel
tubers entonces claro ahí se sentirían
they are a little less pressured
ellos un poquito menos presionados
not another lie that we keep telling
no otra mentira que seguimos hablando
that is that he did not [ __ ] himself and he who does not have
que es que no se [__] y el que no tiene
lawyer eh we luckily have
abogado eh nosotros por suerte tenemos
a good lawyer and we have a great friendship
un buen abogado y tenemos mucha amistad
with the lawyer already explained here by
con el abogado ya se explicado aquí por
h and he knows if he gave it in a
h y é él lo sabe si é lo di en un
straight go lie okay go put
directo ve mintiendo vale fuy poniendo
I say sorry because I don't want any harm.
la Disculpa digo porque no quiero mal
the rolls in a story what he did
los rollos en una historia lo que hizo
be careful to see what she does, leave her
es ten cuidado a ver lo que hace déjala
let her see what she does let's see what she does
déjala a ver lo que hace a ver lo que
like this it was like this and you
hace así estaba Así estaba y que tú
you will enter so I will tell you that too
entraras tan eso te lo digo yo también a
from here you enter the Good
desde aquí que tú entrar en el Bueno le
They put the guasi mark, come on, see you later
pusieron marca guasi venga ya nos vemos
I'll read you privately, we talked about I don't know what
te leeré por privado hablamos no sé qué
sweetheart that's disgusting after
corazoncito eso es asqueroso después de
that the flight was treating us
que el vuelo estuviera tratándonos a
Peppa to Loli and Antonio at that moment
Peppa a Loli y Antonio en ese momento
fatal, I tell you that was it
fatal eso te lo digo yo que fue
disgusting that you were free It's that I am
asqueroso que eras libre Es que yo soy
free to enter wherever you want what you want
libre de entrar donde tú quieras lo que
you wanted you were free to enter What
tú quieras eras libre de entrar Lo que
you want or so let's see if I understand
tú quieras o sea a ver si yo entiendo
one thing that is being claimed here to
una cosa que le está reclamando aquí a
Tania correct me if I'm wrong
la Tania corregirme si me equivoco le
is claiming to Tania that Tania
está reclamando a Tania que Tania
enter the flight chat and say
entrase en el chat del vuelo y dijera
See you later, wasi mark with a heart
Hasta luego marca wasi con un corazón
man my self-criticism another five
hombre mi autocrítica otros cinco
members thanks hey ch okay today you are
miembros gracias oye ch vale hoy estáis
supporting the channel a lot
apoyando el canal un montón
eh Today you are supporting the channel
eh Hoy está hoy estáis apoyando el canal
a lot Thank you very much
un montón Muchas gracias
uncle
tío
who got angry with Tania because they
que se enfadaron con Tania porque les
It seemed ugly disgusting says angel that so
pareció feo asqueroso dice ángel que tan
appeared in the flight chat and said
apareciera en el chat del vuelo y dijera
Mar Kawasi we already spoke a heart Well
mar kawasi ya hablamos un corazón Pues
Don't you guys mess things up with me because
no me la lías ustedes a mi parda porque
I get angry with people who get together
yo me enfadas con gente que se juntara
with you guys, that is, and I was a censor
con ustedes o sea y era yo un censurador
a a how was I or rather was I
un un cómo era yo o sea era
a dictator not a How was I how is it
un un dictador no un Cómo era yo cómo es
what he said at the time that he didn't
lo que decía en el momento que no le
You listen to Javi, he wants to take everything from you.
haces caso a Javi te quiere quitar todo
Wow, they are proving me right all the time.
Wow Me van dando la razón en todo el
time uncle just like you are free to
tiempo tío igual que tú eres libre de
enter where you want to say what you
entrar donde tú quieres decir lo que tú
you want I am free to see what is
quieras Yo soy libre de ver lo que es
one and to give your opinion whatever you want, we're going something
una y de opinar lo que quiera vamos algo
ragman Ah something ragman
trapero Ah algo trapero
Ah well V okay v okay is that I believed
Ah bueno V vale v vale es que me creía
that you thought that was it
que ustedes pensabais de eso que eso era
Damn, [ __ ] what was that like? They told me that
[__] [__] Cómo era lo que me decían que
I was because I felt bad that friends
yo era porque me sentaba mal que amigos
Of course, they are so what the [ __ ]
No claro ellos de la tan qué [__]
They are also what I tell you, I gave you
son también te lo digo te di
moment your problem Thank you interpreted
momento su problema Gracias interpretó
everyone this happens like what happened
todo el mundo esto pasa como lo de lo
He didn't say anything about Javi's sexual harassment.
del acoso sexual de Javi él no lo dijo
but everyone interpreted it and here
pero todo el mundo lo interpretó y aquí
He didn't say anything but everyone did.
Él no dijo nada pero todo el mundo lo
interpreted but please uncle please
interpretó pero por favor tío por favor
given away 20 memberships and the topic of Loli
regalado 20 membresía y tema de que Loli
Huerta buys many wills and many
Huerta compra muchas voluntades y muchas
defenses because you should know better
defensas pues tú debes de saberlo mejor
that no one reigns you must from there there
que nadie reina tú debes de ahí ahí
there because there is a moment when it is
ahí porque hay un momento en que es
It is true that I
cierto que yo
I say no channel I support you and the
digo noo canal te apoyo a ti y a los
hooligans Thanks beautiful a kiss is that
macarras Gracias guapa un beso es que
Loli has many
Loli cumpla muchas
wills, eh, that's what Pepa said the other one
voluntades eh eso lo dijo [__] el otro
day eh eh I am not the wills that
día eh eh yo no estoy las voluntades que
buy buy Loli if you buy them
compra compra Loli si es que las compras
But Loli can do it with her money.
Pero es que Loli con el su dinero puede
do whatever you want to give it to
hacer lo que le dé la gana dárselo a
who wants how he wants and when he wants
quien quiere como quiere y cuando quiere
That Starting there and it is true that I
eso Empezando por ahí y cierto es que yo
well there what pppa said exactly
ahí bueno lo que dijo pppa exactamente
It was that Loli did many bad things, no
fue que Loli hacía muchas cosas malas no
He behaved badly with many people but
eh se portaba mal con mucha gente pero
that those who patted the
que los que le daban la palmadita a la
back because it gives a lot of money
espalda porque como da mucho dinero
maybe I was wrong when I said buy
quizás me equivoqué diciendo compra
wills because possibly yes I
voluntades pues posiblemente sí me
I was wrong. Oh, I was wrong.
equivoqué Ah se equivocado
But one thing is that I am wrong
pero una cosa es que yo me equivoque
saying it and something else is what I
diciéndolo y otra cosa es lo que yo
I can think to myself Oh [ __ ]
pueda pensar para mis adentro Ah [__]
but my rasel also has five members
pero mi rasel también cinco miembros
But what's happening here today is the family
Pero qué pasa aquí hoy familia es la
Puma party What's going on here no what
fiesta de la Puma Qué pasa aquí no que
You want to go to bed and you don't stop making
queréis a la cama no paráis de hacer
you keep achieving goals
objetivos no paráis de hacer
members says l Anne [ __ ] Pepa for a
miembros dice l Anne [__] [__] para una
true what you said and now you collect
verdad que dijiste y ahora recoges
cable or whatever but it's not that it picks up
cable o sea pero no no es que recoja
cable as such is saying that maybe
cable como tal está diciendo que tal vez
I shouldn't have said it. Although I did.
no tenía que Haberlo dicho Aunque lo
think that's what you're saying and
piense eso es lo que está diciendo y
for me inside I can think what to
para m me adentro puedo pensar lo que a
I feel like it, of course, now it's true.
mí me dé la gana claro ahora cierto es
that Loli buys not buys Of course She does it
que Loli compre no compre Claro Ella lo
think that's why she behaved like that
piensa por eso ella se comportaba con
Loli also like that because she does think so
Loli también así porque sí que lo piensa
What happens is that in a certain way it is
lo que pasa que ya en cierto modo Se
he sold not also to Loli Dale whether he does it or not
vendía no también a Loli Dale haga o no
do whatever you want
haga o lo que quiera
do because we're going to see him at 50 eh
hacer porque vamos a verlo de los 50 eh
the screenshot after that
lo de el pantallazo de después lo
He says, let's see, I have it, eh, I have it.
dice sa ver lo tengo yo eh me lo
You sent it, I have it, but I believe that
mandaste tú lo tengo yo pero lo creo que
He says it now better than
lo dice ahora mejor que
nobody because maybe Lori should
nadie porque a lo mejor el Lori debería
to tell everything that has been given to you
de contar todo de lo que te ha dado
and now this starts I'm going to pass it by
y ahora empieza esto lo voy a pasar por
adante because now say let's see
adante porque es que ahora decir a ver
Loli what has given you because I know
Loli lo que te ha dado a ti porque yo sé
what has given me to
lo que me ha dado a
me we have
mí nosotros tenemos
We are fine, only the superat begin
bien quedamos solo los superat empieza
with the deat theme and when although you
con el tema deat y cuando aunque tu
lawyer has said said
abogado ha dich dijo
Queen
Queen
sun here goes the topic Now of the 240 no
sol aquí va el tema Ya de los 240 no
year a memory that I remember is put in
anio un recuer Que yo recuerde se mete
It's not that they told him that he was
que no es que le hayan dicho que yoer
[ __ ] Remember that there are people who
[__] Recuerda que hay gente que le
said mand Well Antonio those same people
dijo mand Bueno Antonio esa misma gente
that he told you that I remember that he gave me that
que te dijo que recuerd que me dio que
it
lo
and you have taken the DEA wheelbarrow
y tú has cogido la carretilla de DEA
So let them take it out. Look, one day I will
pues que lo saquen Mirad tal día yo le
I didn't say anything about the visus, I didn't
di Yo no dije nada de los visus no me
It sounds like I mean, if I said it, it was making me
suena o sea yo si lo dije fue haciéndome
Echo Of what the ar of Troy said to me
Eco De lo que dijo el ar de Troya yo a
I know that there are people who said that
mí yo sé sí que hay gente como que dijo
Not here via chat or not via Twitter
por aquí por el chat no O por Twitter no
putting Oh but me too from Bon no
poniendo Ay pero yo también de Bon no
something of the good but of course never that
algo de los bon pero claro nunca eso
It was like in the air, it's not good to
quedó como en el aire no está bon a la
Pepa liar take it out piece of
[__] mentiroso sacarlo pedazo de
you bastards, you have no shame
cabrones que es que no tenes vergüenza
no liar you and the other one that that
ninguna mentiroso tú y el otro que eso
It is done for said [ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
se hace para dicho cabrón pedazo de
bastard told me now
cabrón me ha dicho Ahora
also [ __ ] because there is no lea if there is
también [__] porque no hay lea si hay
people really he says that he remembers it
gente realmente él dice que lo Recuerda
that there was bizum, that is, it is already entering
que hubo bizum O sea ya está metiendo
[ __ ] we have checked it
[__] nosotros lo hemos comprobado lo
We can say that we have checked it and
podemos decir que lo hemos comprobado y
No bizum was made because if not
no se hizo ningún bizum porque si no se
I would have said it because we didn't care
lo hubiera dicho porque nos daba igual
It became bizum because it became bitum but
se hizo bizum pues se hizo bitum pero
that was not done and that put this [ __ ]
que no se hizo y que meta esta [__]
lying again, let them take it out, let them
mintiendo otra vez que lo saquen que lo
take out
saquen
little people little war between Tania
gente pequeña pequeña guerra entre Tania
and we Tania and we Tania and
y nosotros Tania y nosotros Tania y
us
nosotros
Ok Tania, I'm explaining it because
vale Tania lo estoy explicando porque
That's what Tania says, but that was a year ago.
eso dice Tania Pero eso de hace un año
I don't understand what the point is now. Sorry, oh.
no entiendo ahora a qué viene Perdona Ay
that Tania has appeared in the chat and
que ha aparecido Tania en el chat y les
He said but that is from a year ago, right?
ha dicho pero eso es de hace un año no
I understand now what's coming
entiendo ahora qué viene
Ah Tania you, I mean Tania you are me
Ah Tania tú o sea Tania tú me estás
taking out my video of me insulting
sacando a mi vídeo de yo insultando a
people
gente
There's one in particular that I hate.
Eh en concreto hay uno en el que me cago
in an aunt that I call a [ __ ]
en en una tía que le digo hija de [__]
Go suck an old man or something.
Vete a chupártela a un viejo o algo así
Come on, you're taking that click out of me
va tú me estás sacando ese click que
belongs exactly listen to me Tania to
pertenece exactamente escúchame Tania al
2015 is worth 2015 that you don't even know why
2015 vale al 2015 que ni sabes por qué
I was insulting that disgusting woman
estaba insultando yo a esa asquerosa
ok you don't even know and and that cli yes no
vale que ni lo sabes y Y ese cli sí no
you have uploaded a video there not with that click
has subido t un vídeo ahí no con ese cli
no good he has uploaded 800 videos with that
no bueno ha subido 800 vídeos con ese
That one seems fine to you, right, Tania?
cli ese sí te parece bien verdad Tania
But that's from a year ago, no no.
Pero eso Si es de hace un año no no
but I came in late Tania all that is coming
pero entré tarde Tania todo eso viene
because we are explaining again to the
porque estamos explicando otra vez a la
people that how the fight came between of
gente eso cómo vino la pelea entre de
Troy and we for this comes everything and
Troya y nosotros por esto viene todo y
there is so involved and for this reason
ahí está involucrada tan y por esto de
This is because it was a bit of a fight and
esto porque fue un poco la pelea Y
then like Antonio who at that moment
entonces como Antonio que en ese momento
He was a friend of ours and as he says neither
era amigo nuestro y como él dice tampoco
I knew you when you were doing
te conocía cuando tú estabas haciendo
all these super bad things against
todas estas cosas super chungas contra
my mother, you went straight
mi madre que te tiraste un directo
splitting my mother or not wanting it was a
rajando mi madre o no quiera fue una
thing that the audios the audios cone Y
cosa que los audios los audios cono Y
people who do not have tennis start to upload
emp a subir gente que sí que no tenis
Host friendship It's true Tania took out
amistad [__] Es verdad la Tania sacó
some audios also private
unos audios también privados
related to Peppa Pig not that they
relacionados con la Peppa no que les
He changed his voice to get it out, I don't know what.
cambió la voz para sacarlo no sé qué
history no and get monthly money
historia no y conseguir dinero mensual
to get my father out of where he is
para sacar a mi padre de dónde está
Because I don't want my residency to stop
Porque no quiero que mi resid para para
stop that, you will not forget it
para para eso no se te va a olvidar a ti
The first thing you have to do is not
lo primero que tienes que hacer es no
leaving a job does not double the wolf that
irte de un trabajo no doblar el lobo que
You didn't even get a break because you said goodbye
no cogiste ni paro porque te despediste
You alone because he says you were already there
Tú solito porque dice que ya estabas
fed up and that it hurt your balls to me
harto y que te dolía las pardas a mí me
the paras still hurt many times and
sigue doliendo las paras muchas veces y
a lot of boxes of coca-cola and you told him
mucha caja de coca-cola y le dijiste a
your community that you were on leave for a
tu comunidad que estabas de baja por una
knee when it was a lie that you
rodilla cuando era mentira que tú te
you had fired only Well if so much
habías despedido solo Pues si tanta
You need to take your father out there.
falta te haces de sacar a tu padre allí
that your father has his pension and is
que tu padre tiene su pensión y se está
paying
pagando
Hey, what Peppa just told you.
su Oye esto que acaba de contar Peppa
It is also a private sphere, right?
también es del ámbito privado no o qué
Peppa has just told that the one from Troy
acaba de contar Peppa que al de Troya
He deceived his followers and told them that
engañó a sus seguidores y les dijo que
was on sick leave while in reality
estaba de baja mientras que en realidad
was not of
no estaba de
low but he knew he was gone from work
baja sino que sabía ido el del trabajo
because his back was already hurting
porque le daba le dolía ya la espalda
with 50
con 50
years this would be in the private sphere or or
años esto sería del ámbito privado o o
This is not going to be something that people are going to fear.
esto no Esto se lo van a fear a la gente
or or what Or your residence depends on it
o o qué O depende su residencia que la
has here in this pain I think that is it
tiene aquí en este pena creo que es eso
It's a lie You're making yourself a victim And I don't
es mentira Te estás victimizando Y no me
It gives the Gan that people believe you
da la Gan que la gente te crea
If your father has a short pension, he will be high.
s tu padre tiene su pensión corta alta
I don't know and he pays his own way
yo no lo sé y él se paga su propia
Eh, this is so don't come to me with that I
Eh Esto así que no me vengas con que yo
I am guilty that your father is in a
soy culpable de que tu padre esté en una
residence and you who are lazy don't
residencia y tú que eres un vago No te
put to pick bjena and and and cucumber Ah or
pongas a [__] bjena y y y pepino Ah o
whether you are blaming ar for
sea que estás responsabilizando a ar de
Troy to Peppa that his channel
Troya a a la Peppa de que su canal de
YouTube is like
YouTube es como
Uncle you, you don't have a YouTube channel.
tío tú Tú no tienes un canal de YouTube
as
como
to pretend to depend on him
para pretender depender de él
it's true it's true
es verdad es verdad
says to say where the residence of the
dice decir dónde está la residencia del
father is a little private too no no
padre es un poco privado también no no
but those are unimportant things
pero eso son cosas sin importancia
alne they can do that
alne eso lo pueden
Say no as long as you don't know something
decir no Mientras que no sea sabes algo
What do Javi do? No, nothing happens, but
que haga Javi No no pasa nada que pero
this guy who
este tío que
intends to make a living from Youtube with which
pretende vivir de Youtube con el que
has well that's how it goes So it goes all the way
tiene pues así va Así que va por toda
Of course, that's how it goes, but look at the
claro Así va por toda Pero mira el
victimhood, he already did this when he said
victimismo este ya lo hizo cuando dijo
that he was going to leave the Enton channel at that time
que iba a dejar el canal Enton esa época
He said, do you remember? Look, I'll put it on for you.
dijo te acuerdas Mira te lo voy a poner
here he just put on his channel
aquíel acaba de poner en su canal
tactic of was
táctica de fue
November 21st
del 21 de noviembre
the same tactic as the flight ends is valid
vale la misma táctica de del vuelo acaba
to put on your channel 12 or 13
de poner en su canal de 12 o 13
I'm going to disconnect for a minute
minut voy a desconectar durante una
week of all this fuss during these
semana de todo este follón durante estos
days I will meditate if it is worth continuing
días meditaré Si merece la pena seguir
herein
en esta
platform see you in a week and Os
plataforma nos vemos en una semana y Os
I will share my decision. Thank you.
haré partícipe de mi decisión Gracias
for your support in
por vuestro apoyo en
serious and get monthly money for
serio y conseguir dinero mensual para
take my father where he is because he is not
sacar a mi padre dónde está Porque no
I want to reside
quiero resid
for I don't take it away and you are seeing all the
para no quito y estáis viendo todas las
contradictions that we have sought for
contradicciones que le hemos buscado la
he lies, contradicting himself
mentira él mismo contradiciéndose a sí
Same thing if you don't take it off, do one
mismo vale que si no te quit hac una
comma let's see here about the grap of
coma vamos a ver aquí lo de la grap de
that you saw the staple not the staple
que viste la grapa no lo de la grapa lo
from the staple the thing of the
de la grapa lo de la
staple the arm close to the body and
grapa el brazo pegado al cuerpo y la
I have seen the scar of
cicatrice Yo la he visto la cicatriz de
the back the day I go out dancing with the
la palda el día que salo bailando con la
Palma keeps his arm close to his body if
Palma lleva el brazo pegado al cuerpo si
remove not even a comma Eh, don't remove even one
quita ni una coma Eh no quita ni una
eat eh these words Eh the day that
coma eh estas palabras Eh el día que
He came out with his arm stuck to the leather and
salió lleva el brazo pegado al cuero y
the scar I have seen the scar
la cicatrice Yo la he visto la cicatriz
of the shovel the day he went out dancing with
de la pala el día que salió bailando con
the dove has its arm glued to the
la paloma lleva el brazo pegado al
body if you notice only moves the arm
cuerpo si os fijáis solo mueve el brazo
of the dove and was raging with pain
de la paloma y estaba rabiando de dolor
because she has to do it by force
porque ella por [__] tiene que hacer
dancing video Oh poor Loli by
vídeo bailando Ay la pobre Loli por
balls I had to make a video dancing eh what
[__] teía hacer vdeo bailando eh que
I've seen the scar, huh? What did you see?
yo he visto la cicatriz eh Para que vios
that was fine and I knew I couldn't
que estaba bien y yo sabía que no poda
be fine because he had his back
estar bien porque llevaba la espalda
open [ __ ] Oh, that's why I was wearing it
abierta [__] Ay es que llevaba la
open back [ __ ] glued to the
espalda abierta [__] pegado al
body
cuerpo
liar a comma Eh does not remove even one
mentiroso una coma Eh no quita ni una
comma eh I think you're not ready for
coma eh creo que no estáis listos para
this moment but you have to see it no
este momento pero tenéis que verlo no
Are you ready? Let's see it. Let's see it.
estáis listos lo vamos a verlo vamos a
We remember seeing her from when she was discharged, she was fine.
verlo recordamos ya del alta ella bien
in a live we are going to see
le mamente en un directo vamos a ver a
Loli and having surgery is not worth it.
Loli y ser operado no vale a ver
transition well this is Loli well The
transición bueno Esta es Loli pues El
God of high The God of high will go to her
Dios del alta El Dios del alta la vay a
See, I have it without music, that's Loli.
ver la tengo sin música ojo esa es Loli
recently operated This video was made for
recién operada Este vídeo lo hizo para
us and he said please hang it up
nosotros y me dijo por favor cuélgalo
so that people see that we are fine
para que la gente vea que estamos bien
porch between the trip and everything then
porcho por entre el viaje y todo pues
Between Pepa and I we haven't done anything.
entre [__] yo no hemos hecho nada no
We have Mira Loli eh the dances that are
hemos Mira Loli eh los bailes que se
hit eh a heroine eh Loli dancing
pega eh una heroína eh Loli bailando
so that all followers can see that
para que todos los seguidores vean que
be well and don't worry about
estén bien y que no se preocupen por
She eh after having had an operation
ella eh después de haberse operado un
lung cancer and aers have been put
cáncer del pulmón y aers se he puesto
tits
tetas
Okay, we haven't done it, we haven't done it
vale No le hemos hecho no lo hemos
public today Look Today is a perfect day
público hoy Mira Hoy es un día perfecto
to make it public the arm attached to
para hacerlo público el brazo pegado a
the back Look take it like this does like the
la espalda Mira toma así hace como el
ma
ma
holy [ __ ] dude, not even in his [ __ ]
[__] ostia tío es que ni en su [__]
channel is used to take the uncle to
canal sirve para llevarse ooste tío para
lie Uncle says col menero doesn't do that
mentir Tío dice col menero no hace así
Look, I'm going to discharge you, eh? Look how I am.
mira manda del alta eh Mira cómo estoy
They put a cream on me and well more
me han puesto una crema y bueno má
repaired as well as the science films
reparado así como las películas ciencia
fans, you have a bullet hole here
aficción tienes aquí un agujero de bala
It's okay, they give you a little cream when you
pasa nada te echan una cremita cando
He does that with the dove, the gesture is noticeable
hace eso con la paloma se nota el gesto
on the face the laughter on the face of pain
en la cara el riso en la cara de dolor
because it has an open back for
porque tiene la espalda abierta para
to take the lung and everything they did to him
opar el pulmón y todo lo que le hicieron
be be amazing c hor operation is
ser ser increíble c hor operación está
describing Loli's situation there
describiendo la situación de Loli ahí
where you see her she is raging about this
donde la veis está rabiando de s est es
Loli This is Loli another one is dying
Loli Esta es Loli otra se está muriendo
Loli is in bed for a good part, eh?
en la cama buen parte está Loli eh está
Loli ch a heroine who called the pony
Loli ch una herina que que llaba el pón
It's Loli of my life, eh powerful
es es Loli mío de mi vida eh poderoso
Sir Don Dinero No, because I believe
caballero Don Dinero No porque yo creo
that friendship authorized me to love yes
que la amistad me autorizó el amor sí
but friendship and husband are seen behind
pero la amistad y el marido se ve detrás
authorized it to be seen as I said it
autorizó a que se viese tal cual dije lo
I cut out and say no no I don't want him to see it
recorto dice no no no quiero que lo vea
the whole husband is behind for those
todo el marido est detrás por aquellos
who wonder where the husband is
que se preguntan Dónde está el marido
that doesn't stop her, that I don't know what Loli is, there is no
que no la frena que no s qué Loli no hay
Whoever stops her, Loli does what she wants.
qui la frene Loli hace lo que le da la
wins diamente invents what gives him the
gana diamente se inventa lo que le da la
win vi of Ah look perfo siemo much norm
gana vi de Ah mira perfo siemo much norm
the first part of Peppa that is Loli
la primera parte de Peppa esa es Loli
operated nice
operada bonito
Nice thing about the grpa when it comes, right?
bonito lo de la grpa cuando viene no sí
you've said it before you've said it before
lo has dicho antes lo has dicho al
In the beginning you said no before but you have
principio has dicho antes no pero habéis
seen how he talks about Loli as if she were
visto como habla de Loli como si fuera
a heroine you know a one that's Loli
una heroína una sabes un un esa es Loli
That's Loli, nobody can stop Loli, dude.
esa es Loli a Loli no la frena nadie tío
that what you want is money for not
que lo que quieres es pasta por no
you want to go to work lazy lazy head
quieres ir a trabajar vago vago cabeza
knee
rodilla
loser works a little
pringado trabaja un poco
lazy
vago
Hey Antonio, I'll tell you about the grass.
eh Antonio lo de la grama te lo
You invented it But come on Take my Peppa
inventaste tú Pero vamos Toma mi Peppa
very well and you made up that thing
muy bien y tú te inventaste lo de
Peppa pomegranate, each of you invented one
granada Peppa cada uno os inventaste una
something to play along with for the money
cosa para seguirle el rollo por la pasta
Loli the ard of Troy invented the thing about
Loli el ard de Troya se inventó lo de
the staples and you invented the thing
las grapas y tú te inventaste lo de
grenade that I have a clip of yours here
granada que que tengo aquí un clip tuyo
Wait, I think I have it here at hand.
Espera que creo que lo tengo aquí a mano
Also look
además Mira
Peppa, the click I have here will see you.
Peppa el click que tengo aquí te va verá
How funny it is
Qué gracioso es
If you load me, let's see if I
Si me carga a ver si me
load if it loads me if it loads me if it loads me
carga si me carga si me carga si me
[Music]
[Música]
load I have a cli Ah we have seen it a thousand
carga tengo un cli Ah lo hemos visto mil
sometimes if Ah it doesn't load this I have a
veces si Ah no me carga este tengo un
Click it We were watching it the other day
click lo Estuvimos viendo el otro día
Peppa where you bet your channel you
Peppa donde tú te apostaba tu canal te
I bet your channel is worth it because you had
apostaba tu canal vale porque tú habías
seen that Loli was in Granada with
visto de que Loli estuvo en Granada con
Marta and Antonio David then each one
Marta y Antonio David entonces cada uno
you invented yourselves
os inventaste
Today the Trojan said that Peppa
un hoy ha dicho el troyano que la Peppa
you take the pills two by two
se toma las pastillas de dos en dos qué
today the level has risen like this
hoy ha subido el nivel así
Russell
russel
Hey Peppa, each of you did and followed him.
eh Peppa cada uno hiciste y le seguiste
the Loli roll for pasta like I eat
el rollo a la Loli por pasta como como a
Loli fancied her because she was a
Loli se la antojaba porque era una
heroine who danced with a dove shape
heroína que bailaba con una paloma forma
tremendous because you know perfectly well that
tremenda pues tú sabes perfectamente que
Loli explained to us that they had done a
Loli nos explicó que le habían hecho un
hole here on the side And from there
agujero aquí en el costado Y desde ahí
they had done to him what they had to do
le habían hecho lo que le tenían que
do never said about the staple and in a
hacer jamás dijo lo de la grapa y en un
directly you said Peppa knows the
directo tú dijiste la Peppa sabe la
Peppa has seen I haven't seen anything
Peppa ha visto Yo no he visto nada la
Peppa is the one who knows, she should explain it.
Peppa es la que lo sabe que lo explique
the pppa and I never wanted to talk about it
la pppa y yo nunca quise hablar de eso
I'm not going to talk about it, I've never seen it.
ni voy a hablar de eso yo nunca he visto
staples nor have I seen scars nor have I
grapas ni he visto cicatrices ni he
seen nothing but no
visto nada pero no
I doubt what Loli had. Well, don't you
eh dudo de lo que Loli tuvo Pues no te
I had used the wrong word but it's that
había equivocado de palabra pero es que
With these people you never know where you're going.
con esta gente no sabes nunca por dónde
You stop seeing these people for a week.
van dejas de verlo una semana esta gente
and you don't know where they are going because he didn't say
y no sabes por dónde van pues no dijo
that he had made a mistake
que se había equivocado de
a word that she had not invented
palabra que ella no se había inventado
the cancer but that it had
lo del cáncer sino que se había
wrong and had said cancer instead
equivocado y había dicho cáncer en vez
of
de
biopsy How is he saying now
biopsia Cómo que ahora está diciendo
again that does not doubt what
otra vez que no duda de lo que
had but let's see the Troy card no
tuvo pero vamos a ver el ard de Troya no
There are some audios saying that LoL
tiene unos audios diciendo que que LoL
does not have cancer and has been treated
no tiene cáncer y se la ha estado
inventing and defending it and then
inventando y defendiéndola y luego la
Peppa also has other audios
Peppa también tiene otros audios
saying I don't know what and that he had gotten into trouble
diciendo no sé qué y que se había liado
with the
con las
totally words
palabras totalmente
self-criticism jav despite everything me
autocrítica jav a pesar de todo me
I feel very proud to have them in
siento muy orgullosa de tenerlos en
against us please this rabble
nuestra contra por favor esta gentuza
always
siempre
opposite for me There are two sides yes
enfrente para m Existen dos bandos sí
It is true that for me there are two
que es verdad que para mí Existen dos
sides in this sense the war with this
lados en este sentido la guerra con esta
people in other topics it does not matter is worth in
gente en otros temas da igual vale en
others come out such but what they are with the
otros sal tal pero lo que son con los
geeks for me There are two sides one
frikis para mí Existen dos bandos unos
We are the good ones and others are
somos nosotros en la bueno y otros son
Those who defend all this, well,
los que defienden pues bueno a tod esta
People, but the thing about the staples, that's what you need.
gente pero lo de las grapas eso te lo
you invented it so I don't know how to look good or
inventaste tú para no sé quedar bien o
I have no idea why when I
no tengo ni idea porque yo cuando
I heard to say that not of the staple no
escuché para decir eso no de la grapa no
have you seen the scar what it says I have
ha visto la cicatriz lo que dice yo he
seen the scar what it says yes no but
visto la cicatriz lo que dice sí no pero
then he says the whole back full of
luego dice toda la espalda llena de
staples is there is a
grapas es hay un
moment and no Loli didn't have her back
momento y no Loli no tenía la espalda
full of staples and now we say di
llena de grapas y ahora decimos di
antoito look look
antoñito Mira mira
look not a comma of everything I said in
mira ni una coma de todo lo que dije en
your moment ole t ole your egg ole you
su momento ole t ole tu huevo ole tu
egg
huevo
Moreno has cancer and has never had it.
Moreno tiene cáncer no ha tenido nunca
cancer var yours I do not remove even a comma
cáncer var tuya no quito ni una coma
You know what happens to these people who
sabéis qué pasa con esta gente que al
In the end, they're going to end up killing me.
final matándose me van a terminar dando
the reason in the end they are going to kill me
la razón al final matándose me van a
end up giving the reason and will say
terminar dando la razón y va a decir
Look, Loli didn't have cancer, you take it.
mira Loli no tuvo cáncer tú te lo
you invented Well you took the money from him
inventaste Pues tú le sacaste el dinero
Well, in this conversation you told him
pues tú en esta conversación le dijiste
that I would give you whatever it is because you
que te diera para lo que sea pues tú le
You told me to give it to me for I don't know how much and
dijiste que me diera para no sé cuánto y
In the end they will end up Well with all the
al final terminarán Pues con todo el por
ass they've been giving us, giving us the
culo que han estado dándonos dándonos la
reason they invented a cancer
razón se inventaron un cáncer se
They invented this, they invented the others. And
inventaron esto se inventaron los otr Y
That's how it is and Loli didn't have the
es que eso es así y no Loli no tenía la
back full of staples now we say to
espalda llena de grapa ahora decimos a
See what Antonio says. Look, look, look.
ver lo que dice antoñito Mira mira mira
comma not a comma of all that I said in
comao ni una coma de todo lo que dije en
your moment, ole you, ole your egg, ole you
su momento ole tú ole tu huevo ole tu
Brown egg I like it that way I like it that way
huevo Moreno Así me gusta Así me gusta
Loli does not have cancer, she has never had it.
Loli no tiene cáncer no ha tenido nunca
cancer has for you I no longer remove even one
cáncer ha para tu ya no quito ni una
I like it like this. Loli doesn't have cancer.
coma Así me gusta Loli no tiene cáncer
has never had
no ha tenido nunca
cancer for yours I do not remove even a comma
cáncer paraas tuyas no quito ni una coma
Brown egg I like it that way I like it that way
huevo Moreno Así me gusta Así me gusta
Loli does not have cancer, she has never had it.
Loli no tiene cáncer no ha tenido nunca
cancer has for yours I do not remove even one
cáncer ha para tuyas no quito ni una
eat one that I do not speak of
coma unom que yo no hablo de
oliveira up gets scratched
oliveira para arriba se arañe para
you have had to take it up now
arriba ha tenido que [__] ustedes ya
because she doesn't talk about Jav Oliveira
porque que ella no habla de jav oliveira
so that Javi can scratch himself up
para que Javi olira se arañe para arriba
I can't take this anymore today, I can't take this anymore
yo no puedo más con esto hoy yo con esto
today I don't know if I should continue, eh? Like with me.
hoy no si de seguir eh Como conmigo le
I cut the roll because the ham was
he cortado el rollo porque el jamón se
I think I'm going to buy it from you.
lo vaya a comprar a ustedes me parece
is
est
Christmas that I have to go out and say
navidades que yo tenga que salir a decir
something else an Thank you very much eh an Thank you
algo más an Muchas gracias eh an Gracias
because he called me a piece of [ __ ] a while ago
por me ha llamado pedazo de cabrón hace
for a while don't let go of my limb, my arm
un rato no suélteme el miembro el brazo
the member tells the pier what he grabbed
el miembro dice la pier lo que agarrado
We can't hear you, mom, we can't hear you
no se te escucha mamá no se te escucha
He is taking the gentleman's stake
él está cogiendo el la esta del señor
Javier Lira said
Javier Lira que decía
don't let me pass, remember me because
que no me de pas se acuerda de mí porque
the other one said it like the uncle member
el otro lo ha dicho comem el miembro tío
but if it is not, no, it cannot be, eh?
pero si es que no no no puede ser eh
but apart from that it is not true or
pero aparte que no que no es verdad o
whether they keep sending me clicks like that
sea si a mí me siguen mandando click así
He makes mentions of it every day, yes.
a diario hace menciones por ahí sí que
It is true that he is trying as
es verdad que está intentando como
control yourself that it is okay, it is not okay
controlarse que está bien no está bien
Javi Oliveira is hard to get off the hook, but
desengancharse Javi oliveira cuesta Pero
it's okay it's okay it's okay little by little
está bien está bien está bien poco a
little at least he tries for it
poco por lo menos lo intenta por lo
At least now he's trying, it's true.
menos ahora lo está intentando es verdad
let go of my member, my arm, my member
suélteme el miembro el brazo el miembro
the leg says what you cannot hear
dice la pierna lo que no se te escucha
Mom, I can't hear you, he's [ __ ]
mamá no se te escucha él está cogiendo
the essay of Mr. Javier Lira who
el la estra del señor Javier Lira que
He said, let go of my member. Now then.
decía suéltame el miembro Pues ahora
wants to be a Javi Oliveira 2.0
quiere ser un Javi oliveira 2.0 su
I repeat many things, many things
muchas cosas repito muchas cosas
Let me go, I'll pass you your ass because M is here
suéltamelo te paso de tu culo que M está
death I stopped giving a long time ago
muerte Hace mucho tiempo que deje de dar
by ass
por culo
Aunt of you already brings out the artist that you carry
tía de to ya saca el artista que llevas
Inside Look there is an interview with Kiko
dentro Mira hay una entrevista de Kiko
Hernanda to this lady to this lady
hernanda a esta señora a esta señora
where she talks about that husband she said
donde habla de ese marido que ella decía
who had been 10 years younger than
que había tenido 10 años más joven que
He behaved superbly with his son who was
se portaba superb con su hijo que era
wonderful but she didn't feel anything
maravilloso pero que ella no sentía nada
for him when he got married than when he was
por él cuando se casó que cuando se lo
took him on a trip and got him drunk for
llevó de viaje lo emborrachó durante
night after night and in the morning
noche tras noche y por la mañana le
I said, oh, he gave me a [ __ ]. I'm here.
decía ay me ha hecho un polv estoy
still freaking out hahaha And he says boy
flipando todavía Jajaja Y dice muchach
I remember that I saw it and it
yo me acdo que hab vista y lo
He got drunk night after night on that and
emborrachaba noche tras noche en eso y
then when he came back he did the same
luego cuando vino de vuelta se hizo lo
made him spend money for the wedding
hizo que gastar dinero para la boda
spend money on her honeymoon
gastarse dinero en viaje de novia Ella
he was not left without a trip, he does not forgive
no se iba quedado sin viaje no perdona
but the honeymoon and everything stops
pero el viaje de novio y todo lo para
Here I am, go smart
aqu yo eh anda listillo
Here I put context here an interview
aquí pongo contexto aquí una entrevista
What did Kiko Nandez do to my mother?
que le hizo Kiko nández eh a mi madre
when he left Big Brother
cuando salió de gran hermano
eh he was talking to him about his
eh le le estuvo hablando de de su
ex-husband who if I don't know what her ex-boyfriend
exmarido que si no sé qué que su exnovio
and he lied saying he was the ex-husband
y él mintió diciendo que era el exmarido
who was being talked about in that
de quien se estaba hablando en en esa
interview when they were talking about the
entrevista cuando se estaba hablando del
very different ex-boyfriend and even the
exnovio muy diferente y incluso los
your subscribers told you for sure
suscriptores suyos le dijeron seguro
Antonio who is like that and said Sure sure
Antonio que es así y decía Seguro seguro
We already denied it. So this other one
ya lo desmentimos O sea que esta otra
we're going to call it a lie
mentira la vamos a llamar la
lie wait in public even
mentira espérate en público incluso
Angel says that he has very good memories
Ángel dice que é tiene muy buen recuerdo
The truth is that I do have something about David.
de él la verdad que de David si tengo
good memory, eh, I have good ones
buen recuerdo eh que yo tengo buen
memory of the husband not the ex-boyfriend who
recuerdo del marido no del exnovio que
I was in the interview no matter how much my
estaba en la entrevista por mucho que mi
mother you stopped believing go in the
madre tú dejaste de creer anda en el
The channel I started doesn't want to be put on
canal que empecé yo no se quiere poner
a little bit true that I am a
un poquito verdad que yo a mí Soy un
Tempan I haven't read the interview yet.
tempan no me pasado leer la entrevista
what did she do to Kiko Hernandez that she
que le hizo a Kiko Hernández de que ella
She was the woman abused by that husband and
era la Mujer maltratada por ese marido y
Everything I said is for that husband, not that one.
todo lo que dic es por ese marido no ese
husband not for boyfriend Ah okay, so eh
marido no por el novio Ah vale o sea eh
Peppa suffered or told an episode of
Peppa sufrió o contó un episodio de
abuse With an ex-partner Vale and him and him
maltrato Con una expareja Vale y el y el
angel of another ex-partner says he has
ángel de otra expareja dice que tiene
good memory and the ard of Troy is
buen recuerdo y el ard de Troya está
mixing the two in the same no That
mezclando a los dos en el mismo no Esa
That's the move Russell So
es la Esa es la movida russel O sea que
Hey, he's like telling his son that
eh está como diciéndole al hijo que
has good memories of the abuser
tiene buen recuerdo del maltratador de
your mother that's what she's trying to do
su madre eso es lo que está intentando
roll
liar
not that Pepa who looks at how that guy is
no esa [__] que fijarse como es tío ese
That Antonio Troya That is
ese Antonio Troya Ese es
Antonio is Antonio, why do I say the end?
Antonio es Antonio para que digo final
I who always maintain the same
yo que mantengo siempre lo mismo
saying the same thing you know and what else
diciendo lo mismo sabes Y qué más
We can put it now, I think, with this
podemos poner ya yo creo que ya con esto
let's see
a ver
Thank goodness I praised that for you to see.
Menos mal que loos eso para que veáis
how how of course people who don't know the
cómo cómo claro la gente que no sabe la
people who don't know listen to this and say
gente que no sabe le Escucha esto y dice
you have to go You have to go but after
hay que va Hay que ve pero después de
all this showing the live shows that
todo esto mostrando los directos que
we have done a little work
nosotros hemos hecho un pequeño Trabajo
of research here and this is already known
de investigación aquí ya esto eso se
remains as another lie Work of
queda como otra mentira Trabajo de
research has done, what a great job
investigación ha hecho eh qué trabajazo
Wait, we're done with this.
Espérate que con esto ya hemos terminado
My goodness, the work has invaded a little bit.
madre mía poquito s el trabo invación ha
made my today eh A
hecho mi hoy eh A
see but this lasts 14
ver pero esto dura 14
seconds
segundos
rassel this what do you not realize that
rassel esto qué no os dais cuenta de que
live shows always start when
siempre empiezan los directos Cuando se
wants to victimize that he has had bad
quiere victimizar que ha tenido malos
It's been days, I don't know how many, it says breads are
días lleva no sé cuántos dice panes es
saying no can't stand Two glasses of wine and
decir no aguanta Dos copas de vino y
hold on to the bread-sayings
aguanta los dice panes
doubles how how
dobles cómo cómo
Don't you realize that it always starts
no os dais cuenta de que siempre empieza
the direct ones When you want to victimize
los directos Cuando se quiere victimizar
that he has had bad days, he has I don't know
que ha tenido malos días lleva no sé
how many days with bread, that is, it does not last
cuántos días c panes es decir no aguanta
Two glasses of wine and you can eat 10 loaves of bread.
Dos copas de vino y aguanta los 10 panes
doubles that is the most logical and normal thing
dobles eso es de lo más lógico y normal
What she is saying is that no, that
ella lo que está diciendo es que no que
It's a lie that it hasn't taken two days
es mentira que no ha tomado dos días ese
bread that's what he's saying and what it is
pan eso es lo que está diciendo y qué es
what you told me that
lo que me habéis dicho que
look what look
mire que mire
himself
el mismo
I refuse directly. Ah No, of course not this one.
directo me niego Ah No claro este no
this and at the end a video that I had made
este y al final un vídeo que había hecho
The Angel alone, look, he has done a
el Ángel solito Ay mira ha hecho un
video by itself Let's see, let's see it
vídeo el solito A ver vamos a verlo
look at it, yo, let's see
míralo ayo a ver
year
ao
this inside
esto dentro
Ole H but this has been edited
ole H pero si esto esto lo ha editado
like My dad editing my video of me
como Mi padre editando mi vídeo de mi
first birthday
primer cumpleaños
[Music]
[Música]
epic
épico
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Enjoy, the live show is about to end.
disfruten se va a acabar el directo va a
the text lasts longer than the video
durar más el texto que el vídeo
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
no ah
no ah
I'm going to answer you for the last time because
voy a responderle por última vez porque
step of your
paso de tu
ass 43 years old the baby 43 years old the
culo 43 años la guagüita 43 años la
baby
guagüita
[Laughs]
[Risas]
Hey, this is wonderful!
Oye esto qué maravilla
eh Oh I can't I can't I can't I wish
eh Ay no puedo no puedo no puedo ojalá
I would have made a video like this for myself
me hubiera hecho a mí un vídeo así
I also feel it
también yo me lo
I deserved it, I wish it had been done to me
merecía ojalá me hubiera hecho a mí
also a video like this
también un vídeo así
eh Oh look Oh look there you have to
eh Ay que ve Ay que ve hay que
see the amount of things one has to read
ver la de cosas que tiene uno que lee
there is that there is that
hay que hay que
see but you do find out so that 1
ver pero tú sí que te enteres para que 1
eur can be thrown away
eur se puede tirar por de
Uruguay has had a bit of a crazy night
Uruguay ha tenido una noche un poco loca
Peppa guys I'm leaving I'm leaving eh I'm leaving
la Peppa chicos me voy me voy eh Me voy
with this epic closing
con este cierre épico
Hey, I'm leaving.
Eh me voy
a d has that Javi makes me feel dirty for
a d tien que Javi me siento sucia por
having seen that face of nausea but I
haber visto eso cara de nuseas pero yo
I've been here for almost 4 hours
llevo aquí casi 4 horas
Dude, I've been here for 4 hours, holding on.
tío llevo 4 horas eh aquí eh aguantando
Hey, I'm going to the kids' room for a bit.
eh Me voy para la chavalería un ratito
come on So it's 1 o'clock Let's go
venga Así que son las 1 men1 Vamos a ir
a little while for the kids, come on
un ratillo para la chavalería venga va
We're going to go there for a while
vamos ir un ratillo para all para la
kids come family A kiss
chavalería venga familia Un beso
very handsome I don't know I think not tomorrow
guapísimos no sé ya creo que mañana no
We'll see you tomorrow weekend
nos veremos mañana fin de de semana
Tomorrow I'm going to the movies with the kids. Okay.
mañana voy al cine con los niños Bueno
Let's all go So tomorrow I think not
vamos todos Así que mañana creo que no
us
nos
We'll see, we'll upload some videos and so on.
veremos subiremos algún videíto y demás
You already know about these, I'll send you these on my cell phone.
ya sabéis de estos con el móvil os mando
a huge kiss
un besote enorme
and have a good time, behave well, it's worth it
y Y pasarlo bien portaros bien vale el
Sunday we will see Marina and
domingo nos veremos con Marina y
Let's hope that this ugly topic stays.
esperemos que ese tema feo pues se quede
there but
ahí pero
Well, we look handsome, I rested, okay?
bueno Nos vemos guapos que descansé vale
I'm going to the youth if you want
me voy para la chavalería si queréis
go there, see you there
tirar para allá allí nos vemos